<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<Raíz>
    <ContadorDVD>70</ContadorDVD>
    <UniqueID>123</UniqueID>
    <ContadorVistos>87</ContadorVistos>
    <ContadorSinVer>92</ContadorSinVer>
    <Timestamp>1573484233807</Timestamp>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="1" contador="1">
        <Nombre>Miles Davis - Miles Electric: A Different Kind of Blue</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 64</Id>
        <Annus>2004</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>Description: Widely considered one of the landmark albums in history and the starting point for jazz-rock fusion, Miles Davis' Bitches Brew ranked as one of the one hundred greatest albums of all time in a Rolling Stone magazine poll published in 1987. Miles Electric: A Different Kind of Blue captures Davis performing the album at the 1970 Isle of Weight Music Festival. Along with the music, interviews with performers as varied as Carlos Santana and Joni Mitchell are included.
One of the fine extra treats in this amazing dvd is the equally-thrilling 1964 clip from the Steve Allen show of Davis and his quintet playing "So What.
&#x2026;this DVD has an amazing sounding mix of a great Miles performance. If you dig the Bitches Brew era, then this is a must-have. The interviews are all worth the time and quite insightful too
This film shows Miles in concert from start to finish for 38 minutes and it's like a slice of heaven. You get to see Miles' intensity of concentration when playing and you get to hear the group's improvisations evolve naturally instead of being chopped up in a Teo Macero/Columbia records packaging nightmare. This was a great band and Miles' chops were in top form. There's no diminishing the level of musicianship in this concert--it's 100% prime.
Additional Information:
Extra Info: performance at the Isle of Wight (in front of 600,000 rock fans) is awesome. The fidelity is good and the camera work is too. The average viewer/listener might be awed when watching Jack DeJohnette play his fractured funk or Keith Jarrett grimace while runs of quality music flow forth from his fingertips. Me I already knew this band was this good (these are the guys, minus one keyboard player and plus a different bass player, who went on to cut the massive "Live-Evil" within months). And I really, really enjoy watching this music that I love to listen to so much. 
The interviews which fill out the DVD to movie length are good, interesting, and at times revealing. Bonus footage is included of interview segments that didn't make the film's cut, strung together in a highly watchable manner.
This music makes no bow to commercialism. People who aren't interested in musical experimentation and boundary-smashing might find it hard to take. But make no mistake this is as good as music or art can get. This is Miles at his best and music at its best.
Miles' 1970 Isle Of Wight performance before 600,000 fans had attained legendary status over the decades, but until now only a few audio soundbites had been issued (and remarkably the entire set was never bootlegged). MILES ELECTRIC includes but is not limited to the entire 38-minute IOW performance. In 1970 Davis was perhaps in his all-time peak physical condition, and musically confident of his ability to bridge his jazz-based roots with the more adventurous pop culture sounds of that era. His trumpet work here seems limitless technically and full of fresh improvisatory ideas. And contrary his (exaggerated?) reputation, Davis is seen acknowledging the crowd with a wave of his horn when leaving the stage as the performance ends.
The rest of the group is similiarly adventurous, including Chick Corea and Keith Jarrett on keyboards, Gary Bartz on sax, Dave Holland on bass, Jack DeJohnette on drums, and Airto Moreira on various percussion. What more can you ask for than a collection of outstanding musicians -- all first-tier names in the music's history -- thinking outside the box in a variety of ways? By the way, the video looks crisp and the sound (with two surround options in addition to stereo) is clear and well-balanced, with just some slight distortion on Miles' trumpet at times (but not to a bothersome extent). Considering the recording conditions, the audio and video turned out very well.
Notice that the DVD has a running time of 123 minutes, while the concert itself is 38m. What the producers decided for this release was to surround the IOW gig with a documentary that puts Davis' "electric era" into proper context, with interviews of the IOW bandmembers (all of whom are currently still alive and musically active except of course for Miles, who is nonetheless heard via interview clips from the 1980s). Also interviewed are other Davis associates and a few critics,
Special thanks to dayofthegreen @ Tik for this amazing share.</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>Source: DVD9
Menus: editado
Extras: Untouched
Video Type: NTSC VIDEO_TS
Aspect Ratio: 1.33:1
Audio Format: DTS 5.1
Languages: English,
Subtitles: English, French, Spanish (Sólo los extras)</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>1.26</Duracion>
        <Poster>blue.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="2" contador="2">
        <Nombre>Roger Waters - The Wall (Live in Berlin) - 1990</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 1</Id>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>Songs: In the Flesh, The Thin Ice, Another Brick in the Wall part 1, The Happiest Days of Our Lives, Another Brick in the Wall part 2, Mother, Goodbye Blue Sky, Empty Spaces, Young Lust, Oh My God--What a Fabulous Room, One of My Turns, Don't Leave Me Now, Another Brick in the Wall part 3, Goodbye Cruel World, Hey You, Is There Anybody Out There?, Nobody Home, Vera, Bring the Boys Back Home, Comfortably Numb, In the Flesh, Run Like Hell, Waiting for the Worms &amp; Stop, The Trial, The Tide Is Turning
The Wall (Live in Berlin) seemed uninspired and gimmicky in 1990 but looks and sounds terrifically compelling on DVD, thanks to its vivid image quality and greatly improved audio mixes. The freshly mineswept Potsdamer platz--a once-thriving plaza destroyed by Allied bombing in 1943--proved the perfect place to mark the opening of the Berlin Wall with an all-star production of Pink Floyd's magnum opus: a Wall for a wall. An unlikely assemblage of musicians augments Roger Waters's impressive house band (led by guitarist Rick DiFonzo and organ wizard Nick Glennie-Smith), with everyone from the Scorpions to Joni Mitchell to the Military Orchestra of the Soviet Army getting in on the rock-opera action. Cyndi Lauper, Bryan Adams, James Galway, Thomas Dolby, and Albert Finney all turn in tasty cameos, while Sinead O'Connor looks unaccountably aloof in "Mother." The documentary is thorough and juicy, and producer Tony Hollingsworth offers an above-par essay in the booklet. --Michael Mikesell</Critica>
        <Poster>image013.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="3" contador="3">
        <Nombre>Led Zeppelin - The Song Remains the Same</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 2 - HD</Id>
        <Annus>1976</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>Genre: Rock
Duration: 2:17:42
Year: 1976/2007
Directed by: Peter Clifon, Joe Massot
Starring: John Bonham, John Paul Jones, Jimmy Page, Robert Plant
Description: The film has many scenes that include recording concerts at Madison Square Garden, and behind the scenes footage in the Baltimore Civic Centre carried out in the same round, which are interspersed with staged scenes. In the cinematic scenes are displayed episodes of mob attacks and episodes in the style of fantasy.
For Led Zeppelin fanatics, this 1976 feature The Song Remains the Same is a treasure of searing live performances, particularly welcome in light of the sad scarcity of such visual material from the band's great decade. Despite the group's road weariness after a long tour, their final, three-night stand at Madison Square Garden in 1973 was full of the old power. Performances of "No Quarter," "Whole Lotta Love," "Black Dog," "Dazed and Confused," and "Stairway to Heaven" underscore Zep's charisma. Trouble is, you don't get an unbroken performance here. Viewers have to wade through a mishmash of documentary insight into the lives of Robert Plant, Jimmy Page, John Bonham, and John Paul Jones, as well as fantasy sequences supposedly inspired by the thoughts and fantasies of the band's individual members. It's mostly garish and silly, but there are some nice elements, especially insights into the late Bonham's life.
Tracklist
01. Mob Rubout
02. Mob Town Credits
03. Country Life (Autumn Lake)
04. Bron-Yr-Aur
05. Rock and Roll
06. Black Dog
07. Since I've Been Loving You
08. No Quarter
09. Who's Responsible?
10. The Song Remains the Same
11. The Rain Song
12. Fire And Sword
13. Capturing The Castle
14. Not Quite Backstage Pass
15. Dazed And Confused
16. Strung Out
17. Magic In The Night
18. Gate Crasher
19. No Comment
20. Stairway To Heaven
21. Moby Dick
22. Country Squire Bonham
23. Heartbreaker
24. Grand Theft
25. Whole Lotta Love
26. End Credits (w / Stairway to Heaven)
Bonuses
01. Tampa News Report (News Footage Of The Band's Arrival And Concert In Tampa, Florida)
02. Over The Hills And Far Away (Never-before-released Song)
03. Boating Down The Thames (BBC Vintage Interview With Robert Plant And Peter Grant)
04. Celebration Day (Cutting Copy) (Never-before-released Song)
05. The Robbery (Vintage Footage Of The Infamous Drake Hotel Robbery - Interview With Peter Grant)
06. Misty Mountain Hop (Song)
07. The Ocean (Song)
08. Original Film Trailer</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>Quality: BDRip
Container: MKV
Video codec: H.264
Audio Codec: DTS
Video: x264, 1920x1080p, 23.976fps, ~ 9498kbps
Bonus Video: x264, 1920-1392x1088-1080 / 23.976, ~ 8878-3727kbps
Audio: English DTS 5.1 / 48kHz / 1510kbps
Bonus Audio: English AC3 5.1/2.0 / 48kHz / 448/192kbps
Subtitles: English, SRT subtitle format
Head: present</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>2.17 + bonus</Duracion>
        <Poster>image014.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="4" contador="4">
        <Nombre>Queen - The Making of A Night at the Opera</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 7</Id>
        <Annus>2006</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>If ever there was an album worthy of inclusion in Eagle Vision&#x2019;s Classic Albums series it is Queen&#x2019;s breakout release A Night At The Opera. Released in 1975, this was not only the band&#x2019;s first platinum album, but also the one that catapulted them into the spotlight as one of the biggest rock acts in the world.			
		Now for the first time, fans are offered an in-depth look at one of rock music&#x2019;s seminal records with the Classic Albums DVD Queen &#x2014; The Making Of A Night At The Opera.			
		&#x2022; BRAND NEW INTERVIEWS with guitarist Brian May and drummer Roger Taylor.			
		&#x2022; COMMENTARY by original producer Roy Thomas Baker.			
		&#x2022; ARCHIVAL PERFORMANCE and INTERVIEW FOOTAGE with late lead singer Freddie Mercury.			
		&#x2022; INTERVIEWS and GUEST COMMENTARY by guitarists Joe Perry (Aerosmith), Nuno Bettencourt (Extreme), Ian Hunter (Mott The Hoople) and many more.			
		&#x2022; NEW ACOUSTIC PERFORMANCES of &#x2019;39 and Love Of My Life by Brian May.			
		&#x2022; DRUM and ACOUSTIC DEMONSTRATIONS of I &#x2019;m In Love With My Car from Roger Taylor.			
		&#x2022; ANALYSIS OF THE RECORDING PROCESS of all12 tracks on the album.</Critica>
        <Poster>image016.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="5" contador="5">
        <Nombre>The Dark Side of the Moon</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 8</Id>
        <Annus>2003</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>The most phenomenal recording in rock &amp; roll history is thoroughly examined in Pink Floyd: The Dark Side of the Moon. The Floyd's 1973 masterpiece remained on bestseller charts for nearly 14 years, and its enduring importance is honored here by all four members of Pink Floyd and key personnel (engineer Alan Parsons, mixing supervisor Chris Thomas, sleeve designer Storm Thorgerson, and others) who played essential roles in the landmark album's creation. Produced for the Classic Albums series that originally aired on VH-1, this thorough and thought-provoking study highlights a track-by-track dissection of the LP's master tapes (including the spoken-word passages that bookend the album), superbly interlaced with archival footage, early demo tapes, concert animations, and latter-day acoustic performances by David Gilmour, Roger Waters, and Richard Wright to demonstrate each track's contribution to the final mix--a sonic exploration that extends to the illuminating bonus features. Informative interviews abound (including Rolling Stone senior editor David Fricke), and much-deserved credit is given to saxophonist Dick Parry, solo vocalist Clare Torry, and former Capitol Records chairman Bhaskar Menon, who fostered the album's U.S. commercial success. For Floyd fans, musicians, and studio technicians alike, this is a must-have addition to any DVD library. --Jeff Shannon
Product Description
Pink Floyd's "Dark Side of the Moon" Classic Album is the creative story behind the masterpiece: "Dark Side Of The Moon". "Dark Side Of The Moon" transformed Pink Floyd from art house favorites to global, stadium superstars. Prior to 1973, Pink Floyd maintained a relentless gigging schedule and by the time they came to record "Dark Side Of The Moon" had already created many of the basic tracks. "Dark Side Of The Moon" would be the first Pink Floyd (post Syd Barrett) album where Roger Waters would supply all the lyrics around a concept: The Circle of Life. With the timeless qualities of its production and musicality, allied to the hypnotic evocation of its central themes - alienation, paranoia, madness, war and death, "Dark Side Of The Moon" would become the album that would dominate the 70's and 80's (with a record number of 741 consecutive weeks in the Billboard 200). This program takes an in depth look at the making of the 1973 album. All four members of the band Roger Waters, David Gilmour, Nick Mason and Richard Wright are featured in exclusive interviews. Roger, David and Richard play songs and demonstrate themes from the album. Alan Parsons (the original engineer) takes you through the multi track tapes giving a unique insight into the musical fabric of the record and the program is illustrated throughout with archive footage. "Dark Side Of The Moon" with its combination of great songs, inventive effects and one of the best known sleeves ever, tapped into the world's collective subconscious and became a landmark in Rock history and a truly Classic Album. Pink Floyd's "Dark Side of the Moon" Classic Album is the creative story behind the masterpiece: "Dark Side Of ThThanks for all your help.e Moon". "Dark Side Of The Moon" transformed Pink Floyd from art house</Critica>
        <Poster>image017.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="6" contador="6">
        <Nombre>U2 - Vertigo 2005 - Live From Chicago</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 10</Id>
        <Annus>2005</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>When he isn't rubbing shoulders with the likes of Kofi Annan and George W. Bush, the activist Bono has a side project he likes to call "U2." U2: Vertigo - Live From Chicago captures the band on two nights during their tour to support How to Dismantle an Atomic Bomb. Once known for taking the most technologically extravagant shows on the road, the boys from Dublin have settled into a comfortable role of rock elder statesmen, placing emphasis on the anthems and weepers of their considerable body of work rather than gigantic lemons that descend from the rafters. Always a band that reflects the zeitgeist, this concert film finds them at their earnest best, with comparatively stripped-down stage production and superbly recorded sound. To call U2's more rocking songs "anthems" borders on understatement, and it is their anthems that ring most exuberantly in Chicago's United Center. Bono understandably looks heavier and wearier than in days past, perhaps due to the weight of the world he has hoisted onto his shoulders. While the icon roams the circular stage around the Metallica-style "snakepit," The Edge, drummer Larry Mullen Jr., and bassist Adam Clayton pin the songs to the floorboards and take them to the heavens. How can these guys not play fantastically together? Standouts include hits both classic and newly minted, among them "Beautiful Day," "New Year's Day," "Pride (In the Name of Love)," and "Sunday Bloody Sunday." Late in the concert Bono makes his appeal to the leaders of the world to end extreme poverty, invoking the imagination of a country that put a man on the moon. Ingeniously, he asks the crowd to take out their cell phones and text-message an account that operates as a petition to end world hunger. With the stadium aglow in LED screens, the band smoothly glides into "One." Elsewhere, Bono invokes religion, donning a headband decorated with Islamic, Jewish, and Christian symbols, assuming the appearance of a grizzled No Nukes protester circa 1975. (Perhaps this is a new persona akin to The Fly?) Kidding aside, these may be days in which we need the uplift and passion of U2 more than the 1990s, when they dressed up as the Village People and occasionally performed at K-Mart. Not suitable for those who don't wish to save the world. --Ryan Boudinot
Product Description
U2 Vertigo//2005 is without doubt the hottest tour of the year!! Ticket demand has been phenomenal and by the end of 2005 U2 will have played to 3.25 million people! "Vertigo//2005, U2 Live From Chicago" the DVD captures this unique experience.
		The DVD features 23 electric performances, with songs drawn from across the bands entire career - from first album fan favorites such as "Electric Co," through U2 classics such as "Pride...," "New Years Day" and "Where the Streets Have No Name" and right up to date with "Vertigo" the smash hit that launched this years #1 studio album "How To Dismantle An Atomic Bomb."
		Directed by Hamish Hamilton
		DVD TRACK LISTING
		1. City of Blinding Lights
		2. Vertigo
		3. Elevation
		4. Cry/Electric Co.
		5. An Cat Dubh/Into The Heart
		6. Beautiful Day
		7. New Year&#x2019;s Day
		8. Miracle Drug
		9. Sometimes You Can&#x2019;t Make It On Your Own
		10. Love and Peace or Else
		11. Sunday Bloody Sunday
		12. Bullet The Blue Sky
		13. Running To Standstill
		14. Pride In The Name Of Love
		15. Where The Streets Have No Name
		16. One
		17. Zoo Station
		18. The Fly
		19. Mysterious Ways
		20. All Because Of You
		21. Original Of The Species
		22. Yahweh
		23. 40</Critica>
        <Poster>image019.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="7" contador="7">
        <Nombre>Adiós Sui Generis</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 20</Id>
        <Annus>1976</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Poster>image026.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="8" contador="8">
        <Nombre>Adriana Calcanhotto - Partimpim-O Show</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 28</Id>
        <Annus>2005</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Poster>image038.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="9" contador="46">
        <Nombre>Woodstock</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 31 - HD</Id>
        <Annus>1970</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>The three-day Woodstock music festival in 1969 was the pivotal event of the 1960s peace movement, and this landmark concert film is the definitive record of that milestone of rock &amp; roll history. It's more than a chronicle of the hippie movement, however; this is a film of genuine historical and social importance, capturing the spirit of America in transition, when the Vietnam War was at its peak and antiwar protest was fully expressed through the liberating music of the time. With a brilliant crew at his disposal (including a young editor named Martin Scorsese), director Michael Wadleigh worked with over 300 hours of footage to create his original 225-minute director's cut, which was cut by 40 minutes for the film's release in 1970. Eight previously edited segments were restored in 1994, and the original director's cut of Woodstock is now the version most commonly available on videotape and DVD.
		The film deservedly won the Academy Award for Best Documentary, and it's still a stunning achievement. Abundant footage taken among the massive crowd ("half a million strong") expresses the human heart of the event, from skinny-dipping hippies to accidental overdoses, to unpredictable weather, midconcert childbirth, and the thoughtful (or just plain rambling) reflections of the festive participants. Then, of course, there is the music--a nonstop parade of rock &amp; roll from the greatest performers of the period, including Crosby, Stills, and Nash, Canned Heat, The Who, Richie Havens, Joan Baez, Ten Years After, Sly &amp; The Family Stone, Santana, and many more. Watching this ambitious film, as the saying goes, is the next best thing to being there--it's a time-travel journey to that once-in-a-lifetime event. --Jeff Shannon</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>Versión HD:
Woodstock. 3 Days of Peace and Music.
Duration: 3h 44m
Woodstock. Untold Stories. The Direcor's Cut Bonus
55 Clips, MKV. 16,9 GB</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>3.44</Duracion>
        <Poster>ZIRniSRb.jpeg</Poster>
        <Poster>image045.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="10" contador="10">
        <Nombre>The Beatles: Anthology</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 32  - DVD 33  - DVD 34  - DVD 35  - DVD 36</Id>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>image049.jpg
image050.jpg
image051.jpg
image052.jpg
image053.jpg
image054.jpg
image055.jpg
image056.gif
image057.jpg
image058.jpg
image059.gif
image060.jpg
image061.jpg
image062.gif
DESCRIPTION:
If you could roll the respective significance of "Citizen Kane", "Gone With the Wind" and "Lawrence of Arabia" into one film, you might have somewhat of an idea what the Beatles mean to contemporary music. Indeed, while Elvis Presley, Chuck Berry and Buddy Holly laid the groundwork, the Beatles forever defined the musical and artistic boundaries by which all future pop players would be judged. Indeed, the DVD format has provided modern day audiences with a chance to see why the Fab Four's legacy is something much more significant than a mere history lesson. "The Beatles Anthology" (released April 1, 2003 on DVD) picks up where the 2002-issued collector's edition release of "A Hard Day's Night" left off, providing more insight into the minds and music of the band that put Liverpool on the map. In addition to the in-depth chronology taking viewers on a magical mystery trip through the 1960s, new and never-before-seen material features interviews with Paul McCartney, Ringo Starr and the late George Harrison at Abbey Road Studios in May 1995 as they listen to classic Beatles tracks with producer George Martin. The jewel of the release is additional footage of the three one-time mop tops jamming together in George Harrison's garden.
DVD extras? You get them here. Indeed, the DVD release features a bonus disc featuring approximately 80 minutes of material more than the deluxe, eight-volume VHS release that expanded on the ABC special broadcast on Nov. 19, 22 and 23, 1995. Needless to say, all fans of rock music and 20th century pop culture should own this collection.
Disc One:
Part I: July '40 to March '63
Part II: March '63 to February '64
Disc Two:
Part III: February '64 to July '64
Part IV: August '64 to August '65
Disc Three:
Part V: August '65 to July '66
Part VI: July '66 to June '67
Disc Four:
Part VII: June '67 to July '68
Part VIII: July '68 to The End
Disc Five: Special Features
* Recollections - June 1994
* Compiling the Anthology Albums
* Back At Abbey Road - May 1995
* Recording "Free as a Bird" and "Real Love"
* Production Team
* Making the "Free As A Bird" Video
* "Real Love" Video</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>DVD1: [X] Re-encoded                        
HIGH/LOW/TYPICAL: 2,436/1,771/2,022 Kbs
Overall Bitrate: 2,528/2,022Kbs  
Compression Ratio: 62.2%
DVD2: [X] Re-encoded    
HIGH/LOW/TYPICAL: 2,821/1,855/2,202 Kbs
Overall Bitrate: 2,752/2,202Kbs
Compression Ratio: 63.2%
DVD3: [X] Re-encoded      
HIGH/LOW/TYPICAL: 2,445/1,893/2,205 Kbs
Overall Bitrate: 2,756/2,205Kbs
Compression Ratio: 62.6%
DVD4: [X] Re-encoded      
HIGH/LOW/TYPICAL: 2,301/1,662/1,930 Kbs
Overall Bitrate: 2,412/1,930Kbs
Compression Ratio: 59.2%
DVD5: [X] Untouched    
Overall Bitrate: 6700/5510kbs
AUDIO:
[X] English DTS 5.1
[X] English AC3 5.1
SUBTITLES:
[X] English
[X] French
[X] German  
[X] Spanish
[X] Italian
[X] Portugees [X2]
MENU:
[X] Partial Strip
EXTRAS:
[X] All included
Rippers Notes:
* Ripped to HD using DVDShrink 3.2 uncompressed, removing the English LPCM audio.
* FBI Screen &amp; LPCM Audio buttons removed with DVD ReMake Pro 3.1.4.
* DVD5 reduction done with DVD ReBuilder Pro 1.09.2 using the CinemaCraft Encoder SP [2.70.02.09].</DatosTecnicos>
        <Poster>image046.jpg</Poster>
        <Poster>image047.jpg</Poster>
        <Poster>image048.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="11" contador="11">
        <Nombre>Tribalistas</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 39</Id>
        <Annus>2003</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Poster>image066.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="12" contador="12">
        <Nombre>The Rolling Stones - The Biggest Bang</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 41 - HD</Id>
        <Annus>2007</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>"    DVD 1
   Show de Austin, Texas - EEUU, 22/10/06
    DVD 2
   Paya de Copacabana - Brasil, 19/02/06
    DVD 3
   Shows de Japón, Argentina y Shanghai y material adicional
    DVD 4
   Documental A Bigger Bang Tour y material adiccional
    DVD 1 - Austín - EEUU* + Bonus
   Introducción
1. You Got Me Rocking
2. Let's Spend The Night Together
3. She's So Cold
4. Oh No Not You Again
5. Sway
6. Bob Wills Is Still The King
7. Streets of Love
8. Ain't Too Proud To Beg
9. Bitch
10. Tumbling Dice
11. Learning The Game
12. Little T &amp; A
13. Under My Thumb
14. Get Off My Cloud
15. Start Me Up
16. Honky Tonk Women
17. Sympathy For The Devil
18. Jumpin' Jack Flash
19. (I Can't Get No) Satisfaction
20. Brown Sugar
Bonus:
-Mini Documental del Show de Austin
-""Can't Be Satisfied"" Milan, Italia (Blues Jam)
   * Austin, Texas EEUU 20/10/06 - Show completo 100 minutos
    DVD 2 Copacabana - Brasil* + Bonus
   Introducción
1. Jumpin' Jack Flash
2. You Got Me Rocking
3. Wild Horses
4. Rain Fall Down
5. Midnight Rambler
6. Night Time Is The Right Time
7. Happy
8. Miss You
9. Rough Justice
10. Get Off My Cloud
11. Honky Tonk Women
12. Sympathy For The Devil
13. Start Me Up
14. Brown Sugar
15. You Can't Always Get What You Want
16. (I Can&#x2019;t Get No) Satisfaction
Bonus
Especial del National Geographic (25 minutos)
   * Brasil 19/02/06 - Show completo 95 minutos
    DVD 3 Japon - China - Argentina + Bonus
   Show Saitama
1. Let's Spend The Night Together
2. Rain Fall Down
3. Rough Justice
4. Start Me Up
5. Brown Sugar
   Show Shanghai
1. Bitch
2. Wild Horses
3. Midnight Rambler
4. Gimme Shelter
5. This Place Is Empty
6. It's Only Rock And Roll
   Show Argentina
1. Jumpin' Jack Flash
2. Shattered
3. Worried About You
4. Happy
5. Miss You
6. Paint It Black
7. (I Can't Get No) Satisfaction
   Bonus: Duetos - Especiales
Junto a Bonnie Raitt - ""Shine A Light""
Junto a Eddie Vedder - ""Wild Horses""
Junto a Dave Mathews - ""Let It Bleed""
Junto a Buddy Guy - ""Night Time, Is The Right Time""
    DVD 4 : Documental A Bigger Bang Tour + Bonus
   ""Salt Of The Earth""
1. Tour  &amp; Club Show
2. Boston - Noche de apertura y Fenway Park
3. Sympathy
4. Super Bowl
5. Back of my Hand
6. Rio
7. Buenos Aires
8. Shattered
9. China
10. Extención
11. Milan
12. Midnight Rambler
13. Vancouver - Final del Tour
   Bonus - Dueto
Archivos
1. ""Salt Of The Earth"" (Axl Rose and Izzy Stradlin)
2. ""Little Red Rooster"" (Eric Clapton)
3. ""No Expectations"" (Lenny Kravitz)
4. ""Let It Bleed"" (Hubert Sumlin)
Bonus - Temas
Get Up, Stand Up - Toronto Club Show 08/10/05 - Toronto
Mr. Pitiful - Toronto Club Show 08/10/05 - Toronto
Virtual Ticket Hot Link / Virtual Store Hot Link
Bonus - 4 Temas Inéditos
1. If It Ain't Got That Swing (Charlie Watts)
2. &#x201c;Hurricane&#x201d; (Keith Richards)
3. Outlets Of Emotion (Ron Wood)
4. Busking (Mick Jagger)
CRITICA:
Sus Majestades lanzan los DVDs oficiales del A Bigger Bang Tour 2005/06, donde continúan con la modalidad de presentación similar a la entrega correspondiente al  Four Flicks, Un Box set integrado por 4 DVDs que recorren shows realizados en distintos continente, 1 show histórico, documental integro de los 2 años de tour, 1 dvd con un raconto de 3 shows (Japón, China, Argentina) y 1 documental mas 4 temas inéditos."	"</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>SISTEMA: NTSC
AUDIO: Dolby Digital 2.0 ; Dolby Digital 5.1 ; DTS ; FORMATO: 4xDVD9 =&gt; 4xDVD9
COMPRESION: Sin Compresión. "</DatosTecnicos>
        <Poster>image068.jpg</Poster>
        <Poster>image069.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="13" contador="13">
        <Nombre>Live Earth: The Concerts foraClimate in Crisis</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 44</Id>
        <Annus>2007</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>1. Live Earth London Opening - SOS Allstars
		2. Invisible Touch - Genesis
		3. Shut Your Eyes - Snow Patrol
		4. Que Sera Sera - Rice, Damien &amp; David Gray
		5. Suddenly I See - Tunstall, K.T
		6. My Blue Heaven - Taking Back Sunday
		7. What A Wonderful World - Nutini, Paolo
		8. Where Is The Love - Black Eyed Peas
		9. Planet Earth - Duran Duran
		10. Miss Murder - AFI
		11. Gravity - Mayer, John
		12. Mercy Mercy Me (The Ecology) - Bailey Rae, Corinne &amp; John Legend
		13. Bedshaped - Keane
		14. Sad But True - Metallica
		15. I Need To Wake Up - Etheridge, Melissa
		16. Too Much - Matthews, Dave Band
		17. Sober - Clarkson, Kelly
		18. Tumba - Kidjo, Angelique
		19. Right To Be Wrong - Stone, Joss
		20. Wisemen - Blunt, James
On July 7, 2007, more than 100 musical acts performed at a series of worldwide concerts collectively called Live Earth, kicking off a multi-year		21. Intergalactic - Beastie Boys
campaign to combat climate change	
and advocate environmentally		DVD 2: 1,28
sustainable living. The CD/2DVD Live		
Earth package brings together the		22. Gimme Shelter - Urban, Keith &amp; Alicia Keys
most popular artists and best performances at Wembley Stadium in London, Giants Stadium in New Jersey and Makuhari Messe in Japan from this truly global musical summit.		23. Bailamos - Iglesias, Enrique
The organizers say Live Earth was		24. Steer - Higgins, Missy
the largest global entertainment event ever held. The 2-hour broadcast reached audiences in more than 130 countries through radio, television, and the Internet.		25. Woman - Wolfmother
Live Earth attracted a record online live audience of more than 8 million people. Within the following two		26. Black Hole Sun - Cornell, Chris
weeks alone, more than 55 million video streams hadbeen watched.		27. Wanted Dead Or Alive - Bon Jovi
SPECIAL NOT E : Live Earth's net proceeds from the sale of this DVD/CD package benefit the Alliance for Climate Protection.		28. Are You Gonna Go My Way - Kravitz, Lenny
		29. United States - Smashing Pumpkins
		30. Another Brick In The Wall Part II - Waters, Roger
		31. Driven To Tears - Police
		32. Umbrella - Rihanna
		33. Bleed It Out - Linkin Park
		34. Times Like These - Foo Fighters
		35. La Isla Bonita - Madonna &amp; Gogol Bordello
		Extras (DiSC 2): What U Can Do, Journey To The Unconvenient Truth, Short Films.</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>NTSC
Subtitles: NO
AUDIO: Dolby Digital 5.1, Inglés 2.0
D.A.R: 16:9 &amp; 4:3		
DURATION:262 min.</DatosTecnicos>
        <Poster>image076.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="14" contador="14">
        <Nombre>Astor Piazzolla in Portrait</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 51</Id>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <DatosTecnicos>Video: 2733 Kbps (334 KB/s)
Audio: 48 KHz stereo, 192 Kbps AC-3
Norma de Video: NTSC	
Formato de Pantalla: Widescreen</DatosTecnicos>
        <Poster>image082.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="15" contador="15">
        <Nombre>Michael Jackson - Number Ones</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 61</Id>
        <Annus>2003</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>Tracklisting
1. Dont Stop Til You Get Enough
2. Rock With You
3. Billie Jean
4. Beat It
5. Thriller
6. Bad
7. The Way You Make Me Feel
8. Man in the Mirror
9. Smooth Criminal
10. Dirty Diana
11. Black or White
12. You Are Not Alone
13. Earth Song
14. Blood on the Dancefloor
15. You Rock My World</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>Format: PAL
Language English
Aspect Ratio: 1.33:1
Classification: Exempt
Studio: Sony Bmg
DVD Release Date: 17 Nov 2003</DatosTecnicos>
        <Poster>x6la4i.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="16" contador="16">
        <Nombre>John Lennon - Classic Albums: John Lennon - Plastic Ono Band</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 62</Id>
        <Annus>2008</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>Description: "John Lennon / Plastic Ono Band" was John Lennon's first solo studio album after the break up of The Beatles. Both John &amp; Yoko had been undergoing primal scream therapy in the lead up to the recording of the album and both this and Yoko Ono's companion album ("Yoko Ono / Plastic Ono Band" were deeply influenced by their therapy. This latest addition to Eagle's acclaimed Classic Albums series explores the creation of this groundbreaking album through new interviews, archive footage and detailed analysis of the original multi-track masters. Interviewees include Ringo Starr, Yoko Ono and bass player Klaus Voorman.
TRACK LISTING: Features excerpts from: Mother - Hold On - Isolation - I Found Out - Love - God - Working Class Hero - and more...</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>Source: DVD5
Menus: Untouched
Extras: Untouched
Video Type: PAL
Aspect Ratio: 16:9
Audio Information:
Audio Format: Dolby Stereo
Languages: English
Subtitles: English Espanol Francais Italiano Nederlands Portugues</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>0.53 + 0.35</Duracion>
        <Poster>51Iz6cOtRAL._SS500_.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="17" contador="17">
        <Nombre>Divididos - Amapola del 66</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 63</Id>
        <Annus>2010</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>Dvd del nuevo disco de divididos, amapola del 66.
la verdad que si pueden comprarlo (casi $70), vale la pena, la edición está muy buenas y trae el cd que ya está para bajar en otro torrent, y este dvd.
Los que no puedan comprarlo, o por lo menos no aún y estén ansiosos, ¡disfrútenlo!
(pero si pueden, cómprenlo.)</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>Video: 100% / 5881 kbps
Audio: AC3 48000Hz  192 kb/s tot , stereo (2/0)
Norma de Video: NTSC
Formato de Pantalla: Widescreen

[:exc:] DATOS:
Idioma Audio: Español
Subtitulos: No
Menú: Sí
Extras: No
Link con Info: Link
Velocidad de Subida: El seeder afirma tener 128 Kb</DatosTecnicos>
        <Poster>amapoladel66tapa.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="18" contador="0">
        <Nombre>Live 8</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 3 - DVD 4 - DVD 5 - DVD 6</Id>
        <Estado>Archivado</Estado>
        <Critica>Filming Locations: Chateau de Versailles, Versailles, Yvelines, France| Circus Maximus, Rome, Lazio, Italy| Hyde Park, London, England, UK| Makuhari Messe, Makuhari, Tokyo, Japan| Mary Fitzgerald Square, Newtown, Johannesburg, Gauteng, South Africa| Park Place, Barrie, Ontario, Canada| Philadelphia Museum of Art - 26th Street and Ben Franklin Parkway, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, USA| Red Square, Moscow, Russia| SiegessÃ¤ule, Tiergarten, Berlin, Germany| The Eden Project, St Austell, Cornwall, England, UK			
Two decades years after Live Aid addressed the issue, lethally oppressive poverty in Africa remains a blight on the planet. Thus, in the Summer of 2005 activist Bob Geldof staged an even more ambitious series of continent-spanning concerts dedicated to raising funds and public consciousness about international debt relief. This expansive four-disc chronicles those shows in one of the most ambitious concert documents ever attempted, capturing all of the highlights (and a few complete artist sets) of concerts in London, Philadelphia, Toronto, Paris, Berlin and Moscow. Underscoring the events' sense of unity, the performances here span both generations and genres, offering veteran rock fans often muscular sets by Elton John (including a woozy take on T. Rex's "Children of the Revolution" with Baby Shambles' Pete Doherty), The Who, Sting (who sharply reprises a trio of Police favorites) and the ubiquitous Paul McCartney. But the highlight of the Jurassic set's contributions are a reunion of Roger Waters and his long-estranged Pink Floyd bandmates on a sonically flawless five-song whirl through highlights of Dark Side of the Moon, Wish You Were Here and The Wall; footage of their rehearsal for the show is contained on the set's equally eclectic fourth disc of bonus materials. But there are highlights here for nearly every taste, be they a fine sampling of contemporary UK and Australian rockers ( Coldplay, Jet, Razorlight and especially blistering performances by Stereophonics and Kaiser Chiefs), a little hip-hop nostalgia (a joyous Will Smith and Jazzy Jeff leading what seems half of his Philly hometown in a goofy singalong of the "Fresh Prince of Bel Air" theme); showy turns by pop-meister Robbie Williams and chateuses Mariah Carey, a rousing set by Black Eyed Peas (featuring Rita and Stephen Marley on a cover of "Get Up Stand Up"). Other one-off duets include Coldplay and Richard Ashcroft doing a fine version of the latter's "Bittersweet Symphony," Stevie Wonder with Rob Thomas ("Higher Ground") and Adam Levine ("Signed Sealed Delivered"), a tender take on "Angel" by Sarah McLachlan and Josh Groban and McCartney and George Michael taking an upbeat turn via "Drive My Car," before Macca closes out the London show by leading its various participants in an obligatory singalong of "Hey Jude." Royalties from sales of the set will go to the Band Aid Trust for the relief of hunger and poverty in Africa. --Jerry McCulley			
DVD 4					
DVD 5		DISC 1	DISC 2	DISC 3	DISC 4 EXTRAS
DVD 6		Paul McCartney &amp; U2 - Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band	Destiny's Child - Survivor	Mariah Carey - Make It Happen	EDINBURGH CONCERT
v		U2 - Beautiful Day	Destiny's Child - Girl	Mariah Carey - Hero	The Walk to Edinburgh - Highland Fling
		U2 - Vertigo	Razorlight - Somewhere Else	Vusi Mahlasela - When You Come Back ( Johannesburg)	The Proclaimers - I'm Gonna Be (500 Miles)
		U2 - One	Razorlight - Golden Touch	Roxy Music - Do The Strand ( Berlin)	Wet Wet Wet - Love Is All Around
		Coldplay - In My Place	Bryan Adams - All For Love	Maroon 5 - This Love	1 Giant Leap - My Culture
		Coldplay with Richard Ashcroft - Bittersweet Symphony	Kanye West - Diamonds From Sierra Leone	Maroon 5 - She Will Be Loved	George Clooney
		Coldplay - Fix You	CBC Ethiopian Famine Film	Neil Young - Four Strong Winds ( Toronto)	Annie Lennox - Sisters Are Doin' It For Themselves
		Elton John - The Bitch Is Back	Madonna - Like A Prayer	Pet Shop Boys - Go West ( Moscow)	Bono
		Elton John - Saturday Night's Alright For Fighting	Madonna - Ray Of Light	Robbie Williams - We Will Rock You	Nelson Mandela
		Elton John with Pete Doherty - Children Of The Revolution	Madonna - Music	Robbie Williams - Let Me Entertain You	Bob Geldof - The Great Song Of Indifference
		Dido &amp; Youssou N'Dour - 7 Seconds	Will Smith - Getting' Jiggy Wit It	Robbie Williams - Feel	The Thrills - Santa Cruz (You're Not That Far)
		Stereophonics - Bartender And The Thief	Will Smith - Switch	Robbie Williams - Angels	Herbert Gronemeyer &amp; Claudia Schiffer
		REM - Everybody Hurts	Will Smith - The Fresh Prince Of Bel Air	Keith Urban - Somebody Like You	Midge Ure &amp; Eddie Izzard - Vienna
		REM - Man On The Moon	Brian Wilson - Good Vibrations ( Berlin)	Placebo - Twenty Years ( Paris)	Texas - Say What You Want
		Ms Dynamite - Dy-Na-Mi-Tee	Snow Patrol - Run	Rob Thomas - Lonely No More	Katherine Jenkins - Nessun Dorma
		Keane - Somewhere Only We Know	Toby Keith - Stays In Mexico	Faithless - We Come 1 ( Berlin)	Travis - Why Does It Always Rain On Me?
		Black Eyed Peas - Where Is The Love	The Killers - All These Things That I've Done	Stevie Wonder - Master Blaster (Jammin')	James Brown - I Got You (I Feel Good)
		Black Eyed Peas - Let's Get It Started	Dave Matthews Band - American Baby	Stevie Wonder &amp; Rob Thomas - Higher Ground	James Brown &amp; Will Young - Papa's Got A Brand New Bag
		Black Eyed Peas with Stephen Marley - Get Up Stand Up	Daniel Powter - Bad Day	Stevie Wonder &amp; Adam Levine - Signed Sealed Delivered	Bob Geldof, Bono, Midge Ure
		Duran Duran - Wild Boys ( Rome)	Linkin Park - In The End	Stevie Wonder - So What The Fuss/Superstition	Murrayfield crowd - Flower Of Scotland
		Bob Geldof - I Don't Like Mondays	Linkin Park with Jay-Z - Numb	The Who - Who Are You?	McFly - All About You (Live 8 Tokyo)
		Muse - Time Is Running Out ( Paris)	Joss Stone - Super Duper Love	The Who - Won't Get Fooled Again	Good Charlotte - Lifestyles Of The Rich And Famous (Live 8 Tokyo)
		Travis - Sing	Joss Stone - Some Kind Of Wonderful	Pink Floyd - Speak To Me	Dreams Come True - Love Love Love (Live 8 Tokyo)
		Kaiser Chiefs - I Predict A Riot	Jars Of Clay - Show You Love	Pink Floyd - Breathe	Bjork - All Is Full Of Love (Live 8 Tokyo)
		Kaiser Chiefs - Everyday I Love You Less And Less	Scissor Sisters - Laura	Pink Floyd - Money	Tim McGraw - Live Like You Were Dying (Live 8 Roma)
		UB40 with Hunterz &amp; The Dohl Blasters - Reasons	Scissor Sisters - Take Your Mama	Pink Floyd - Wish You Were Here	Faith Hill - Breathe (Live 8 Roma)
		UB40 - Red Red Wine	Alicia Keys - For All We Know	Pink Floyd - Comfortably Numb	Shakira - Whenever, Wherever (Live 8 Paris)
		Green Day - American Idiot ( Berlin)	Velvet Revolver - Fall To Pieces	Paul McCartney - Get Back	Audioslave - Black Hole Sun (Live 8 Berlin)
		Snoop Dogg - Signs	Def Leppard - Pour Some Sugar On Me	Paul McCartney &amp; George Michael - Drive My Car	Audioslave - Like A Stone (Live 8 Berlin)
		Snoop Dogg - Who Am I (What's My Name)?	Jet - Are You Gonna Be My Girl?	Paul McCartney - Helter Skelter	Who Are You? Film - The Who
		Bon Jovi - Livin' On A Prayer	Sarah McLachlan &amp; Josh Groban - Angel	Paul McCartney - The Long And Winding Road	Why Does It Always Rain On Me? film - Travis
		Annie Lennox - Why	Sting - Message In A Bottle	Finale - Hey Jude	Ricky Gervais - Enjoy the day
		Annie Lennox - Sweet Dreams	Sting - Driven To Tears		Backstage at Hyde Park
			Sting - Every Breath You Take		Pink Floyd rehearsal and interview footage</Critica>
        <Poster>image015.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="19" contador="50">
        <Nombre>The Doors - Live at the Hollywood Bowl</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 11 - HD</Id>
        <Annus>1968</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>Filming Locations: Hollywood Bowl - 2301 N. Highland Avenue, Hollywood, Los Angeles, California, USA
Director : Ray Manzarek 
		Watching The Doors Live at the Hollywood Bowl is a sobering experience, for the viewer must confront the painful truth that popular music, to judge by its increasingly infantile and banal state, will never see their like again. Either that, or admit the Doors were an irrelevant footnote in the history of pop--an idle thought that a few minutes of this extraordinary concert will dispel. Fortunately for posterity, this July 5, 1968 performance was captured by four cameras and recorded in 16-track audio, resulting in generally excellent stereo sound that is far better than most archive footage of this band.
		On stage Jim Morrison has the aura of an intense performance artist, whose dark, smoky voice forms only a part of his complex persona. Guitarist Robby Krieger, keyboard player Ray Manzarek, and drummer John Densmore complement Morrison's free-associative outpourings with improvisational, jazz-inspired interjections. They make music like no other band before or since. Who else could segue effortlessly from Kurt Weill's "Alabama Song" to Willie Dixon's "Back Door Man"? And just when they're in danger of becoming too pretentious, Morrison bursts any lurking self-importance with a wry smile, a jokey aside, or even a belch. But the seriousness remains, at least implicitly, throughout as Morrison's edgy lyrics (from "When the Music's Over" to "The Unknown Soldier" and "The End") constantly hint at disturbing social undercurrents outside the concert arena. Is it fanciful to imagine that in the minds of his audience the ghosts of the Vietnam War and the Civil Rights movement are hovering just out of view? Such thoughts are what make the Doors so unique. Their music invites questions, positively dares the audience to ask them. That's why they remain so endlessly fascinating well over three decades later. And that's why this concert performance will find a home with any and every fan of the band. "The time to hesitate is through." --Mark Walker, Amazon.co.uk
Track Listing
01. Show Start / Intro
02. When The Music's Over
03. Alabama Song (Whisky Bar)
04. Back Door Man
05. Five To One
06. Back Door Man (Reprise)
07. The Wasp (Texas Radio And The Big Beat)
08. Hello, I Love You
09. Moonlight Drive
10. Horse Latitudes
11. A Little Game
12. The Hill Dwellers
13. Spanish Caravan
14. Hey, What Would You Guys Like To Hear?
15. Wake Up!
16. Light My Fire
17. Light My Fire (Segue)
18. The Unknown Soldier
19. The End (Segue)
20. The End</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>Versión HD:
The.Doors.Live.At.The.Bowl.1968.1080p.MBluRay.x264-FKKHD
fkkhd-tdlatb-1080.mkv
Container: Matroska
Runtime: 1h 11mn
Size: 5.46 GiB
DXVA: Compatible
Video
Codec: x264
Resolution: 1920x1080
Aspect ratio: 16:9
Frame rate: 23.976 fps
Bit rate: 9 483 Kbps
Audio
English 5.1ch DTS @ 1 510 Kbps</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>1.11</Duracion>
        <Poster>image020.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="20" contador="2">
        <Nombre>Live Aid</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 12 - DVD 13 - DVD 14 - DVD 15</Id>
        <Annus>1985</Annus>
        <Estado>Archivado</Estado>
        <Critica>01 STATUS QUO- Don't Waste My Time [04:34]	31 THE WHO- My Generation [01:40] The BBC blew a fuze during the two first numbers by The Who.	60 SANTANA- [05:14] Open Invitation
02 STYLE COUNCIL- You're the Best Thing [05:00]	32 THE WHO- Pinball Wizard [03:02] The band didn't stop playing but the broadcast was interrupted.	61 SANTANA + PAT METHENY- [07:32] By The Pool/Right Now
03 STYLE COUNCIL- Big Boss Groove [03:55]	33 ELTON JOHN- I'm Still Standing [03:20]	62 THE CARS- [03:02] You Might Think
04 BOOMTOWN RATS- Rat Trap [05:37]	34 ELTON JOHN- Can I Get a Witness [03:42]	63 THE CARS- [04:04] Drive
05 ULTRAVOX- Reap The Wild Wind [02:58]	35 ASHFORD &amp; SIMPSON- [04:56] Solid	64 NEIL YOUNG- [04:45] Sugar Mountain
		06 ULTRAVOX- One Small Day [03:49]	36 KOOL &amp; THE GANG (pre-recorded live video)- [02:01] Stand up and Sing	65 NEIL YOUNG- [04:22] Helpless
		07 SPANDAU BALLET- Virgin [04:40]	37 KOOL &amp; THE GANG (pre-recorded live video)- [03:11] Cherish	66 NEIL YOUNG- [04:49] Powderfinger
		08 NIK KERSHAW- Wide Boy [03:25]	 P3	67 POWER STATION- [04:20] Murderess
		09 NIK KERSHAW- Don Quixote [04:48]	38 MADONNA- [05:17] Love Makes The World Go Round	68 POWER STATION- [06:00] Get It On
		10 NIK KERSHAW- The Riddle [04:13]	39 TOM PETTY &amp; The HEARTBREAKERS- [04:46] The Waiting	69 THOMPSON TWINS- [07:59] Hold Me Now
		11 SADE- Why Can't We Live Together [05:35]	40 TOM PETTY &amp; The HEARTBREAKERS- [05:42] Rebels	70 PHIL COLLINS- [03:45] Against All Odds
		12 SADE- Is It a Crime [06:10]	41 THE HOOTERS- [04:37] And We Danced	71 LED ZEPPELIN- [04:43] Rock &amp; Roll
		13 STING- Driven To Tears [03:17]	42 THE HOOTERS- [05:44] All You Zombies	72 LED ZEPPELIN- [05:20] Whole Lotta Love
		14 STING- Message In A Bottle [04:32]	43 THE FOUR TOPS- [02:42] Shake Me, Wake Me (When It's Over)	73 LED ZEPPELIN- [09:19] Stairway To Heaven
		15 PHIL COLLINS- In The Air Tonight [04:45]	44 THE FOUR TOPS- [01:43] Bernadette	74 CROSBY - STILLS - NASH (&amp; YOUNG)- [03:33] Only Love Can Break your Heart
		16 STING + PHIL COLLINS- Long Long Way To Go [03:30]	45 THE FOUR TOPS- [01:20] It's The Same Old Song Motown Medley	75 CROSBY - STILLS - NASH (&amp; YOUNG)- [03:09] Daylight Again
		17 BRYAN FERRY- Sensation [04:31]	46 THE FOUR TOPS- [01:36] Reach Out I'll Be There Motown Medley	76 DURAN DURAN- [04:07] A view to a Kill
		18 BRYAN FERRY- Boys And Girls [04:31]	47 THE FOUR TOPS- [02:28] I Can't Help Myself (Sugar Pie, Honey Bunch) Motown Medley	77 PATTI LABELLE- [02:51] New Attitude
		19 BRYAN ADAMS- [04:12] Tears Are Not Enough	48 BILLY OCEAN- [04:08] Caribbean Queen	78 PATTI LABELLE- [02:20] Stir It Up
		20 BRYAN ADAMS- [05:34] Cuts Like A Knife	49 BILLY OCEAN- [03:38] Loverboy	79 PATTI LABELLE- [02:43] Over The Rainbow
		21 THE BEACH BOYS- [02:31] California Girls	50 BLACK SABBATH- [04:18] Children Of The Grave	80 PATTI LABELLE- [02:44] Why Can't I Get It Over
		22 THE BEACH BOYS- [03:07] Help Me, Rhonda	51 BLACK SABBATH- [07:44] Iron Man	81 HALL &amp; OATES- [04:27] Out Of Touch
		23 GEORGE THOROGOOD &amp; THE DESTROYERS + BO DIDDLEY- [05:34] Who Do You Love	52 RICK SPRINGFIELD- [03:37] Love Somebody	82 HALL &amp; OATES w/EDDIE KENDRICKS &amp; DAVID RUFFIN- [02:41] The Way You Do The Things You Do (voc : E. KENDRICKS)
		24 GEORGE THOROGOOD &amp; THE DESTROYERS- [07:02] The Sky Is Crying	53 RICK SPRINGFIELD- [04:04] State Of The Heart	83 MICK JAGGER- [03:25] Lonely At The Top
		25 SIMPLE MINDS- [03:00] Promised You a Miracle (The feed was lost during the song. The broadcast time is only 02:09)	54 RICK SPRINGFIELD- [02:32] Human Touch	84 BOB DYLAN + RON WOOD + KEITH RICHARDS- [04:34] Ballad Of Hollis Brown
		26 BERNARD WATSON- All I Really Want To Do (Bob Dylan Cover)	55 CROSBY, STILLS &amp; NASH- [04:57] Southern Cross	85 BOB DYLAN + RON WOOD + KEITH RICHARDS- [03:36] When The Ship Comes In
		27 BERNARD WATSON- Interview (Original B. Watson song)	56 CROSBY, STILLS &amp; NASH- [08:05] Suite: Judy Blue Eyes	
		28 JOAN BAEZ- [02:34] We Are The World	57 JUDAS PRIEST- [07:16] You've Got Another Thing Comin'	
		29 THE PRETENDERS- [03:35] Time The Avenger	58 SANTANA- [03:22] Brotherhood	
		30 THE PRETENDERS- [03:15] Message of Love	59 SANTANA- [02:11] Primera Invasion</Critica>
        <Poster>image021.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="21" contador="3">
        <Nombre>Eric Clapton - 24 Nights</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 13</Id>
        <Annus>1991</Annus>
        <Estado>Archivado</Estado>
        <Critica>Recorded live at the royal albert hall,London 1990 &amp; 1991		
		Imdb link: http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0191992/		
		imdb rate: 7.9/10		
		compressed with dvdshrink (automatic 71.5%)		
		picture format:PAL 4:3		
		Angles: 1
		Region code: 2/3/4/5/6
		dvd format: dvd 5
		Duration: 90 mins
		Audio: English/Linear PCM stereo
		Subs: Englisch lyric subtitles
		piece band 
		1. running on faith
		2. white room
		3. sunshine of your love
		Blues band (feat. buddy guy,robert cray)
		4. watch yourself
		5. have you ever loved a woman
		6. worried live blues
		piece band
		7. pretending 
		8. bad love
		9. old love
		10.wonderful tonight
		orchestra
		11. bell bottom blues
		12. hard times
		13. edge of darkness</Critica>
        <Poster>image022.gif</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="22" contador="4">
        <Nombre>Eric Clapton and Friends</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 16</Id>
        <Annus>1986</Annus>
        <Estado>Archivado</Estado>
        <Critica>A concert by rock singer/guitarist Eric Clapton, with colleagues Phil Collins, Nathan East and others.</Critica>
        <Poster>image023.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="24" contador="6">
        <Nombre>The History of Rock and Roll</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 19 - DVD 24</Id>
        <Estado>Archivado</Estado>
        <Critica>DVD 19 - Disco 1
DVD 24 - Disco 2</Critica>
        <Poster>image025.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="25" contador="7">
        <Nombre>John Lennon - Legend: The Very Best Of John Lennon</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 22</Id>
        <Estado>Archivado</Estado>
        <Critica>Tracks:
		Imagine
		Instant Karma (We All Shine On)
		Mother
		Jealous Guy
		Power to the People
		Cold Turkey
		Love
		Mind Games
		Whatever Gets You Through the Night
		#9 Dream
		Stand by Me
		(Just Like) Starting Over
		Woman
		Beautiful Boy (Darling Boy)
		Watching the Wheels
		Nobody Told Me
		Borrowed Time
		Working Class Hero
		Happy Xmas (War Is Over)
		Give Peace a Chance
		Extras:
		Working Class Hero
		Slippin' &amp; Slidin'
		Imagine
		Hair Peace
		Everybody Had a Hard Year
		Animations
		Gallery</Critica>
        <Poster>image030.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="26" contador="8">
        <Nombre>Bob Marley - Live At Rainbow</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 23</Id>
        <Annus>1977</Annus>
        <Estado>Archivado</Estado>
        <Poster>image032.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="27" contador="9">
        <Nombre>Pink Floyd - Pulse</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 25</Id>
        <Annus>2006</Annus>
        <Estado>Archivado</Estado>
        <Critica>At long last Pink Floyd: Pulse has arrived on DVD, and Floyd fans already know it's a major cause to celebrate. The original VHS release was a milestone bestseller, but it seemed to take forever for the DVD to arrive, with numerous delays while Floyd guitarist David Gilmour and long-time Floyd producer James Guthrie labored to restore, re-edit, and remix this legendary concert video in 5.1-channel Dolby Surround Sound. The resulting two-disc set was well worth the wait: While the limitations of the original video source are still evident in the sometimes-hazy image quality (Gilmour would later admit the concert should have been captured on film), Floyd fans will unanimously agree that Pulse has never looked or sounded better, and only the absence of group co-founder Roger Waters prevents this from being the ultimate document of Pink Floyd in performance. (Even without Waters, it's easily one of the group's most impressive stage productions.) Gracefully directed with minimal intrusion by veteran music video and concert director David Mallet, and shot on video during Pink Floyd's two-week stint at London's Earls Court Exhibition Centre in October 1994, this 145-minute performance (from Floyd's Division Bell tour) is a sonic marvel to behold. Under a massive arch festooned with then-state-of-the-art laser, lighting, and projection systems, the 1987 incarnation of Pink Floyd (Gilmour, keyboardist Richard Wright, and drummer Nick Mason) and their stellar supporting band kicks off with "Shine on You Crazy Diamond" (a loving tribute to Floyd co-founder Syd Barrett), followed by four tracks from The Division Bell, two from 1987's A Momentary Lapse of Reason, "Another Brick in the Wall (Part 2)" from 1979's magnum opus The Wall, and leading into intermission with an absolutely stunning performance of "One of These Days," the timeless opening track from 1971's Meddle.
		The centerpiece of Disc 2 is a near-perfect performance of 1974's Dark Side of the Moon in its entirety--reason enough to make this a must-have DVD for even the most casual Floyd admirers. And while no one will ever re-create the sheer magnificence of Clare Torry's original tour de force vocals on "The Great Gig in the Sky," it's safe to say that backup singers Sam Brown, Claudia Fontaine, and Durga McBroom deliver the next best thing, in addition to seamless contributions throughout the concert. After the closing heartbeat of "Eclipse," the concert ends with encore performances of "Wish You Were Here," "Comfortably Numb," and a no-holds-barred, pyrotechnically explosive rendition of The Wall's "Run Like Hell," all showcasing Gilmour's guitar mastery with frequent close-ups of his picking and fret-work as seen throughout the concert. (Like Gilmour, Mason and Wright were never dynamic onstage, and that's true here as well, but their technical precision is fully evident, and while guitarist Tim Renwick and saxophonist Dick Parry are each given moments to shine, bassist Guy Pratt is a worthy substitution for Waters, especially when vocally sparring with Gilmour on "Run Like Hell.")
		With beautiful packaging, an 8-page booklet, and menu designs by long-time Floyd associate Storm Thorgerson, the DVDs offer an abundance of bonus features including "Bootlegging the Bootleggers," featuring surprisingly good-quality "boot" video performances of "What Do You Want From Me?," "On the Turning Away," "Poles Apart," and "Marooned." The surreal round-ratio screen films seen throughout the concert can all be viewed independently (still in round format, and several offered in both original and alternate versions). Music videos for "Learning to Fly" and "Take It Back" are included on Disc 1, along with "Tour Stuff" including maps, itineraries, and stage plans for the 1994 tour. "Say Goodbye to Life as We Know It" is a playful backstage video (mostly involving the production staff's ongoing quest for a good pint of beer), and after delivering a heartfelt introduction to Pink Floyd's 1996 induction into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame (with Roger Waters and Syd Barrett acknowledged by Gilmour), Smashing Pumpkins leader Billy Corgan joins Gilmour and Wright for a moving acoustic performance of "Wish You Were Here" (directed at Waters, perhaps?). Additional features include album cover art, a photo gallery, and the concert-only audio choice between a 448kbps audio bitstream or a higher-quality 640kbps stream for higher-quality DVD players. The system set-up feature ensures that audiophiles will achieve optimum speaker performance in keeping with Pink Floyd's exacting technical standards. In tandem with the superior concert presentation, these features make Pulse one of the best--if not the best--music DVDs of 2006, guaranteed to satisfy Floyd fans for many years to come. --Jeff Shannon
		Description
		This landmark DVD features the first ever film of Pink Floyd playing the band's seminal album, The Dark Side of the Moon, live in concert. The set documents the 1994 Division Bell tour and was filmed at London's Earls Court during a record-breaking 14-night residency. The two-disc release contains the full concert performance with rare backstage footage and previously unseen extras making the collection a must-have for Pink Floyd fans.
		Disc 2 features a live filmed performance of Pink Floyd--David Gilmour, Nick Mason and Rick Wright--performing the group's towering masterpiece, The Dark Side of the Moon, in its glorious entirety during the second half of the Division Bell concert. Included on disc 1 are "Shine on You Crazy Diamond," "Another Brick in the Wall (Part 2)," "High Hopes," and "Learning to Fly" as well as never-before-seen rarities such as Bootlegging the Bootleggers and exclusive behind-the-scenes footage of life on the road with one of the world's biggest and most influential rock bands.
		Mixed in mind-expanding 5.1 surround sound and digitally re-mastered by James Guthrie, the Pulse DVD includes some of original screen films used for the 1970s concert performances of The Dark Side of the Moon (which were never filmed) as well as the visual components for the piece which were remade for the 1994 tour.</Critica>
        <Poster>image035.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="28" contador="10">
        <Nombre>Roger Waters: In the Flesh Live</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 26</Id>
        <Annus>2000</Annus>
        <Estado>Archivado</Estado>
        <Critica>Recorded on a single night in June 2000, In the Flesh: Live is a thrilling live testament to the strength of Roger Waters's peculiar artistic vision. Backed by a crack ensemble of both fresh and seasoned players, the former Pink Floyd songsmith powers through Floyd classics, underserved relics, and highlights from his spotty solo career. The man is in great shape, physically and musically, and he obviously has a blast playing live.
		What of the axe work? Accept the fact that Waters and Floyd guitarist David Gilmour no longer play together, and you'll appreciate stand-ins Snowy White and Doyle Bramhall II--and the degree to which they honor the parts and solos immortalized by Gilmour. (See the lavish but impersonal Pulse for a healthy dose of Gilmour's Floyd.) The Dolby Digital 5.1 surround mix is massive, presenting both the music's inherent spaciousness and the favorable acoustics in Portland, Oregon's Rose Garden Arena. The DVD's 18-minute documentary is long on downtime and short on musical interplay. Any way you cut it, though, this is a must for Floyd fans and a real treat for lovers of arty, intelligent rock. --Michael Mikesell
		Product Description
		Columbia recording artist and Pink Floyd founder Roger Waters toured the United States for the first time in 12 years in 1999-2000 with his highly acclaimed "In The Flesh" show that presented, for the first time, a comprehensive overview of Waters's music including: early Pink Floyd material; classic compositions from his masterpieces "The Wall" and "Dark Side of the Moon;" less well-known pieces from "Animals," "Wish You Were Here," and "The Final Cut;" songs from the solo tour de force "Amused To Death" and "The Pros and Cons of Hitch Hiking;" and the debut of a new song, "Each Small Candle." Songs: In the Flesh, The Happiest Days of Our Lives, Another Brick in the Wall Part 2, Mother, Get Your Filthy Hands Off My Desert, Southampton Dock, Pigs on the Wing Part 1, Dogs, Welcome to the Machine, Wish You Were Here, Shine On You Crazy Diamond (Parts 1-8), Set the Controls for the Heart of the Sun, Breathe (In The Air), Time, Money, The Pros and Cons of Hitch Hiking Part 11 (5:06 am? Every Stranger's Eyes), Perfect Sense (Parts I and II), The Bravery of Being Out of Range, It's a Miracle, Amused to Death, Brain Damage, Eclipse, Comfortably Numb, Each Small Candle.</Critica>
        <Poster>image033.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="29" contador="11">
        <Nombre>The Beatles - Let it be</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 27</Id>
        <Estado>Archivado</Estado>
        <Poster>image037.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="30" contador="12">
        <Nombre>The Beatles - Magical Mistery Tour</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 29</Id>
        <Annus>1967</Annus>
        <Estado>Archivado</Estado>
        <Poster>image039.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="31" contador="13">
        <Nombre>Bob Dylan - Compilation #1</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 30</Id>
        <Annus>1963 ~ 65</Annus>
        <Estado>Archivado</Estado>
        <Critica>CONTENTS
		Greenwood, Mississippi (6 July 1963)
		Only A Pawn In Their Game [last 2 verses only]
		March on Washington (28 Aug 1963)
		When The Ship Comes In
		Only A Pawn In Their Game
		Hold On
		Quest, CBC TV (1 Feb 1964)
		The Times They Are A-Changin&#x2019;
		Talkin&#x2019; World War III Blues
		The Lonesome Death Of Hattie Carroll
		Girl From The North Country
		A Hard Rain&#x2019;s A-Gonna Fall
		Restless Farewell
		BBC Tonight Show (May 1964)
		With God On Our Side [first three verses only]
		Steve Allen Show (25 Feb 1964)
		The Lonesome Death Of Hattie Carroll
		[same take is shown twice, first with then without timing strip]
		San Francisco Press Conference (3 Dec 1965)
		In full
		All very good quality monochrome archive footage</Critica>
        <Poster>image040.jpg</Poster>
        <Poster>image043.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="32" contador="14">
        <Nombre>Jaime Roos - Que te abrace el viento</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 37</Id>
        <Estado>Archivado</Estado>
        <Critica>Este DVD consiste en un Video-Largometraje basado en el "Concierto Aniversario" ofrecido en 1997, en el Teatro Solís de Montevideo al cumplirse 20 años de Jaime Roos con la música, el mismo esta recreado con notables imágenes de la Capital, muchas de ellas grabadas en 35m calidad CINE, todo se entrelaza Música e Imágenes hablan por si solas, logrando que el espectador comprenda el por que Montevideo es una Ciudad de Culto. Esa noche se dieron cita sobre el escenario del Solis, junto a Roos renombrados músicos de la escena uruguaya como los hermanos Fattoruso y los Ibarburu, Popo Romano, Gustavo Etchenique, Freddy Bessio y muchos más. El DVD surge del trabajo del reconocido director uruguayo Guillermo Peluffo.</Critica>
        <Poster>image063.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="33" contador="15">
        <Nombre>LUIS SALINAS  -  Música Argentina</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 38</Id>
        <Annus>2003</Annus>
        <Estado>Archivado</Estado>
        <Critica>  TEMAS
		- Zamba triste
		- Un vals
		- Zamba tonada
		- Por milonga
		- La pesada
		- Aire de tango
		- La cristalina
		- Para Corrientes y el Chaco
		- Balada para guitarra
		- Para Troilo y Salgan
		- Zamaba en mi
		- La misteriosa
		- Tangos:volver
		- La casita de mis viejos
		- El ultimo cafe
		- Mujer niña y amiga
		- La milomguera
		- Zamba de mi esperanza
		- Nostalgia santiagueña
		- Luna Cautiva</Critica>
        <Poster>image065.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="34" contador="16">
        <Nombre>Antonio Carlos Jobim featuring Gal Costa - Rio Revisited</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 40</Id>
        <Estado>Archivado</Estado>
        <Critica>1.  One Note Samba 3:13 Tom Jobim - Newton Mendonza
			2.  Desafinado 2:59 Tom Jobim - Newton Mendonza
			3.  Agua de Beber 3:06 Tom Jobim - Vinicius de Moraes
			4.  Dindi 4:57 Tom Jobim - Aloysio de Oliveira
			5.  Wave 2:54 Tom Jobim
			6.  Bolero 3:21 Tom Jobim
			7.  Gabriela 7:42 Tom Jobim
			8.  Chega de Saudade 4:19 Tom Jobim - Vinicius de Moraes
			9.  Two Kites 4:42 Tom Jobim
			10. Samba do Soho 3:15 Paulo Jobim - Ronaldo Bastos
			11.  Sabi? 3:14 Tom Jobim - Chico Buarque
			12.  Samba do Avi?o 3:29 Tom Jobim
			13.  Aguas de Mar?o 3:39 Tom Jobim
			14.  Corcovado 3:07 Tom Jobim</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>Formato   :   NTSC Region 2
			Aspecto Ratio : Full Screen
			Localizacion :  Los Angeles
			Año             :  1989
			Audios          : Portuguez PCM Stereo / Dolby Digital 5.1
			Fuente         :  DVD5  Original
			Backup         :  Copia 100% exacta del original
			Software       : DVD Decripter
			Subs             :  Japanese</DatosTecnicos>
        <Poster>image070.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="35" contador="17">
        <Nombre>LED ZEPPELIN - Mothership-remasterered</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 42</Id>
        <Annus>2007</Annus>
        <Estado>Archivado</Estado>
        <Critica>INTÉRPRETES: Robert Plant: vocals	
		Jimmy Page:  guitar	
John Paul Jones: bass	
John Bonham: drums	
		1. We&#x2019;re Gonna Groove (Royal Albert Hall)	
		   2. I Can&#x2019;t Quit You Babe (Royal Albert Hall)	
		   3. Dazed &amp; Confused (Royal Albert Hall)	
		   4. White Summer (Royal Albert Hall)	
		   5. What Is &amp; What Should Never Be (Royal Albert Hall)	
		   6. Moby Dick (Royal Albert Hall)	
		   7. Whole Lotta Love (Royal Albert Hall)
		   8. Communication Breakdown (Royal Albert Hall)
		   9. Bring It On Home (Royal Albert Hall)
		  10. Immigrant Song (Audio: 1972 / Pics, Australia 1972 Super8)
		  11. Black Dog (Madison Square Garden)
		  12. Misty Mountain Hop (Madison Square Garden)
		  13. Going To California (Earls Court)
		  14. In My Time Of Dying (Earls Court)
		  15. Stairway To Heaven (Earls Court)
		  16. Rock And Roll (Knebworth)
		  17. Nobody&#x2019;s Fault But Mine (Knebworth)
		  18. Kashmir (Knebworth)
		  19. Whole Lotta Love (Knebworth)
		"CRITICA: Mothership. The very best of Led Zeppelin saldrá el próximo 13 de noviembre, según ha anunciado el propio grupo. El nuevo disco de la formación británica es un doble CD que contiene una selección de las 24 mejores canciones de la historia musical de Zeppelin. Trayectoria que duró 12 años y que a pesar de no haber dado señales de vida durante más de veinticinco años, desde que falleciera el batería John Boham en 1980, la banda ha sido inspiración obligada para los grupos que han llegado posteriormente a la escena musical internacional.
La selección de los temas ha corrido de la mano de los tres integrantes que quedan, Jimmy Page, Robert Plant y John Paul Jones. En ella podemos encontrar títulos tan importantes para la historia del rock como Stairway to heaven, Whole lotta love, Kashmir, Rock and roll, Dazed and confused o Inmigrant song.
Además el nuevo lanzamiento incluirá un DVD de 90 minutos de canciones en directo extraídas del homónimo DVD que se lanzó en el 2003. Las imágenes recorren los años comprendidos entre 1969 y 1979, etapa en la que tocaron en el Royal Albert Hall (1970), en el Madison Square Garden(1973) o en Knebworth (1979)."</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>SISTEMA: PAL
AUDIO: Inglés Dolby Digital 5.1, Inglés DTS, Inglés 2.0
RELACION DE ASPECTO: 4:3		FORMATO: DVD9 =&gt; DVD9		DURACIÓN: Time: 118 min.	COMPRESIÓN: Sin Compresión.</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>1.58</Duracion>
        <Poster>image072.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="36" contador="18">
        <Nombre>Bob marley Reggae Roots</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 43</Id>
        <Estado>Archivado</Estado>
        <Critica>1. Introduction
		2 .I Shot The Sheriff
		3. Rebel Music
		4. Lively Up Yourself
		5. Dub Those
		6. Medley
		a. Jammin
		b. Get Up Stand UP
		c. Exodus
		Bonus Tracks (Video Clips)
		9. Is This Love
		10.Could You Be Loved
		11.Stir It Up
		12.Satisfy My Soul
		13.Buffalo Soldier
		14.Redemption Song
		15.Back To Jamaica.
		Boys From Jamaica.</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>SISTEMA: PAL
AUDIO: Inglés Dolby Digital 5.1
RELACION DE ASPECTO: 4/3"</DatosTecnicos>
        <Poster>image074.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="37" contador="53">
        <Nombre>Spinetta - Vivo en Personal Fest</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 48</Id>
        <Annus>2007</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <DatosTecnicos>Video: 4380 Kbps
Audio: 256 Kbps, 48 KHz, Stereo
Norma de Video: PAL
Formato de Pantalla: Fullscreen"</DatosTecnicos>
        <Poster>image077.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="38" contador="20">
        <Nombre>JANIS JOPLIN - THE KOZMIC BLUES</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 49</Id>
        <Estado>Archivado</Estado>
        <Critica>Cry Baby.
		Nor more Cane
		Throwing a Party
		Tell Mama
		Move Over
		Kozmic Blues
		Generation Club NYC 1967 :
		Coming Home	
		Cheap Thrills Sessions :	
		Coming Home	
		Piece of my Heart	
		Down on Me	
		Dick Cavett Show :	
		Combination of Two	
		Ball &amp; Chain	
		Monterey Pop :	
		Summertime	
		Ball &amp; Chain	
		Come Up the Years TV-Show :	
		Down on Me	
		The Goo Goo	
		TV-Show 1969 :	
		Summertime	
		Summertime Rehersal	
		Woodstock Unreleased :	
		Work me Lord	
		Musicscene :	
		Try	
		Bonus :	
		Raise your Hand	
		Summertime</Critica>
        <Poster>image080.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="39" contador="21">
        <Nombre>David Gilmour - Live in Gdansk</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 50</Id>
        <Annus>1986</Annus>
        <Estado>Archivado</Estado>
        <Critica>Disc : 3
1  Castellorizon (DVD)     
2  On An Island (DVD)      
3  The Blue (DVD)            
4  Red Sky At Night (DVD)      
5  This Heaven (DVD)          
6  Then I Close My Eyes (DVD)   
7  Smile (DVD)                
8  Take A Breath (DVD)
9  A Pocketful Of Stones (DVD) 
10  Where We Start (DVD)
11  Astronomy Domine (DVD)
12  High Hopes (DVD)
13  Echoes (DVD)  
14  A Great Day For Freedom (DVD)  
15  Comfortably Numb (DVD)  

-----------------------------------------------------------------------------   
Disc : 4
1  Shine On You Crazy Diamond (DVD)   
2  Wearing The Inside Out (DVD)     
3  Comfortably Numb (DVD)           
4  On An Island (DVD)           
5  High Hopes (DVD)                
6  The Blue (DVD)
7  Take A Breath (DVD)  
8  Echoes (Acoustic) (DVD) 
9  Barn Jam 166 (DVD) 
10  Barn Jam 192 (DVD) 
11  Barn Jam 121 (DVD)  </Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>Dolby Digital 5.1</DatosTecnicos>
        <Poster>image081.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="40" contador="22">
        <Nombre>Peter Gabriel - Growing Up Live</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 52</Id>
        <Annus>2003</Annus>
        <Estado>Archivado</Estado>
        <DatosTecnicos>Video: 2.13Mbps
			Audio: Dolby Digital 48Khz. 6 canales
			Norma de Video: PAL
			Formato de Pantalla: Widescreen (16:9)  </DatosTecnicos>
        <Poster>image083.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="41" contador="54">
        <Nombre>Spinetta - Un Mañana &#x2013; Edición de lujo</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 53 FALTA</Id>
        <Annus>2008</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Poster>image085.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="42" contador="24">
        <Nombre>Bob Dylan - Dont Look Back: 65 Tour Deluxe Edition</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 56</Id>
        <Annus>1967</Annus>
        <Estado>Archivado</Estado>
        <Critica>Dont Look Back is a 1967 documentary film by D.A. Pennebaker that principally covers Bob Dylan's 1965 concert tour of the United Kingdom. In 1998, the film was selected for preservation in the United States National Film Registry by the Library of Congress as being "culturally, historically, or aesthetically significant".
The film features Joan Baez, Donovan and Alan Price (who had just left The Animals), Dylan's manager Albert Grossman and his road manager Bob Neuwirth; Marianne Faithfull, John Mayall, Ginger Baker, and Allen Ginsberg may also be glimpsed in the background. The film shows a young Dylan: confident if not arrogant, confrontational and contrary, but also charismatic and charming. Notable scenes include:
- Dylan's extended taunting of Time Magazine's London arts and science correspondent Horace Freeland Judson who was subjected to what he believes to be a contrived tirade of abuse from Dylan.
- Dylan's interrupting Alan Price's backstage performance of "Little Things" to ask Price why he left The Animals.
- Dylan and Baez singing Hank Williams songs in a hotel room, as well as Baez singing the first few verses of "Percy's Song" and "Love Is Just a Four-Letter Word" (which was still apparently unfinished at the time, as Baez later tells Dylan, "If you finish it I'll sing it on a record"; she would record it in 1968.)
- Dylan's pre-concert philosophical jousting with a "science student" (Terry Ellis, who later co-founded Chrysalis Records).
- Grossman negotiating with former Bebop Dance band leader and music agent, Tito Burns.
- Dylan singing "Only a Pawn in Their Game" on July 6, 1963 at a Voters' Registration Rally in Greenwood, Mississippi (shot by artist and experimental filmmaker Ed Emshwiller).
- A selection of songs from Dylan's Royal Albert Hall performance.
- Dylan destroying the room with "It's All Over Now, Baby Blue" after politely listening to Donovan play a song.
Dylan's romance with Baez had pretty much run its course by the time of the tour, and the film candidly captures what essentially amounts to their breakup.
The opening scene of the film also served as a kind of music video for Dylan's song "Subterranean Homesick Blues", in which the singer displays and discards a series of cue cards bearing selected words and phrases from the lyrics (including intentional misspellings and puns). Allen Ginsberg makes a cameo appearance.  ~ Wikipedia
Disc 1:
- Feature (96min)
- Commentary by D.A. Pennebaker and Bob Neuwirth
- 5 Complete Audio Tracks of Performances from the Tour
- Alternate Take of the Subterranean Homesick Blues Cue Card Video
- Original Trailer
- Discographies, Filmographies, Biographies
Disc 2:
- 65 Revisited [Additional Footage from the Tour] (65min)
- Commentary by D.A. Pennebaker and Bob Neuwirth</Critica>
        <Poster>image089.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="43" contador="25">
        <Nombre>Roberto Carlos &amp; Caetano Veloso - E a Musica De Tom Jobim</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 57</Id>
        <Annus>2007</Annus>
        <Estado>Archivado</Estado>
        <Critica>1. Garota de Ipanema
2. Wave
3. Águas de Março
4. Por Toda a Minha Vida ( Exaltação do Amor )
5. Ela é Carioca
6. Inútil Paisagem
7. Meditação
8.Caminho de Pedra
9.O que Tinha que Ser
10.Surfboard
11. Insensatez
12. Por Causa de Você
13. Ligia
14. Corcovado
15. Samba do Avião
16. Eu Sei que Vou Te Amar / Soneto da Fidelidade
17. Tereza da Praia
18. Chega de Saudade</Critica>
        <Poster>image093.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="44" contador="26">
        <Nombre>Mercedes Sosa - Cantora por un viaje intimo</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 60</Id>
        <Annus>2009</Annus>
        <Estado>Archivado</Estado>
        <Critica>SINOPSIS:
ZONA DE PROMESAS - MERCEDES SOSA CON GUSTAVO CERATI
CELADOR DE SUEÑOS - MERCEDES SOSA CON OROZCO BARRIENTOS-GUSTAVO SANTAOLALLA
AQUELLAS PEQUEÑAS COSAS - MERCEDES SOSA CON JOAN MANUEL SERRAT
NADA - MERCEDES SOSA CON M.GRAÑA L.FEDERICO
DONDE TERMINA EL ASFALTO - MERCEDES SOSA CON COQUI SOSA
BARRO TAL VEZ - MERCEDES SOSA CON LUIS ALBERTO SPINETTA
ZAMBA PARA OLVIDARTE - MERCEDES SOSA CON DIEGO TORRES FACUNDO RAMIREZ
LA LUNA LLENA RUBEN RADA LA CHILINGA
ESA MUSIQUITA - MERCEDES SOSA CON TERESA PARODI
NOVICIA - MERCEDES SOSA CON VICTOR HEREDIA
PARAO - MERCEDES SOSA CON VICENTICO
PAJARO DE RODILLAS - MERCEDES SOSA CON NACHA ROLDAN
ZAMBA DEL CIELO - MERCEDES SOSA CON FITO PAEZ LILIANA HERRERO
LA MAZA - MERCEDES SOSA CON SHAKIRA
HIMNO DE MI CORAZON - MERCEDES SOSA CON LEON GIECO
JAMÁS TE OLVIDARE - MERCEDES SOSA CON MARCELA MORELO
DEJA LA VIDA VOLAR - MERCEDES SOSA CON PEDRO AZNAR
ZAMBA DE LOS ADIOSES - MERCEDES SOSA CON DUO NUEVO CUYO
DESARMA Y SANGRA - MERCEDES SOSA CON CHARLY GARCIA
CANCION PARA UN NIÑO DE LA CALLE - MERCEDES SOSA CON CALLE 13
MISIONERA - MERCEDES SOSA CON LUIZ CARLOS BORGES
RAZON DE VIVIR - MERCEDES SOSA CON LILIA DOWNS
ROMANCE DE LA LUNA TUCUMANA - MERCEDES SOSA CON J.QUINTERO LUNA MONTI
EL ANGEL DE LA BICICLETA - MERCEDES SOSA CON GUSTAVO CORDERA
INSENSATEZ - MERCEDES SOSA CON LUIS SALINAS
CORACAO VAGABUNDO - MERCEDES SOSA CON CAETANO VELOSO
O QUE SERA - MERCEDES SOSA CON DANIELA MERCURY
Y ASI Y ASI MERCEDES SOSA CON LUCIANO PEREYRA</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>Video: 3.300/2.640Kbs
Audio: 2.0 LPCM
Norma de Video: NTSC
Formato de Pantalla: Widescreen
Idioma Audio: Español
Subtitulos: español - ingles - Portugues
Menú: Si
Extras: Si
Informacion del CCE
Phase I, PREPARATION started.
- DVD-RB v1.20.4
- AVISYNTH 2.5.6.0
- CCE 2.70.2.10 encoder selected.
- "Steal Space from Extras" mode (33%) is enabled.
- Source: MERCEDES SOSA - CANTORA
- VTS_01: 2.864.345 sectors.
-- Scanning and writing .D2V &amp; .AVS files
-- Processed 182.302 frames.
-- Building .AVS and .ECL files
- VTS_03: 67.186 sectors.
-- Scanning and writing .D2V &amp; .AVS files
-- Processed 3.239 frames.
-- Building .AVS and .ECL files
- Reduction Level for DVD-5: 54,1%
- Overall Bitrate : 3.300/2.640Kbs
- Space for Video : 2.494.002KB</DatosTecnicos>
        <Poster>mercedessosacantora.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="45" contador="27">
        <Nombre>Elis Regina - MPB Especial</Nombre>
        <Estado>Archivado</Estado>
        <Critica>Programa para la televisión que contiene... ¡¡¡documental, entrevista y show!!!</Critica>
        <Poster>image094.png</Poster>
        <Poster>DVD 58</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="46" contador="0">
        <Nombre>Pink Floyd - Live at Pompeii</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 9 falta dvd</Id>
        <Annus>1971</Annus>
        <Estado>Espera</Estado>
        <Critica>Plot Synopsis: Live versions of the songs, filmed in an old Pompeii amphitheater. Songs included are Echoes (split into 2 parts), Careful with that axe, Eugene, A saucerful of secrets, One of those days, Set the controls for the heart of the sun, Mademoiselle nobbs (Seamus, but with Rick's dog on vocals). "Careful" and "Set the controls" are shot at night with minimal lighting, setting a beautiful mood. And the live Saucerful just has to be seen, with Waters jumping around in the sunlight banging the huge gong. The 80-minute version features studio footage from the recordings of Dark side of the Moon, with alternate versions of Us and them, On the run and Brain Damage, as well as hilarious interviews with the band (don't miss Waters raving about the great economical collapse, and Nick whining about the crust on the pie).
		Conceived by the French director Adrian Maben as "an anti-Woodstock film," Pink Floyd: Live at Pompeii was shot in October 1971 in a vacant, 2,000-year-old amphitheater--a venue chosen to accentuate the grandeur and spaciousness of the band's Meddle-era music. This disc contains a new, 90-minute director's cut as well as the original 60-minute concert film, whose production and effects feel inescapably dated. Maben's cut goes to great lengths to lend the film a more contemporary feel, but it's the earlier version that makes this disc such a gem, being more focused on the music and more wholistic in vision. The anamorphic, 16:9 director's cut interweaves the Pompeii performances with fascinating but distracting interviews and music snippets filmed later (mostly during the recording of Dark Side of the Moon). The movie was originally prepared in a 4:3 aspect ratio, however, and the widescreen version crops perfectly framed images like the nine-square mosaic of drummer Nick Mason in "One of These Days." The original offers plenty of closeups of fingers on frets and keys, with shots that are often luxuriously long in duration. And the picture quality from Pompeii is revelatory: outstandingly sharp and clear, rich in subtle grades of light and color.
		Generous extras include everything from original posters, reviews, bootleg album covers, and song lyrics to a 24-minute interview with Maben. But for all the director's talk of the glorious acoustics in Pompeii's amphitheater, there's little natural ambience to be heard. The Dolby Digital 2.0 sound is clear, dry, and two-dimensional, though notably better than any previous video release. --Michael Mikesell</Critica>
        <Poster>image018.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="47" contador="0">
        <Nombre>Pink Floyd - Wish You Were Here</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 21</Id>
        <Annus>2006</Annus>
        <Estado>Espera</Estado>
        <Critica>Wish You Were Here was released in September 1975 as the follow up to Dark Side Of The Moon - a pretty hard act to follow, but in many respects this amazing new album outshone its illustrious predecessor. Shine On You Crazy Diamond with its majestic introduction is arguably the finest recording in the entire Pink Floyd career. On this flawless album every track pulls its weight and the title track Wish You Were Here which was revived for Live 8 has gone on to achieve classic status . This is the long awaited critical review of the album featuring rare live performances by Pink Floyd alongside rare archive interviews with the band.</Critica>
        <Poster>image028.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="48" contador="0">
        <Nombre>Paul McCartney: The McCartney Years</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 45</Id>
        <Annus>2007</Annus>
        <Estado>Espera</Estado>
        <Critica>"Cuatro décadas de imágenes inéditas, actuaciones en directo y vídeos musicales se resumen en ""The McCartney Years"", el triple DVD del ex-beatle que se ha puesto a la venta el 13 de noviembre.
Paul McCartney también ha grabado nuevos comentarios para los más de cuarenta vídeos que se incluyen en el DVD y que pueden ser vistos en orden cronológico.
Los dos primeros discos incluyen clips que van desde ""Maybe I'm Amazed"", de la década de los 70, hasta ""Fine Line"", de 2005. Los extras son el filme promocional de ""Band on the Run"" y un documental sobre la grabación del álbum ""Chaos and Creation in the Backyard"" (2005).
En el tercer disco figuran imágenes de ""Rockshow"", filmado durante la gira de Wings de 1976; un nuevo montaje de la aparición, en 1991, de McCartney en la serie ""Unplugged"", de la MTV, y once canciones de su actuación en el Festival de Glastonbury, en 2004, con nuevos comentarios del músico.
"	"Disco 1  
""Tug Of War""
""Say Say Say""
""Silly Love Songs""
""Band On The Run""
""Maybe I'm Amazed""
""Heart Of The Country""
""Mamunia""
""With A Little Luck""
""Goodnight Tonight""
""Waterfalls""
""My Love""
""C-Moon""
""Baby's Request""
""Hi Hi Hi""
""Ebony And Ivory""
""Take It Away""
""Mull Of Kintyre""
""Helen Wheels""
""I've Had Enough""
""Coming Up""
""Wonderful Christmastime"""	"Disco 2
""Pipes Of Peace""
""My Brave Face""
""Beautiful Night""
""Fine Line""
""No More Lonely Nights""
""This One""
""Little Willow""
""Pretty Little Head""
""Birthday""
""Hope Of Deliverance""
""Once Upon A Long Ago""
""All My Trials""
""Brown-Eyed Handsome Man""
""Press""
""No Other Baby""
""Off The Ground""
""Biker Like An Icon""
""Spies Like Us""
""Put It There""
""Figure Of Eight""
""C'Mon People"""	"Disco 3
De ""Rockshow"":
""Venus And Mars""
""Rock Show""
""Jet""
""Maybe I'm Amazed""
""Lady Madonna""
""Listen To What The Man Said""
""Bluebird""
De ""MTV Unplugged"":
""I Lost My Little Girl""
""Every Night""
""And I Love Her""
""That Would Be Somethin""
De Glastonbury 2004:
""Jet""
""Flaming Pie""
""Let Me Roll It""
""Blackbird""
""Band On The Run""
""Back In The USSR""
""Live And Let Die""
""Hey Jude""
""Yesterday""
""Helter Skelter""
""Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"""
	Título Original: Paul McCartney: The McCartney Years				
	Año: 2007				
	País: Reino Unido				
	Director: Dick Carruthers				
	Compañia: Cheese Film &amp; Video				
	Género: Musical				
	Lanzamiento: 12 Noviembre de 2007 (UK)				
		live 1970 Various Locations Canada :</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>Origen: DVD9
Formato: DVD9 - FullDVD
Sistema: PAL
Zona: Multizona
Imagen: 720x576 16:9
Compresión: Ninguna
Idiomas: Inglés LPCM 2ch; Inglés DTS 5.1ch; Inglés AC3 2ch
Subtítulos: Inglés, Francés, Alemán, Español, Portugué, Italiano y Holandés.
Tamaño: 7,7GB Dvd1 7,4GB Dvd2 7,3GB Dvd3</DatosTecnicos>
        <Poster>image079.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="49" contador="0">
        <Nombre>Maria Rita &#x2013; Segundo ao vivo</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 54</Id>
        <Annus>2006</Annus>
        <Estado>Espera</Estado>
        <Poster>image087.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="50" contador="0">
        <Nombre>Peter Gabriel Play The Videos</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 55</Id>
        <Estado>Espera</Estado>
        <Critica>Lista de Temas:  
1 FATHER, SON 
2 SLEDGEHAMMER 
3 BLOOD OF EDEN 
4 GAMES WITHOUT FRONTIERS 
5 I DON'T REMEMBER 
6 BIG TIME 
7 LOVETOWN 
8 RED RAIN 
9 IN YOUR EYES 
10 DON'T GIVE UP 
11 THE BARRY WILLIAMS SHOW 
12 WASHING OF THE WATER 
13 BIKO 
14 KISS THAT FROG 
15 MERCY STREET 
16 GROWING UP 
17 SHAKING THE TREE 
18 SHOCK THE MONKEY 
19 STEAM 
20 THE DROP 
21 ZAAR 
22 SOLSBURY HILL 
23 DIGGING IN THE DIRT 
EXTRAS: 
24 [PROGRAMMABLE 18 TRACK JUKEBOX] 
25 GAMES WITHOUT FRONTIERS [liVE 2004] 
26 [VIDEO INTRODUCTIONS] 
27 [trAILER FOR GROWING UP ON TOUR - A FAMILY PORTRAIT] 
28 THE NEST THAT SAILED THE SKY 
29 MODERN LOVE [ORIGINAL 1977 MUSIC VIDEO] 
30 [trAILER FOR GROWING UP LIVE] 
31 [trAILER FOR SECRETWORLD LIVE]</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>DVD9
AUDIO (CODEC):
Dolby 2.0 y 5.1 + dts 5.1 96/24
SUBTÍTULOS:
Aleman, Inglés, Español, Frances. Italiano, Portugués
SISTEMA:
PAL   4/3
MÉTODO DE RIPEO:
Dvd original desencriptado con Shrink  sin compresión.</DatosTecnicos>
        <Poster>image088.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="51" contador="0">
        <Nombre>Saturday Night Live *25 Years of Music*</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 59</Id>
        <Annus>2003</Annus>
        <Estado>Espera</Estado>
        <Critica>saturdaynightlive25year_5.jpg
	DIRECTOR: Aviva Slesin, Christopher Guest, Claude Kerven, Mike DeSeve, Robert Smigel
	INTÉRPRETES: Don Pardo, Lenny Pickett, Darrell Hammond, G.E. Smith, Tim Meadows y otros
	SINOPSIS:
	Colección de 5 dvd's conmemorativos del 25 aniversario del programa, con lo mejor de las actuaciones musicales en directo y sketches de humor.
	Volumen 1
	Billy Joel Only - The Good Die Young (1978), Ray Charles - What'd I Say (1975), Carly Simon - You're So Vain (1976), Grateful Dead - Casey Jones (1978), Simon &amp; Garfunkel - The Boxer (1975), Joe Cocker - Feelin Alright (1975), Elvis Costello - Less Than Zero / Radio Radio (1977), Blues Brothers - Soul Man (1978), Patti Smith - Gloria (1976), Mick Jagger &amp; Peter Tosh - Don't Look Back (1978), The Band - The Night They Drove Old Dixie Down (1976)
	Sketches de John Belushi, Steve Martin, Jane Curtin, Laine Newman, Gilda Radner, Chevy Chase, Paul Simon, Bill Murray, Andy Kaufman, Lorne Michaels, Dan Aykroyd y Mick Jagger.
	Volumen 2
	Tina Turner - Better Be Good to Me (1985), James Brown - I Got You (1980), Queen - Crazy Little Thing Called Love (1982), Randy Newman - I Love L.A. (1983), The Go Go's - We Got the Beat (1981), Rick James - Super Freak (1981), Talking Heads - Take Me To The River (1979), Spinal Tap - Big Bottom (1984), John Mellencamp - Pink Houses (1983), Duran Duran - Hungry Like The Wolf (1983)
	Volumen 3
	The Bangles - Hazy Shade of Winter (1988), Tom Petty &amp; The Heartbreakers - Free Falin' (1989), Paul Simon - Diamonds on the Soles of Her Shoes (1986), Neil Young - Rockin' in the Free World (1989), Roy Orbison - O Pretty Woman (1987), Pretenders - Don't Get Me Wrong (1986), Fine Young Cannibals - She Drives Me Crazy (1989), Sting - We'll Be Together (1987), Elvis Costello - Veronica (1989)
	Sketches de Mike Myers, Dana Carvey, Aerosmith, Chris Farley, Patrick Swayze, Jon Lovitz, Harry Hall, Mick Jagger, Phil Hartman, Michael Myers, Chris Rock, Sting, Valerie Bertinelli y Eddie Van Halen
	Volumen 4
	R.E.M. - Losing My Religion (1991), Sinead O'Connor - War (1992), Madonna - Fever (1993), Aretha Franklin - Chain of Fools (1994), Eric Clapton - Wonderful Tonight (1990), Nirvana - Rape Me (1993), Paul McCartney - Hey Jude (1993), En Vogue - Free Your Mind (1992), Counting Crows - Round Here (1994), Bruce Springsteen - Living Proof (1992), Live - I Alone (1995), Blind Melon - No Rain (1994)
	Sketches de Mike Myers, Mick Jagger, Dana Carvey, Madonna, Phil Hartman, Adam Sandler, Chris Farley, James Taylor, Rosie O'Donnell, Kevin Knealon, David Spade, Paul McCartney y Michael Bolton</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>vol 1: Video: 4554 Kbps; 
	vol 2: Video: 4708 Kbps
	vol 3: Video: 4697 Kbps
	vol 4: Video: 4845 Kbps
	Audio: Ac3 5.1 - 2.0
	Norma de Video: NTSC
	Formato de Pantalla: Fullscreen
	Idioma Audio: Ingles
	Subtitulos: Frances - Aleman - Español
	Menú: Si
	Extras: No</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>90 minutos por DVD aprox.</Duracion>
        <Poster>saturdaynightlive25year.jpg</Poster>
        <Poster>saturdaynightlive25year_3.jpg</Poster>
        <Poster>saturdaynightlive25year_4.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="52" contador="28">
        <Nombre>Jimi Hendrix - Live at Monterey</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>1967</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>The Jimi Hendrix Experience: Live At Monterey
Year: 1967
Genre: Rock
Jim Hendrix Experience: Live at Monterey is the definitive Blu-ray presentation of Jimi Hendrix's unforgettable Monterey Pop Festival performance.
This special edition Blu-ray features all of the exciting film footage from Jimi's incendiary June 18, 1967 concert newly transferred from the original 16mm camera reversal, into 1080i high-definition video, re-edited and presented in its original performance sequence. The audio soundtrack features a new 5.1 and 2.0 stereo soundtrack mixed by Eddie Kramer, Jimi's original engineer. 
Tracks:
01. Killing Floor
02. Foxey Lady
03. Like A Rolling Stone
04. Rock Me Baby
05. Hey Joe
06. The Wind Cries Mary
07. Purple Haze
08. Wild Thing
09. Stone Free
10. Like A Rolling Stone 
Usa | Universal Music</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>Complete name : Jimi.Hendrix.Live.At.Monterey.BluRay.720p.DTS.x264-CtrlHD.mkv
Format : Matroska
File size : 3.29 GiB
Duration : 1h 2mn
Overall bit rate : 7 512 Kbps
Encoded date : UTC 2008-12-16 06:39:24
Bit rate : 6 000 Kbps
Width : 1 280 pixels
Height : 720 pixels
Display aspect ratio : 16:9
Frame rate : 23.976 fps
Language : English
Audio
Format : DTS
Bit rate : 1 510 Kbps
Channel(s) : 6 channels
Sampling rate : 48.0 KHz
Bit depth : 24 bits
Compression mode : Lossy</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>1.02</Duracion>
        <Poster>image086.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="53" contador="0">
        <Nombre>Lou Reed - Berlin</Nombre>
        <Estado>Espera</Estado>
        <Critica>Lou Reed; guitarra voz
Fernando Saunders; bajo
Tony "Thunder" Smith; batería
Rob Wassserman; percusión
Ruphert Christie; teclados
Steve Hunter; guitarra
Sharon Jones, Antony; coros
New London's Children Choir
TEMAS:
01 &#x201c;Sad Song (Intro)&#x201d;
02 &#x201c;Berlin&#x201d;
03 &#x201c;Lady Day&#x201d;
04 &#x201c;Men of Good Fortune&#x201d;
05 &#x201c;Caroline Says I&#x201d; 
06 &#x201c;How Do You Think It Feels?&#x201d; 
07 &#x201c;Oh, Jim&#x201d; 
08 &#x201c;Caroline Says II&#x201d; 
09 &#x201c;The Kids&#x201d; 
10 &#x201c;The Bed&#x201d; 
11 &#x201c;Sad Song&#x201d;
12 &#x201c;Candy Says&#x201d; 
13 &#x201c;Rock Minuet&#x201d; 
14 &#x201c;Sweet Jane&#x201d; 
CRITICA: Treinta y cinco años han pasado desde la aparición en 1973 de la obra maestra de Lou Reed Berlin, un álbum donde el cantante, compositor y poeta americano nos adentra en el romance de una pareja de jovenes abrumados por la drogadicción mediante una dramática história que nos envuelve de principio a fin. El disco fue un gran fracaso comercial y en los últimos 30 años nunca había sido tocado en directo. Producida en la edición actual y la original por Bob Ezrin, la famosa obra de Reed es ahora presentada en un directo en CD y DVD grabado en el año 2006 en Nueva York y que lo encaminó en una gira por todo el mundo representando por primera vez la obra Art Rock al completo.</Critica>
        <Duracion>1.17</Duracion>
        <Poster>image091.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="54" contador="22">
        <Nombre>Patricio Rey y sus Redonditos de Ricota - Estadio de Racing - Diciembre de 1998</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 66</Id>
        <Annus>1998</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>"En el año 1998, llaman nuevamente a Conejo Jolivet, para incorporarse definitivamente a la banda. Al mismo tiempo graban junto al asistente de la banda "EL Soldado" un CD llamado "Tren de Fugitivos", en el que participan Skay, Semilla, Sidotti, Dawi, Indio y Conejo, con gran repercusión under. Para 1998 se incorporó también a la banda, como miembro estable un viejo colaborador de la época de Lobo suelto/Cordero atado: Hernán Aramberri, en samplers y teclados. Ese mismo año salió a la venta Último bondi a Finisterre, disco que representa un giro musical en su carrera gracias a la incorporación de sonidos digitales y samplers. Este material fue presentado las noches del 18 y 19 de Diciembre  en el estadio de Racing Club de Avellaneda, totalizando noventa mil espectadores."         (cita de Wikipedia)

[:exc:] TEMAS:

# El Pibe De Los Astilleros
# Un Angel Para Tu Soledad
# ¡Cruz Diablo!
# Scaramanzia
# Drogocop
# La Pequeña Novia Del Carioca
# Pogo
# Las increíbles andanzas del Capitán Buscapina en Cibersiberia
# Vamos Las Bandas
# Nueva Roma
# Todo Un Palo
# Gualicho
# Alien Duce
# El Arbol Del Gran Bonete
# ¡Estás Frito Angelito!
# Shopping disco-zen
# Juguetes Perdidos
# Esto es to-to-todo amigos
# Mi Perro Dinamita
# Ñam fi frufi fali fru
# La Bestia Pop
# Queso Ruso
# Un Tal Brigitte Bardot
# Jijiji

     Tiempo Total: 2h. 13 m.</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>Video: 4000 kbps.
Audio: AC3 48khz 224 kb/s tot, Stereo (2/0)
Norma de Video: NTSC
Formato de Pantalla: Fullscreen 4:3

Idioma Audio: Español
Subtitulos: No.
Menú: Si.
Extras: No.
Link con Info: Link</DatosTecnicos>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="55" contador="20">
        <Nombre>The Doors - 30th Anniversary Collection</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 65</Id>
        <Annus>2001</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>INTÉRPRETES:
Jim Morrison - vocals
Ray Manzarek - keyboards
John Densmore - drums
Robby Krieger - guitar
DURACIÓN: 185 minutos
GÉNERO: Musical
SINOPSIS:
* Live at the Hollywood Bowl
 Filmado en vivo en el Hollywood Bowl durante el fin de semana del Cuatro de Julio de 1968
1. WhenThe Music's Over
2. Alabama Song (Whiskey Bar)
3. Back Door Man
4. 5 to 1
5. Moonlight Drive
6. Horse Latitudes
7. From The Celebration of the Lizard
8. Spanish Caravan
9. Unknown Soldier
10. Light My Fire (extended Version)
11. The End
* Dance on Fire
colección de presentaciones en vivo y por televisión, videos promocionales y grabaciones raras detrás de las cámaras.
1. Break On Through
2. People are Strange
3. Light My Fire
4. Wild Child
5. L.A Woman
6. The Unknown Soldier
7. Roadhouse Blues
8. Texas Radio
9. Love me Two Times
10. Touch Me
11. Horse Latitudes
12. Moonlight Drive
13. The End
14. Crystal Ship
15. Adagio
16. Rider on the Storm
* The Soft Parade
1. The Changeling
2. Wishful Sinful
3. Wild Child
4. Build Me a Woman
5. The Unknown Soldier
6. The Soft Parade
7. Hello I Love You
* Bonus
1. Break on Through (Isle of Wight Track)
2. The Ghost Song</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>SISTEMA: PAL
AUDIO: Inglés 2.0, LPCM
SUBTÍTULOS: Español, Francés, Italiano, Alemán
RELACION DE ASPECTO: 4:3
FORMATO: DVD9 =&gt; DVD9
COMPRESIÓN: Sin Compresión.</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>1.02+1.05+0.47</Duracion>
        <Poster>thedoors30c2.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="56" contador="41">
        <Nombre>Queen - Rock Montreal &amp; Live Aid</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>1981</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>The only Queen concert ever filmed in its entirety, this 1981 Montreal Live Aid performance has been digitally restored and remixed. Featuring dynamic front man Freddie Mercury, the band puts on a high-octane show for a crowd of excited fans. Songs include "We Will Rock You," "We Are the Champions," "Somebody to Love," "Get Down Make Love," "Under Pressure," "Crazy Little Thing Called Love," "Killer Queen," "Bohemian Rhapsody" and many more.
Queen: Rock Montreal and Live Aid rocks the Blu-ray format in a 1080p/VC-1 encode framed at a widescreen 1:78:1 aspect ratio. For a film that is twenty-six years old, it looks pretty good. Sourced from 35mm film, there are no pops, scratches or dirt to distract from the concert. Black levels are stable, sometimes crushed, and are not as deep as I have seen on other concert videos. Colors are somewhat less vibrant than usual, but the colored lights do manage to wash the stage with a blend of primary colors. Detail is well rendered from the hair and facial features, to the texture of clothing. However the detail drops in the presence of the white spotlights used with the colored stage lights. Color banding is apparent in some shots, and film grain becomes more obvious when all lighting is shining simultaneously. Some shots are also softer than others, but aside from all this it's a phenomenal presentation nevertheless.
This concert video features two audio tracks to choose from - DTS-HD HR 24-bit/96 kHz 5.1 (at 3Mbps), and a Stereo LPCM track at a 24-bit/48 kHz. Much to my surprise I found the stereo track much more satisfying. The vocals are very well recorded, and the balance of the vocal harmony is excellent - capturing every part equally. Although Mercury has a very dynamic voice, there is no audible clipping to be heard. Bass emanating from the LFE is strong and powerful, but always balanced with the other elements in the mix. The piano and lead guitar are perfectly balanced with the other instruments, and no element sticks out of the mix at any time. The DTS-HD track uses the surrounds for ambience and crowd noise, and it fills out the front sound stage effectively. Both audio tracks are strong presentations, and sure to please Queen fans everywhere. 
Track listing:
1 - Intro
2 - We Will Rock You (fast)
3 - Let Me Entertain You
4 - Play The Game
5 - Somebody To Love
6 - Killer Queen
7 - I'm In Love With My Car
8 - Get Down Make Love
9 - Save Me
10 - Now I'm Here
11 - Dragon Attack
12 - Now I'm Here (reprise)
13 - Love Of My Life
14 - Under Pressure
15 - Keep Yourself Alive
16 - Drum &amp; Timpani Solo
17 - Guitar Solo
18 - Crazy Little Thing Called Love
19 - Jailhouse Rock
20 - Bohemian Rhapsody
21 - Tie Your Mother Down
22 - Another One Bites The Dust
23 - Sheer Heart Attack
24 - We Will Rock You
25 -We Are The Champions
26 - God Save The Queen</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>Contenedor Matroska - 4,84GB - 95 min
Video AVC - 1280x720 - Progresivo - 23,976fps - 4978Kbps
Audio AC3 - 6 canales - 640 Kbps - 48 KHz - Inglés
Audio DTS - 6 canales - 1510 Kbps - 48 KHz - Inglés
Subtitulos No
Menú capítulos No
Encode Video y montaje Grupo LorDS</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>1.35</Duracion>
        <Poster>queen_montreal.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="57" contador="18">
        <Nombre>The Rolling Stones - Ladies &amp; Gentlemen</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>1972</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>Film of The Rolling Stones' 1972 United States tour.
Tracks:
1. Brown Sugar&#x2028;
2. Bitch&#x2028;
3. Gimme Shelter&#x2028;
4. Dead Flowers&#x2028;
5. Happy&#x2028;
6. Tumbling Dice&#x2028;
7. Love in Vain&#x2028;
8. Sweet Virginia&#x2028;
9. You Can&#x2019;t Always Get What You Want&#x2028;
10. All Down the Line&#x2028;
11. Midnight Rambler&#x2028;
12. Bye Bye Johnny&#x2028;
13. Rip This Joint&#x2028;
14. Jumpin&#x2019; Jack Flash&#x2028;
15. Street Fighting Man</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>CONTENEDOR: MKV
FUENTE DE VIDEO: BLU-RAY
CODEC DE VIDEO: x264
FRAMES DE VIDEO: 24
RESOLUCIÓN DE VIDEO: 1920x1032
BITRATE DE VIDEO: 10,6 Mbps
AUDIO 1: DTS 5.1 1536 Kbps Inglés
TAMAÑO: 6,97 GB</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>1.22</Duracion>
        <Poster>rollingstonesladiesandg.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="58" contador="21">
        <Nombre>Roger Waters - The Wall on Tour 2010</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 67</Id>
        <Annus>2010</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>DVD ONE: Approx. 58 mins

Intro
In The Flesh?
The Thin Ice
Another Brick In The Wall (Part 1)
The Happiest Days Of Our Lives
Another Brick In The Wall (Part 2)
Mother
Goodbye Blue Sky
Empty Spaces
What Shall We Do Now
Young Lust
One Of My Turns
Don't Leave Me Now
Another Brick In The Wall (Part 3)
The Last Few Bricks
Goodbye Cruel World


DVD TWO: Approx. 53 mins

Hey You
Is There Anybody Out There?
Nobody Home
Vera
Bring The Boys Back Home
Comfortably Numb
The Show Must Go On
In The Flesh
Run Like Hell
Waiting For The Worms
Stop
The Trial
Outside the Wall

All songs are chapter indexed.

The foundation of all the footage (and audio) was taken from 9/20. Additional shots are from the 9/21, 10/12 and 10/13 shows and all are from tapehead2's HD master files.

Thanks to all those who shared their footage for this project. Thanks once again to the HVR team, MOB for the appropriate EQ work and Big Ed for checking and correcting, and for the quick turn around. Thanks to Chris for the artwork, you always have the coolest sigs on the forum. Thanks to Rick B. for this and 30+ years of recording shows in Chicago.

But the biggest thanks of all goes to my new friend tapehead2 (TH2) for shooting these shows so brilliantly. After posting the initial clips on YouTube I contacted TH2 to see if a multi-camera edit was ever considered. The response was that TH2 wished for the shows to be shared "as is". I decided to cut together a few songs just to show TH2 the possibilities and after watching them on YouTube agreed to send me the master HD footage. The 9/20 and 9/21 shows cut together beautifully, but I still wished that we had a few more shots covered. Since TH2 had tickets to the Nassau Coliseum shows and was planning on shooting them as well I offered some camera suggestions, a lot of them in fact, to get some of the shots I still wanted. The dude abides. So thanks to TH2 for the ultimate sacrifice of not being able to enjoy these shows like the rest of us have. That's a hefty price, especially when considering that Pink Floyd isn't on the top of TH2's favorites list. Perhaps inspired by being embraced by the PF "communities" has changed that? And of course thanks to Roger for putting on such a kick ass show.

This was great fun and a labor of love. The biggest challenge was not in the synching up of all the various shows. Since this is all run to a precise click track synchronization was fairly easy. The challenge was finding matching choreography from shot to shot while at the same time retaining my shot preference and length as well. I'm sure you'll find a few transitions that reveal such continuity blunders, but I'll bet that there's even more that you don't catch. It's amazing how much did actually work. It's all part of the fun and we hope you enjoy the product of our collaboration.</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>Roger Waters The Wall on Tour 2010
"iShoot, iEdit" (HRV DVD 019)
Filmed at The United Center, Chicago, IL September 20 &amp; 21
Additional footage filmed at The Nassau Coliseum, Long Island, NY October 12 &amp; 13

Format: NTSC DVD (16 x 9 widescreen), 5.1 Dolby Digital Stereo (48kHz)

iShoot: tapehead 2
iEdit: rontoon
iRemaster: MOB
iCheck: Big Ed
iDesign: Christopher for Ediskrad Studios
iHelp: Pinkerton, volcso, selbst93, Robert Perry (additional photopraphy)

Video: Sony HDR-CX520V @ 1920x1080i (AVCHD) &gt; MPEG2 720x480 (16 x 9 widescreen, CBR 8)
Audio: (tapehead2): SP-CMC-8 (AT943s) &gt; SP-SPSB-10 &gt; M10 (24/44.1) &gt; FLAC &gt; WAVE (front left, center, and right speakers)
Audio: (Rick B) Mics: DPA 4022, Recorder: Sound Devices 722 (16/44.1K) &gt; FLAC &gt; WAVE (rear speakers and LFE)</DatosTecnicos>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="59" contador="23">
        <Nombre>The Who - The Kids Are Alright</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>1979</Annus>
        <Imdb-puntaje>7.9/10   1,936 votes</Imdb-puntaje>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>01. My Generation
02. I Can't Explain
03. Russell Harty #1
04. Baba O'Riley
05. Shout and Shimmy
06. Russell Harty #2
07. Young Man Blues
08. Melvin Bragg #1
09. Drum Kit Mayhem
10. The Keith Ringo Knows?
11. Tommy Can You Hear Me?
12. Ringo &amp; Keith: On Roger
13. Pinball Wizard
14. Ummm... Jah
15. See Me, Feel Me
16. Melvin Bragg #2
17. My Generation Conclusion
18. Anyway, Anyhow, Anywhere
19. Russell Harty #3
20. Success Story
21. Pete: On the Beatles
22. Substitute, Pictures of Lily, Magic Bus
23. Happy Jack
24. Melvin Bragg #3
25. A Quick One
26. A Circus Act?
27. Ringo &amp; Keith: Joining the Who
28. Cobwebs and Strange
29. Russell Harty #4
30. Ringo &amp; Keith: On Pete
31. Pete: On Doing His Job
32. Sparks
33. Barbara Ann
34. Roadrunner! My Generation Blues
35. Pete: The Power of Volume
36. Russell Harty #5
37. Who Are You
38. Russell Harty #6
39. My Generation
40. Final Words
41. Won't Get Fooled Again
42. Long Live Rock</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>The Who - The Kids Are Alright 2010 720p BluRay DTS-HD x264-ArcTic
Subtitle: English,spanish,german,french,portuguese</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>1.49</Duracion>
        <Poster>The_Who_The_Kids_Are_Alright .jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="60" contador="29">
        <Nombre>David Gilmour - Remember That Night</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>2006</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>Track listing:

1 - Speak to Me
2 - Breathe
3 - Time
4 - Breathe (Reprise)
5 - Castellorizon
6 - On An Island
7 - The Blue
8 - Red Sky at Night
9 - This Heaven
10 - Then I Close My Eyes
11 - Smile
12 - Take a Breath
13 - A Pocketful of Stones
14 - Where We Start
15 - Shine on You Crazy Diamond
16 - Fat Old Sun
17 - Coming Back To Life
18 - High Hopes
19 - Echoes
20 - Wish You Were Here
21 - Find the Cost of Freedom (featuring David Crosby and Graham Nash)
22 - Arnold Layne (featuring David Bowie)
23 - Comfortably Numb (featuring David Bowie)</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>RELEASE.NAME..: David.Gilmour.Remember.That.Night.2006.720p.BluRay.DTS.x264-ESiR 
RELEASE.DATE..: 07.12.2007 
THEATRE.DATE..: 05.2006
RUNTiME.......: 2:31:24
SiZE..........: 10,9 GB
ViDEO.CODEC...: x264 
FRAMERATE.....: 29.97
BiTRATE.......: 8804kbps 
RESOLUTiON....: 1280x720 
AUDiO.........: English DTS 5.1 1.5mbit
SUBTiTLES.....:
SOURCE........: David Gilmour- Remember That Night - Blu Ray 1080p</DatosTecnicos>
        <Poster>51ZNUjuzXEL.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="61" contador="25">
        <Nombre>George Harrison: Living In The Material World</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>2011</Annus>
        <Imdb-puntaje>8.4/10   741 votes</Imdb-puntaje>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>Director:
Martin Scorsese
Inter-cut with archive material, friends, family and associates of the musician tell the story of his life and how spirituality became such a major part of it</Critica>
        <Problemas>Subtítulos malos</Problemas>
        <DatosTecnicos>George.Harrison.Living.in.the.Material.World.2011.BluRay.720p.x264.DTS-DAViDSK8
General Info Part I
Source: 2011 Blu-ray 1080p AVC DTS-HD 5.1
Container: MKV
Runtime: 1h:34Min
Total Bitrate: 7 590 Kbps
Audio Info
Codec: DTS
Bitrate: 1 510 Kbps
kHz/bit: 48.0 KHz / 16 bits
Channels: 6
Language: English
Subtitles: English (SRT)
Video Info
Codec: x264
Type: 720p
Resolution: 1280x720p
Aspect Ratio: 16:9
Bitrate: 6 079 Kbps
Framerate: 23.976 fps
General Info: Part II
Source: 2011 Blu-ray 1080p AVC DTS-HD 5.1
Container: MKV
Runtime: 1h:54Min
Total Bitrate: 7 518 Kbps
Audio Info
Codec: DTS
Bitrate: 1 510 Kbps
kHz/bit: 48.0 KHz / 16 bits
Channels: 6
Language: English
Subtitles: English (SRT)
Video Info
Codec: x264
Type: 720p
Resolution: 1280x720p
Aspect Ratio: 16:9
Bitrate: 6 009 Kbps
Framerate: 23.976 fps</DatosTecnicos>
        <Poster>george_harrison_living_in_the_material_world.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="62" contador="30">
        <Nombre>The Rolling Stones - Some Girls - Live in Texas 1978</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>2011</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>The Rolling Stones 1978 gira por los EE.UU. en apoyo del album de ese año Same Girls es considerado por los fans como uno de sus mejores. El recorrido siguió de inmediato en el lanzamiento del álbum Some Girls y por el tiempo, la banda llegó a Texas a mediados de julio el álbum había alcanzado el punto N º 1 en las listas de EE.UU.. La gira tuvo un regreso a lo básico enfoque, con la banda y su música muy a la vanguardia y la puesta en escena elaborada poco o nada. Filmado en el Will Rogers Memorial Center en Fort Worth, Texas, el 18 de julio de 1978, este concierto es típico de la gira con los Rolling Stones, la entrega de un rendimiento bruto, enérgica frente a una multitud, que son claramente amante del espectáculo. Muchas de las canciones de Some Girls están incluidos en el set en vivo con una rociada de piedras clásicos de anteriores álbumes. Originalmente filmada en 16 mm, el material ha sido cuidadosamente restaurado y el sonido remezclado y remasterizado por Bob Clearmountain de las cintas multipistas originales. Este es sin lugar a dudas los Rolling Stones en la cima de su forma.
rsz_rolling_stones_some_girls_br_cover_hr.jpg</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>Contenedor: MKV
Fuente video: BluRay AVC 1080i
Fuente Audio: BluRay 
Codec de video: x264
Frames de video: 23,976
Resolucion: 1200x720
Audio 1: DTS 5.1 @1,5Mbps core del DTS-HD MA 5.1 del BD
Tamaño: 4,48 GB</DatosTecnicos>
        <Poster>rsz_rolling_stones_some_girls_br_cover_hr.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="63" contador="24">
        <Nombre>U2 - From the Sky Down</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>2011</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>In the terrain of rock bands, implosion or explosion is seemingly inevitable. U2 has defied the gravitational pull towards destruction; this band has endured and thrived. This documentary asks the question why.</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>CONTENEDOR: MKV 
FUENTE DE VIDEO: BLU-RAY 
CODEC DE VIDEO: x264 
FRAMES DE VIDEO: 23,976 
RESOLUCIÓN DE VIDEO: 1920x1280 
BITRATE DE VIDEO: 10095Kbps
AUDIO 1: Español 
AUDIO 2: Inglés 
SUBTÍTULOS: Español
TAMAÑO: 6,42 GB</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>1.25</Duracion>
        <Poster>u2_From_the_Sky_Down.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="64" contador="26">
        <Nombre>Spinetta - En vivo en el Salón Blanco</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 68</Id>
        <Annus>2005</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>Luis Alberto Spinetta en vivo en el Salón Blanco.
Lista de temas:
01. Viaje y epílogo
02. Era de uranio
03. La herida de París
04. Yo miro tu amor
05. Kamikaze
06. Crisantemo
07. Tonta luz
08. Un niño nace
09. Barro tal vez
10. Pequeño angel
11. Luna nueva (mundo arjo)
12. Durazno sangrando
13. Nelly, no me mientas
14. Agua de la miseria
15. Plegaria para un niño dormido
16. Seguir viviendo sin tu amor
En Extras, las letras de las canciones.</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>Video: 6000kbps
Audio: LPCM 2ch
Norma de Video: NTSC
Formato de Pantalla: Fullscreen
Idioma Audio: Castellano
Subtitulos: No
Menú: SI
Extras: SI</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>1.23</Duracion>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="65" contador="27">
        <Nombre>Spinetta y los socios del desierto - San Cristóforo</Nombre>
        <Id>DVD 69</Id>
        <Annus>1998</Annus>
        <Pais>Argentina</Pais>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>Show grabado el 20 y 21 de Agosto de 1998 en la sala Pablo Picasso del Paseo La Plaza.
INFORMACIÓN ADICIONAL:
Lista de temas
- Estas acá
- Piluso y Coquito
- Como el viento voy a ver
- Me gusta ese tajo
- San Cristoforo
- El rebaño del pastor
- Bosnia
- Ana no duerme
- Sucia estrella
- Rutas argentinas
- Viento del lugar</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>[DVD-R]
 ESPECIFICACIONES:
Video: 100%
Audio: PCM 2.0
Norma de Video: NTSC
Formato de Pantalla: Fullscreen
Idioma Audio: Español
Subtitulos: no
Menú: si
Extras: si</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>1.06</Duracion>
        <Poster>sanCristoforo.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="66" contador="34">
        <Nombre>The Rolling Stones - Gimme Shelter</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>1970</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>El 6 de diciembre de 1969, 300.000 personas se reunieron en Altamont para oír en concierto gratuito a The Rolling Stones, Jefferson Airplane, Tina Turner y The Flying Burrito Brothers, entre otros. Cuatro meses antes había sido Woodstock, el mítico concierto de la generación del amor unidad por la música. Todo indicaba que Altamont estaría a la altura. Pero estuvo a la altura de la tragedia: los Stones, preocupados por la seguridad, encargaron del mantenimiento del orden a miembros de los Ángeles del Infierno. Armados de tacos de billar y cuchillos se emplearon a fondo, golpeando a los espectadores hasta que al final mataron a uno de ellos...</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>Gimme.Shelter.1970.PROPER.720p.Bluray.X264-DIMENSION</DatosTecnicos>
        <Poster>Gimme_Shelter-250680069-large.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="67" contador="33">
        <Nombre>B.B. King -  Live at the Royal Albert Hall</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>2011</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>Blu-Ray pressing. 2012 live release from the King Of The Blues. On June 28, 2011, B.B. King played to an adoring sold-out crowd at London's spectacular Royal Albert Hall. It was another unforgettable night in the career of one of the most legendary bluesmen to ever pick up a guitar. Joining the illustrious Mr. King onstage were guitar virtuoso Derek Trucks, songbird extraordinaire Susan Tedeschi, The Rolling Stones' Ronnie Wood, Simply Red's Mick Hucknall and former Guns N' Roses axeman Slash.</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>format.....mkv
video......1920x1080 @ 10400 Kbps
audio......DTS 5.1 @ 1510 Kbps</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>1.20</Duracion>
        <Poster>bbking.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="68" contador="38">
        <Nombre>Led Zeppelin - The Song Remains the Same+</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>1976</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>Genre: Rock
Duration: 2:17:42
Year: 1976/2007
Directed by: Peter Clifon, Joe Massot
Starring: John Bonham, John Paul Jones, Jimmy Page, Robert Plant
Description: The film has many scenes that include recording concerts at Madison Square Garden, and behind the scenes footage in the Baltimore Civic Centre carried out in the same round, which are interspersed with staged scenes. In the cinematic scenes are displayed episodes of mob attacks and episodes in the style of fantasy.
For Led Zeppelin fanatics, this 1976 feature The Song Remains the Same is a treasure of searing live performances, particularly welcome in light of the sad scarcity of such visual material from the band's great decade. Despite the group's road weariness after a long tour, their final, three-night stand at Madison Square Garden in 1973 was full of the old power. Performances of "No Quarter," "Whole Lotta Love," "Black Dog," "Dazed and Confused," and "Stairway to Heaven" underscore Zep's charisma. Trouble is, you don't get an unbroken performance here. Viewers have to wade through a mishmash of documentary insight into the lives of Robert Plant, Jimmy Page, John Bonham, and John Paul Jones, as well as fantasy sequences supposedly inspired by the thoughts and fantasies of the band's individual members. It's mostly garish and silly, but there are some nice elements, especially insights into the late Bonham's life.
Tracklist
01. Mob Rubout
02. Mob Town Credits
03. Country Life (Autumn Lake)
04. Bron-Yr-Aur
05. Rock and Roll
06. Black Dog
07. Since I've Been Loving You
08. No Quarter
09. Who's Responsible?
10. The Song Remains the Same
11. The Rain Song
12. Fire And Sword
13. Capturing The Castle
14. Not Quite Backstage Pass
15. Dazed And Confused
16. Strung Out
17. Magic In The Night
18. Gate Crasher
19. No Comment
20. Stairway To Heaven
21. Moby Dick
22. Country Squire Bonham
23. Heartbreaker
24. Grand Theft
25. Whole Lotta Love
26. End Credits (w / Stairway to Heaven)
Bonuses
01. Tampa News Report (News Footage Of The Band's Arrival And Concert In Tampa, Florida)
02. Over The Hills And Far Away (Never-before-released Song)
03. Boating Down The Thames (BBC Vintage Interview With Robert Plant And Peter Grant)
04. Celebration Day (Cutting Copy) (Never-before-released Song)
05. The Robbery (Vintage Footage Of The Infamous Drake Hotel Robbery - Interview With Peter Grant)
06. Misty Mountain Hop (Song)
07. The Ocean (Song)
08. Original Film Trailer</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>Quality: BDRip
Container: MKV
Video codec: H.264
Audio Codec: DTS
Video: x264, 1920x1080p, 23.976fps, ~ 9498kbps
Bonus Video: x264, 1920-1392x1088-1080 / 23.976, ~ 8878-3727kbps
Audio: English DTS 5.1 / 48kHz / 1510kbps
Bonus Audio: English AC3 5.1/2.0 / 48kHz / 448/192kbps
Subtitles: English, SRT subtitle format
Head: present</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>2.17 + bonus</Duracion>
        <Poster>image014.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="69" contador="31">
        <Nombre>Nirvana - Live at the Paramount</Nombre>
        <Annus>1991</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>Featuring the following performances: 1 Jesus Doesn't Want Me For A Sunbeam 2 Aneurysm 3 Drain You 4 School 5 Floyd The Barber 6 Smells Like Teen Spirit 7 About A Girl 8 Polly 9 Breed 10 Sliver 11 Love Buzz 12 Lithium 13 Been A Son 14 Negative Creep 15 On A Plain 16 Blew 17 Rape Me 18 Territorial Pissings 19 Endless, Nameless</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>Nirvana.Live.at.the.Paramount.1991.720p.BluRay.x264.DTS-WiKi
ENCODER...................: Island
RELEASE DATE..............: 2011-10-12
RELEASE SIZE..............: 5.45 GiB
SOURCE....................: BluRay
VIDEO CODEC...............: x264: 2pass-L4.1 @ 9445 Kbps
RESOLUTION................: 1232x720
DISPLAY ASPECT RATIO......: 1.71:1
FRAME RATE................: 23.976 fps
AUDiO CODEC...............: English dts @ 1510 Kbps</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>1.11</Duracion>
        <Poster>20111012nlatp1991w.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="70" contador="68">
        <Nombre>Santana - Greatest Hits: Live at Montreux</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>2011</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>Original title: Santana Greatest Hits: Live at Montreux
Released: 2011
Genre: Rock
Description:
With a momentous career stretching back into the sixties, Santana has led the way in introducing initially Latin Rhythms and styles and late influences from worldly cultures into the world of mainstream rock music. Along the way they have collected numerous awards, accrued multi-million album sales and garnered a string of top hit singles. Masterfully filmed in Montreux, Switzerland in July of 2011, this epic show captures the band performing their classic tracks from early hits such as "Jingo," "Evil Ways" and "Black Magic Woman" through to their later No.1 hits "Maria , Maria "and" Smooth. "This is undoubtedly the must-have definitive Santana live concert.
Tracklist:
A. Spark of the Divine
Two. SOCC
Three. Back in Black
4. Singing Winds, Crying Beasts
Five. Black Magic Woman / Gypsy Queen
6. Oye Como Va
7. Maria, Maria
Eight. Foo Foo
9. Corazon Espinado / Guajira
10. Benny and Cindy Solo
11. Jingo
12. Carlos Speaks / Novus
13. Europa (Earth's Cry, Heaven's Smile) / I Want You
14. Batuka / No One to Depend On
15. Duende / Open Invitation
16. Make Somebody Happy / Right On Be Free
17. Evil Ways / A Love Supreme
18. Sunshine of Your Love
19. Smooth / Dame tu Amor
20. Soul Sacrifice / Dennis Drum Solo
21.Samba Pa Ti
22. Into the Night
23. Love, Peace and Happiness / Freedom
Issued: United States | Eagle Rock Entertainment</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>MKV
1280x720 at 23.976 fps, x264 (L4.1, crf), ~6243 kbps avg
English: 48 kHz, DTS, 3/2 (L,C,R,l,r) + LFE ch, ~1536.00 kbps avg
English: 48 kHz, LPCM, 2/0 (L,R) ch, ~1536.00 kbps avg</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>2.47</Duracion>
        <Poster>1330839339_santana.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="71" contador="35">
        <Nombre>Dire Straits - Alchemy Live</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>1983</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>Técnica:	Dire Straits Alchemy Live
Plot:
British pub band turned internationally famous rock stars Dire Straits are featured doing several different live performances on ALCHEMY. Live footage the band performing many of their most popular hits, including "Sultans of Swing," is included.
Tracklist:
1. Intro (Saturday Night at the Movies)
2. Once Upon a Time in the West
3. Expresso Love
4. Romeo &amp; Juliet
5. Private Investigations
6. Sultans of Swing
7. Two Young Lovers
8. Tunnel of Love
9. Telegraph Road
10. Solid Rock
11. Going Home - Theme from 'Local Hero'
Dire.Straits.Alchemy.Live.(1983).720p.Blu-ray.PCM.x264-HDCLUB</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>SIZE...........: 7.03 GIB
VIDEO CODEC....: x264
RESOLUTION.....: 1280x720
BITRATE........: 5 040 Mbps
FRAMERATE......: 29.970 fps
AUDIO..........: English DTS 5.1 1 510 Kbps, English PCM 2.0
SUBTITLES......: None
SOURCE.........: Blu-ray</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>1.30</Duracion>
        <Poster>d5fc0f13432cfb9fd3ae2195c490fe1bf4995bff.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="72" contador="32">
        <Nombre>Madonna - Sticky And Sweet Tou</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>2010</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>The show will include many of the Material Girl's hits from the course of her career including, "4 Minutes," "Like a Prayer," "Hung Up" and "Ray of Light". Filmed in Buenos Aires, over four days to a crowd exceeding 256,000 fans, the concert also includes a show-stopping moment when Madonna performs a historic "Don't Cry For Me Argentina" to a thunderous audience response from her Argentine fans. Also included are several hits from the multi-Grammy winner's most recent CD Hard Candy, which debuted at No. 1 in 37 countries. Special features include 30 minutes of behind-the-scenes footage.
CANCIONES:
1. The Sweet Machine (Intro)
2. Candy Shop
3. Beat Goes On
4. Human Nature
5. Vogue
6. Die Another Day (Remix) (Interlude)
7. Into the Groove
8. Heartbeat
9. Borderline
10. She's Not Me
11. Music
12. Rain" (Remix) (Interlude)
13. Devil Wouldn't Recognize You
14. Spanish Lesson
15. Miles Away
16. La Isla Bonita
17. Doli Doli
18. You Must Love Me/Don't Cry for Me Argentina
19. Get Stupid (Interlude)
20. 4 Minutes
21. Like a Prayer
22. Ray of Light
23. Hung Up
24. Give It 2 Me</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>Release Date ...... :2010/03/31 
Video Bitrate ..... :X264 8494K 
Audio Bitrate ......:DTS 1536K 
Language ...........:English 
Substitle...........:N/A 
Resolution .........:1920 x1080</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>2.05</Duracion>
        <Poster>madonnastickyandsweettoq.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="73" contador="36">
        <Nombre>Peter Gabriel - New Blood - Live in London</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>2011</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>CANCIONES:
Intruder
Wallflower
The Boy In The Bubble
Apres Moi
The Drop
Washing Of The Water (2D disc only)
The Book Of Love
Darkness
The Power Of The Heart
Biko
San Jacinto
Digging In The Dirt
Signal To Noise
Downside Up
Mercy Street
The Rhythm Of The Heat
Blood Of Eden
Red Rain
Solsbury Hill
In Your Eyes
Don't Give Up
The Nest That Sailed The Sky</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>CONTENEDOR: MKV 
FUENTE DE VIDEO: BLU-RAY 
CODEC DE VIDEO: x264 
FRAMES DE VIDEO: 23,976 
RESOLUCIÓN DE VIDEO: 1280x720 
BITRATE DE VIDEO: 6 000 Kbps
AUDIO 1: DTS 5.1 1536 Kbps Inglés 
TAMAÑO: 6,81 GB</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>2.09</Duracion>
        <Poster>petergabriel.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="74" contador="39">
        <Nombre>Bob Marley - Live In Concert in Germany</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>1981</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>01 // Trenchtown Rock
02 // Them Belly Full
03 // I Shot The Sheriff
04 // Rebel Music
05 // Lively Up Yourself                
06 // Crazy Baldhead/ Running Away            
07 // War/No More Trouble                       
08 // The Heathen
09 // No Woman, No Cry
10 // Jamming
11 // Get Up, Stand Up!
12 // Exodus</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>Bob.Marley.Live.in.Concert.2012.1080p.MBluRay.x264-LOUNGE
rLS......04/07/2012
sTORE....02/04/2012
fORMAT...iso
viDEO....1294x1054 @ 13300 @ 25.000
aUDiO....ac3 5.1 @ 448
siZE.....72x100mb (7045379605)
lENGTH...62min
sOURCE...bluray</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>1.06</Duracion>
        <Poster>aY8rM.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="75" contador="37">
        <Nombre>Jimi Hendrix  - Voodoo Child</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>2012</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>PLOT:
TWO HOUR DOCUMENTARY FEATURING THE LEGENDARY GUITARIST'S STORY IN HIS OWN WORDS WITH EXCLUSIVE INTERVIEWS AND RECORDINGS FROM THE HENDRIX PRIVATE ARCHIVE
Over the course of just four extraordinary years, Jimi Hendrix left an indelible stamp on the world, shaping not only popular music but popular culture as well. He remains the most innovative musician of his, or any other, era having virtually reshaped the vocabulary of the electric guitar for future generations. "Jimi Hendrix Voodoo Child" is an autobiographical journey that reveals the man as never before, featuring the legendary musician's own words to tell the story of his remarkable life.
Drawing upon interviews granted by Hendrix, coupled with letters, writings and recordings, "Jimi Hendrix Voodoo Child" provides new insight into one of the most enduring icons of popular culture. The special is filled with never before seen photographs and film footage from the Hendrix family archive and features a soundtrack that includes such legendary Hendrix recordings as "Purple Haze," "Hey Joe," "Fire," "Voodoo Child (Slight Return)" together with never before heard live performances. Funk legend and Rock and Roll Hall of Fame member Bootsy Collins of Parliament-Funkadelic renown, is featured as the voice of Jimi Hendrix.</Critica>
        <Problemas>Jimi.Hendrix.Voodoo.Child.2012.1080p.BluRay.x264-MOOVEE
REGION: A
AUDIO: English AC3
VIDEO: 8078
RESOLUTION: 1920x1080</Problemas>
        <DatosTecnicos>FILENAME       : moovee-jimi.hendrix.vood.child.720
FORMAT         : Matroska
DURATION       : 3.28 GiB for 1h 31mn 44s 896ms
VIDEO          : AVC at 4 665 Kbps
ASPECT         : 1280 x 720 (1.77 at 29.970 fps
AUDIO #0       : AC3 at 448 Kbps
CHANNELS       : 2 channels, 48.0 KHz
LANGUAGE       : English
SUBTITLES      : English</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>1.31</Duracion>
        <Poster>26595b1134.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="76" contador="45">
        <Nombre>Jimi Hendrix - Jimi Plays Berkeley 1970</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>2012</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>Derivado de un par de conciertos en el Teatro de Berkeley (California) de la Comunidad el 30 de Mayo de 1970, Jimi Plays Berkeley está aquí para la primera vez en Blu-ray como una nueva transferencia, restaurada digitalmente en alta definición presentada por el negativo 16 mm original. Jimi Plays Berkeley de vídeo Jimi Plays Berkeley ahora cuenta con casi 20 minutos de material inédito, incluyendo presentaciones recientemente descubiertas de las obras clásicas tales como "Hear My Train A Comin '" y "Voodoo Child (Slight Return)", junto con el contenido documental de que no se ve la versión original . Una nueva presentación característica especial incluye una entrevista con Abe Jacob, ingeniero de Hendrix por carretera, las dos interpretaciones legendarias y un quinto disco Una banda sonora envolvente para el programa de actuación toda la segunda (mezcla original de Jimi Hendrix, el ingeniero Eddie Kramer), que son un montón de canciones como "Hey Joe" y "Stone Free" no se ve en la película. El nuevo video incluye un ensayo detallado y muchas fotos inéditas.
Este despertar de fama mundial de conciertos es por los críticos como una de las mejores actuaciones de Jimi Hendrix jamás ser. Entre las imágenes de dos actuaciones independientes en el Teatro Comunitario de Berkeley 30a 05 1970 para ayudar a estas bombas incendiarias espectáculos cuentan con las revueltas estudiantiles en Berkeley, por el material en el impresionante telón de fondo de algunos impresionante material de Hendrix. Canciones como "Purple Haze", "Voodoo Child (Slight Return)", "Star Spangled Banner", "Hey Joe", y muchos otros. Esta es una experiencia que nunca se olvida musical que podrán disfrutar de una y otra vez.
Filmado 30a Mayo 1970 en el Centro Comunitario de Berkeley, California.
Actuación en directo.
Tracks:
01. Pass It On (Straight Ahead)
02. Hey Baby (New Rising Sun)
03. Lover Man
04. Stone Free
05. Hey Joe
06. I Don't Live Today
07. Machine Gun
08. Foxy Lady
09. Star Spangled Banner
10. Purple Haze
11. Voodoo Child (Slight Return)
Este Blu-ray se obtienen a partir del negativo original de 16 mm. Aunque la imagen no puede ser muy bueno como se ve en las capturas de pantalla, discos como este son ideales para la calidad del sonido.</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>Quality: BDRip 1080p
Video codec: MPEG-4 AVC
Audio Codec: DTS
Video: 1440x1080 / 4:3 / 23,976 fps / ~ 7934 Kbps
Audio: English DTS 5.1 / 48 kHz / 1510 kbps / 24 bits</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>1.04</Duracion>
        <Poster>45087_front.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="77" contador="40">
        <Nombre>Bob Marley - Marley (Documental)</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>2012</Annus>
        <Imdb-puntaje>7.9/10   2,016 votes</Imdb-puntaje>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <DatosTecnicos>BITRATE &lt; 9290 Kbps
VIDEO RESOLUTION &lt; 1920x1080
ASPECT &lt; 16:9
FORMAT &lt; DTS
AUDIO BITRATE &lt; 1509 kbps
LANGUAGE &lt; ENGLISH
SUBTITLES &lt; ENGLISH, SPANISH</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>2.25</Duracion>
        <Poster>posterqbm.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="78" contador="43">
        <Nombre>Elvis Presley - Elvis on Tour</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>1972</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>TÍTULO ORIGINAL: Elvis on Tour
AÑO: 1972
PAÍS:   Estados Unidos
DIRECTOR: Pierre Adidge, Robert Abel
GUIÓN: Pierre Adidge, Robert Abel
MÚSICA: Elvis Presley
FOTOGRAFÍA: Robert E. Thomas
REPARTO: Documentary, Elvis Presley
Crónica de un tour que el ya legendario Elvis Presley (1935-1977) realizó por Norteamérica en abril de 1972. Se ofrecen algunos de sus grandes éxitos y una semblanza personal del hombre que había tras el mito. "La historia de Elvis", que aparece al final, fue un trabajo supervisado por Martin Scorsese.</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>CONTENEDOR: MKV
FUENTE DE VIDEO: BLU-RAY
CODEC DE VIDEO: x264
FRAMES DE VIDEO: 23,976
RESOLUCIÓN DE VIDEO: 1280x534
BITRATE DE VIDEO: 5 208 Kbps
AUDIO 1: DTS 1536 Kbps Inglés
SUBTÍTULOS: Español, Inglés
TAMAÑO: 4,37 GB</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>1.33</Duracion>
        <Poster>elvisontour.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="79" contador="42">
        <Nombre>Pink Floyd - The Story of Wish You Where Here</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>2012</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>Interesante, interesante. Y más para los que tienen a &#x201c;Wish you were here&#x201d;, como la obra cumbre de Pink Floyd, como es mi caso.
En efecto, el sello Eagle rock pone en el mercado este atractivo BluRay que repasa la historia de una de las obras definitivas de la historia del rock. Noventa minutos de documental que contará con entrevistas exclusivas e inéditas de tres de sus miembros vivos como son Roger Waters, David Gilmour y Nick Mason, e incluso material de archivo del fallecido Richard Wright.
En este documento audio-visual no faltarán: la aportación de Roy Harper, que puso su voz en la excelente &#x201c;Have a cigar&#x201d;; el ingeniero de sonido Brian Humphries, que nos contará el laborioso desarrollo de las canciones en el mítico Abbey Road Studios, y por supuesto, Storm Thorgerson, diseñador gráfico de Hipgnosis, que creó innumerable portadas innovadoras en el mundo del rock y muy principalmente en la carrera de Pink Floyd. La cinta también abarcará la inesperada visita de Syd Barrett en el estudio y la decisión de dividir finalmente &#x201c;Shine on your crazy diamond&#x201d; en dos partes.
Un BluRay imprescindible para los más devotos seguidores de &#x201c;Wish you were here&#x201d; y entender un poco mejor la compleja y dificultosa gestación de esta obra irrepetible, que sigue teniendo una fuerza poderosa e única cada vez que lo ponemos en nuestro tocadiscos.
Eagle Rock Entertainment ha anunciado que el 26 de junio será el lanzamiento simultáneo en formato DVD y Blue-ray de &#x201c;PINK FLOYD - La historia de Wish You Were Here&#x201d;. Es la historia autorizada del álbum hecho con la plena participación y aprobación de los miembros de Pink Floyd.
Según indica la nota de prensa que lo publicita Wish You Were Here, publicado en septiembre de 1975, fue el álbum siguiente del mundialmente exitoso &#x201c;The Dark Side Of The Moon&#x201d; y es citado por muchos fans, así como miembros de la banda Richard Wright y David Gilmour, como su álbum favorito de Pink Floyd. El lanzamiento se fue directo al # 1 en el Reino Unido y los EE.UU. y encabezó las listas en muchos otros países alrededor del mundo
Este vídeo narra la historia de la realización de este histórico acontecimiento, a través de nuevas entrevistas con Roger Waters, David Gilmour y Nick Mason y entrevistas de archivo con el fallecido Richard Wright. También se destacan la participación del diseñador Storm Thorgerson, del vocalista invitado Roy Harpe y otros involucrados en la creación del álbum. Además, el ingeniero de la grabación original, Brian Humphries, revisa las cintas maestras en los estudios Abbey Road para ilustrar aspectos de la construcción de las canciones
Los miembros de la banda discuten los temas del álbum, como el de la ausencia, la codicia de la industria musical y la presencia del ex miembro de la banda Syd Barrett, quien recordado en 'Shine On You Crazy Diamond', que abre y cierra el álbum. El vídeo incluye también la inesperada visita de Barrett, la tensión en Abbey Road durante la grabación, las dificultades de las primeras sesiones de grabación y de cómo la decisión de dividir 'Shine On You Crazy Diamond' en dos secciones fue el catalizador para la finalización con éxito del álbum
Los estrenos en DVD y Blu-ray contiene material adicional que no aparece en la versión que se transmitió por la televisión, incluyendo nuevas entrevistas con Roger Waters, David Gilmour y Nick Mason
Como se ve, parece ser un material indispensable para los seguidores de Pink Floyd.</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>CONTENEDOR: MKV
FUENTE DE VIDEO: BLU-RAY
CODEC DE VIDEO: x264
FRAMES DE VIDEO: 23,976
RESOLUCIÓN DE VIDEO: 720p
BITRATE DE VIDEO: 3.000 kbps
AUDIO: Ingles DTS 5.1@755 kbps
SUBTÍTULOS: Español, Inglés
TAMAÑO: 1,67 GB[/center]
EXTRA: Previously unseen on TV
CONTENEDOR: MKV
FUENTE DE VIDEO: BLU-RAY
CODEC DE VIDEO: x264
FRAMES DE VIDEO: 23,976
RESOLUCIÓN DE VIDEO: 720p
BITRATE DE VIDEO: 2.800 kbps
AUDIO: Ingles AC 2.0@640 kbps
SUBTÍTULOS: Español, Inglés
TAMAÑO:  657MB</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>1 + 0.26</Duracion>
        <Poster>sinttulo1bnt.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="80" contador="44">
        <Nombre>The Rolling Stones - Live At The Max</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>1991</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>1. Continental Drift
2. Start Me Up
3. Sad Sad Sad
4. Tumbling Dice
5. Ruby Tuesday
6. Rock And A Hard Place
7. Honky Tonk Woman
8. You Can't Always Get What You Want
9. Happy
10. Paint It Black
11. 2,000 Light Years From Home
12. Sympathy For The Devil
13. Street Fighting Man
14. It's Only Rock 'N' Roll
15. Brown Sugar
16. (I Can't Get No) Satisfaction
Bonus Material:
17. Behind The Scenes</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>CONTENEDOR:     MKV
FUENTE DE VIDEO:   Bluray
CODEC DE VIDEO:     x264
FRAMES DE VIDEO:   23.976  fps
RESOLUCION DE VIDEO:   720p (1280 x 720)
BITRATE DE VIDEO:   5 738Kbps
 AUDIO 1 :   DTS 1536 kbps
 TAMAÑO: 4&#x2019;38  GB</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>1.24</Duracion>
        <Poster>rollingstonesliveatthem.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="81" contador="64">
        <Nombre>Queen - Hungarian Rhapsody - Live In Budapest</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>1987</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>Tracklisting:
01. One Vision
02. Tie Your Mother Down
03. In the Lap of the Gods. . .Revisited
04. Seven Seas of Rhye
05. Tear It Up
06. A Kind of Magic
07. Under Pressure
08. Who Wants to Live Forever
09. I Want to Break Free
10. Guitar Solo
11. Now I'm Here
12. Love of My Life
13. Tavaszi Szet Vizet Araszt
14. Is This the World We Created. . .?
15. Tutti Frutti
16. Bohemian Rhapsody
17. Hammer to Fall
18. Crazy Little Thing Called Love
19. Radio Ga Ga
20. We Will Rock You
21. Friends Will Be Friends
22. We Are the Champions
23. God Save the Queen
Reviewed by Jeffrey Kauffman, November 5, 2012
Bohemian has become such a commonplace adjective that people have perhaps grown unaccustomed to associating it with the actual place called Bohemia, which is where one would assume the descriptive term probably originated. The nation previously known as Czechoslovokia was home to Bohemia, and while the vagaries of history have now but Slovakia in between the Czech Republic and Hungary, when Freddie Mercury and Queen played Budapest in 1986, Bohemia was in a certain sense "right next door" and perhaps provided an added allure to including this odd venue on Queen's world tour. It's hard to even imagine it now, but the Iron Curtain was still very much vertical and seemingly impenetrable, and a stadium rock performance was not a de rigeur situation even for the biggest bands. As the liner notes to this new Blu-ray and double CD release state, the band knew going in they weren't going to make much if any money from this performance, and yet they jumped at the chance, if for no other reason than that Hungary had long been "off limits" for rock concerts.
There was obviously a pent up audience for Queen, for once their concert was announced, it sold out in an astoundingly short amount of time, all the more astounding when one considers the fact that this particular concert was played before literally tens of thousands of people. This was the first stadium rock concert by a western act to be performed behind the Iron Curtain, and it was big news in its day. A coterie of British journalists flew to Budapest to cover the proceedings (some of which is captured in some non-concert footage included in this documentary), and because this was such an obviously big deal within Hungary itself, famed Hungarian cinematographer János Zsombolyai was hired to film the concert, and to do so he had to utilize every available film camera in the nation.</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>Queen Hungarian Rhapsody - Live In Budapest (1986) [Bluray 720p x264 DTS 5.1 Subt][GrupoHDS].mkv
CONTENEDOR: MKV 
FUENTE DE VIDEO: BLU-RAY 
CODEC DE VIDEO: x264 
FRAMES DE VIDEO: 24 
RESOLUCIÓN DE VIDEO: 1280x720 
BITRATE DE VIDEO: 12.7 Mbps 
AUDIO 1:DTS 5.1 1536 Kbps
SUBTÍTULOS: PGS Español, Inglés 
TAMAÑO: 9,27 GB</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>1.31</Duracion>
        <Poster>56083_front.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="82" contador="47">
        <Nombre>Serrat &amp; Sabina - Dos Pájaros de un tiro</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>2007</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>Después de su extenso tour por España y Latinoamérica, Serrat y Sabina nos ofrecen 'Dos pájaros de un tiro', una completa muestra de lo que ha sido su gira. Tanto los que tuvieron la suerte de verlos juntos en directo, como los que no fueron tan afortunados, ésta es una buena oportunidad de recrearse con una unión inéditaye, repetible con "Dos pájaros contraatacan".
INFORMACIÓN ADICIONAL:
Lista de temas:
01. Ocupen su localidad/ Hoy puede ser un gran día
02. Aves de paso
03. Pueblo blanco
04. Algo personal
05. Y sin embargo
06. No hago otra cosa que pensar en ti
07. Quien me ha robado el mes de abril
08. Princesa
09. Contigo
10. Tu nombre me sabe a yerba
11. A la orilla de la chimenea
12. Señora
13. Aquellas pequeñas cosas/ Ruido/ El muerto vivo
14. Es caprichoso el azar
15. Fa vint anys que tinc vint anys
16. Poema de amo
17. Pacto entre caballeros
18. Noche de bodas
19. Mediterráneo
20. 19 días y 500 noches
21. Penélope
22. Más de cien mentiras
23. Fiesta
24. Pastillas para no soñar
25. Cantares/ Y nos dieron las 10
26. Despedida
27. Paraules d'amor
28. Lucía/ La del pirata cojo
29. Calle melancolía
30. Que se llama soledad/ Para la libertad</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>Resolución: 1280x720
Formato: BDrip
Codec Video: WMV3
Codec Audio: WMA
Bitrate Video: 7000Kbps
Bitrate Audio: 640Kbps</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>2.25</Duracion>
        <Poster>8mJ2y.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="83" contador="49">
        <Nombre>The Rolling Stones - Live One More Shot</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>2012</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>Duración: 2 hs. 35 min.
SETLIST
"Sympathy for the Devil" (by marching band, Stones not on stage yet)
"Get Off of My Cloud"
"The Last Time"
"It's Only Rock 'n' Roll (But I Like It)"
"Paint It Black"
"Gimme Shelter"
"Respectable" (with John Mayer)
"Wild Horses"
"Around and Around"
"Doom and Gloom"
"One More Shot"
"Miss You"
"Honky Tonk Women"
"Before They Make Me Run"
"Happy"
"Midnight Rambler" (with Mick Taylor)
"Start Me Up"
"Tumbling Dice"
"Brown Sugar"
"Sympathy for the Devil"
Encores:
"You Can't Always Get What You Want"
"Jumpin' Jack Flash"
"(I Can't Get No) Satisfaction"</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>Resolución: 1280 x 720
Formato: SAT TV Rip
Codec Video: x264
Codec Audio: AC3
Bitrate Video: 4887 kbps
Bitrate Audio: 384 kbps</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>2.35</Duracion>
        <Poster>HPCGR.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="84" contador="48">
        <Nombre>The Rolling Stones - The Stones in the Park</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>1969</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>July 5, 1969 is one of the most historic days in rock and roll. The Stones concert in London's Hyde Park would pay homage to the late Brian Jones and usher in the new and extraordinary era of Mick Taylor (1969-74).
For those that have looked to fault every possible second of the event and judge the release on only the musical portion and not include "The Event" it is only right equal time is given to counter the unneccesary critisism the gig received.
The typical complaint about any music DVD not recorded with a 34 billion dollar budget to the sound snob is the fidelity doesn't meet the quality standard. In 1969 you were not dealing with digital technology and preserving the moment is worth more stars than how the mix is.
It has been discussed that newcomer Mick Taylor looks nervous. That is earth shattering news. He had less than 48 hours notice the permits were in place and they could perform. If your first show was in front of over 100,000 people and your bandmates lost somebody that they had often spent more time with than their own families, if there weren't butterflies he wouldn't have a heart or soul.
Keith's guitar is out of tune during "Satisfaction." There is a first. No musician has ever had this before. It is amazing that any of the Stones could get through the day knowing Brian's departure is now in a permanent sense.
The band isn't inspired. Then why did they play the longest version of "Sympathy For The Devil" (19:00) ever performed? If you look at the complete list of songs regardless if they are included or not, they could have easily made the show a hit factory. There are a myriad of tunes that only a hardcore Stones aficionado would be able to name correctly.
The only knock that is justifable (Surprisingly it is the one thing the Skeptic's hadn't been thrilled to inform every Amazon review reader) the playing time of the DVD does not encompass the entire set. I have listed the songs and next to the ones that aren't found on the DVD will be the letters NF (Not Found).
To Brian Jones thank you for your incredible contribution to the Stones and to Mick Taylor there wasn't a better man for the job.
1 EULOGY FOR BRIAN 2:42
2 I'M YOURS SHE'S MINE 2:12
3 JUMPING JACK FLASH 3:10
4 NO EXPECTATIONS 3:42 NF
5 MERCY, MERCY 3:13 NF
6 STRAY CAT BLUES 3:43 NF
7 I'M FREE 2:25 NF
8 DOWN HOME GIRL 5:22 NF
9 LOVE IN VAIN 4:39
10 LOVING CUP 5:38 NF
11 MIDNIGHT RAMBLER 8:09
12 SATISFACTION 4:24
13 HONKY TONK WOMEN 3:40
14 STREET FIGHTING MAN 3:42 NF
15 SYMPATHY FOR THE DEVIL 19:01
Enjoy the music and be well,
Craig Fenton</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>General           : The.Rolling.Stones.The.Stones.In.The.Park.1969.720p.MBluRay.x264\rolling.stones.in.the.park.720p.mkv
Format            : Matroska at 10.3 Mbps
Length            : 4.01 GiB for 55mn 43s 632ms
Video #0          : AVC at 9 449 Kbps
Aspect            : 960 x 720 (1.333) at 23.976 fps
Audio #0          : AC-3 at 640 Kbps
Infos             : 2 channels, 48.0 KHz</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>0.55</Duracion>
        <Poster>44968_front.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="85" contador="58">
        <Nombre>The Rolling Stones - Crossfire Hurricane</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>2012</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>The Rolling Stones: Crossfire Hurricane is presented on Blu-ray courtesy of Eagle Rock Entertainment with an AVC encoded 1080p transfer in 1.78:1. This documentary culled together from hugely disparate sources, including some with formats as small as 8mm. Therefore, it's important not to expect a uniform video quality throughout this offering. Some of the footage, notably some of the contemporary establishing shots of various locations, looks excellently sharp, and appears to have been shot digitally. The bulk of this enterprise is cobbled together from old films and television appearances, however. Those pieces are widely variant in quality. Some of the concert footage is decent enough looking, while some of the television outings are pretty ragged looking. Though this is a progressive presentation, it's obvious that some of the source material was originally interlaced, as there are noticeable combing artifacts during fast motion.
The Rolling Stones: Crossfire Hurricane features a lossless DTS-HD Master Audio 5.1 mix as well as an LPCM 2.0 stereo mix. While some of the audio here obviously had multitrack masters that were ported over into a 5.1 rendering, it's just as obvious that many did not and have been artificially repurposed for surround sound. For that reason, I actually preferred the LPCM 2.0 mix. For me personally, this offered a much clearer, more focused audio presentation that I found generally more pleasurable. There's nothing horribly wrong with the 5.1 mix, but it often sounds hazy and too widely disbursed for my personal taste. Fidelity is quite good, especially considering the wide variety of source audio. The contemporary interviews of course sound clear as a bell.</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>The Rolling Stones Crossfire Hurricane Mkv 720p Dts Hd
Format : Matroska
Format version : Version 2
File size : 4.83 GiB
Duration : 1h 50mn
Overall bit rate mode : Variable</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>1.51</Duracion>
        <Poster>67651_front.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="86" contador="60">
        <Nombre>Jeff Beck - Performing This Week: Live at Ronnie Scott's</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>2009</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>1) Beck's Bolero
2) Eternity's Breath
3) Stratus
4) Cause We've Ended As Lovers
5) Behind The Veil
6) You Never Know
7) Nadia
8) Blast From The East
9) Led Boots
10) Angel (Footsteps)
11) People Get Ready - with JOSS STONE
12) Scatterbrain
13) Goodbye Pork Pie Hat / Brush With The Blues
14) Space Boogie
15) Blanket - with IMOGEN HEAP
16) Big Block
17) A Day In The Life
18) Little Brown Bird - with ERIC CLAPTON
19) You Need Love - with ERIC CLAPTON
20) Rollin' And Tumblin' - with IMOGEN HEAP
21) Where Were You</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>CONTENEDOR: .... MKV
FUENTE DE VIDEO: ....  Blu-ray
CODEC DE VIDEO:.... x264
FRAMES DE VIDEO: .... 25.000 fps
RESOLUCION DE VIDEO: .... 720p ( 1280*720 )
BITRATE DE VIDEO: .... 7846 Kbps
AUDIO :  
5.1 / DTS / 1 509 Kbps
TAMAÑO 6.56 GiB</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>1.40</Duracion>
        <Poster>OXn3PwD.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="87" contador="51">
        <Nombre>Divididos - Audio y agua</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>2011</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>SINOPSIS:
DIVIDIDOS presenta AUDIO Y AGUA, ahora en formato Blu-Ray. El monumental registro audiovisual, con sonido 5.1 y una decisión de planos e imágenes que permiten sentir su demoledora y emocionante actuación
La más novedosa tecnología de filmación acompaña la interpretación en vivo de las 26 canciones que integran este doble BLU-RAY y doble CD de audio junto a un libro de fotografías, dibujos e información que completan una edición totalmente irresistible, complementaria al lanzamiento que ya hicieron del vinilo y siguiendo la entera dedicación a su obra.
Grabado en vivo el 2 y 3 de junio de 2010 en el Luna Park, AUDIO Y AGUA es el documento de las presentaciones de AMAPOLA DEL 66. Con una puesta deslumbrante, el escenario con la whipala y el molino real, 16 invitados especiales, los primeros planos del público, el trabajo de luces y proyecciones dan un marco conmovedor. Este primer DVD del Power Trío, aquí también apreciado en su perfil más folklórico, trae además una serie de extras que ilustran los momentos previos y posteriores al concierto, y material que a modo de guiño con sus seguidores, han querido compartir en este formato de colección, del cual se ha visto un anticipo en su página web, territorio de novedades directas y sorpresivas.
Lista de canciones AUDIO Y AGUA. DIVIDIDOS: EL ARRIERO / HOMBRE EN U / BUSCANDO UN ANGEL / MANTECOSO / MUERTO A LABURAR / VIENTITO DEL TUCUMÁN / PAR MIL / AVANZANDO RETROCEDEN / LA FLOR AZUL / QUE VES? / GUANUQUEANDO / BOYAR NOCTURNO / SENDEROS / JUJUY / CRISTÓFORO CACARNÚ / CAMINANDO / MAÑANA EN EL ABASTO / TODOS / PERRO FUNK / SUCIO Y DESPROLIJO / RASPUTÍN / EL 38 / ALA DELTA / WITH A LITTLE HELP FROM MY FRIENDS / AMAPOLA DEL 66 / NEXT WEEK.</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>Resolución: 1920*1080
Formato: BluRay Rip
Codec Video: x264
Codec Audio: AC3
Bitrate Video: ~8000 kbps
Bitrate Audio: 640 kbps
[DATOS:
Idioma: Español
Fecha de Rippeo: 2013
Ripper: QEN</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>1.31 + 1.14</Duracion>
        <Poster>6e1aj468.png</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="88" contador="62">
        <Nombre>Jimi Hendrix - Live at Woodstock</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>1969</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <DatosTecnicos>video: [x264] 1022x720 crf=22
audio 1: [flac] 5.1 channels
audio 2: [dts] 1.5mbit
General
CompleteName                      Jimi.Hendrix.Live.at.Woodstock.720p.BluRay.FLAC.DTS.x264-quaz.mkv
Format                            Matroska
FileSize                          8.57 GiB</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>1.38</Duracion>
        <Poster>yX6cbEIV.jpeg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="89" contador="67">
        <Nombre>The Rolling Stones - Sweet Summer Sun: Hyde Park Live</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>2013</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <DatosTecnicos>Filename.......: lqd-rollingstonessss720p
Container......: Matroska
Duration.......: 1h 57mn 50s 16ms
Size...........: 4.37 GiB
&#x66d;Video Details&#x66d;
Codec..........: AVC High@L4.1 8 bits
Type...........: Progressive
Resolution.....: 1280x544
Aspect ratio...: 2.353:1
Bit rate.......: 4 547 Kbps
Frame rate.....: 29.970 fps
&#x66d;Audio Details&#x66d;
Format.........: DTS  
Channels.......: 6 channels
Bit rate.......: 755 Kbps
Language.......: English</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>1.57</Duracion>
        <Poster>w4b51fuo.png</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="90" contador="57">
        <Nombre>The Doors -  R-Evolution</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>2013</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>Combining early TV appearances with their own music films, it illustrates how The Doors evolved from the constraints of late sixties television to a point where they had the creative input and power to shape how they were portrayed on screen. Throughout the unique charisma and talent of The Doors comes across, whether it be on a lightweight pop show or on a film created from their own imaginations, along with some of the most influential music ever made.</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>AUDIO..........: DTS 5.1 (768)                    
NAMED..........: lqd-thedoorsrevo720pp.mkv     
SUBS...........: en es fr</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>1.17</Duracion>
        <Poster>1a62850431f2fb0d10a25c53a464da0d.jpeg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="91" contador="55">
        <Nombre>Lour Reed - Berlin</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>2007</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>Plot: Lou Reed's 2006 live concert performance of his 1973 concept album "Berlin", filmed over five nights at St. Ann's Warehouse in Brooklyn, New York.
Cast:
Lou Reed as Himself
Fernando Saunders as Himself
Sharon Jones as Herself
Antony Hegarty as Himself (as Antony)
Brooklyn Youth Chorus as Themselves
Steve Hunter as Himself 
How do you adapt a record once described as "the most depressing album of all time" into a multi-media stage performance? Rather well, when it comes to Lou Reed?s Berlin. The former Velvet Underground mainstay was already established as a solo artist, buoyed by the hit "Walk on the Wild Side," when he released the Berlin recording in 1973. That it was not a commercial success, to say the least, is unsurprising, given its relentlessly grim lyric content and music that, while often very appealing, is hardly the stuff that Top Ten dreams are made of. Still, it made sense when Reed revived the work some 35 years later for a single world tour and concert DVD. Working with film director Julian Schnabel (The Diving Bell and the Butterfly), Reed brings a quiet power to his weary tale of hopeless junkies Caroline and Jim, whose lives, already bound for the gutter when the performance begins, completely bottom out little over an hour later (the 81-minute DVD includes a few encores, notably the Velvet Underground classic "Sweet Jane. The songs, played by a standard rock band but with subtle touches of horns, strings, and choir (Antony Hegarty of Antony and the Johnsons adds vocals as well), are for the most part strikingly prosaic; Reed has never been much of a singer, and his words are anything but flowery, closer to prose than verse (many lines, like "All of her friends call her Alaska when she takes speed," are more spoken than sung). Schnabel does a superb job matching the downbeat mood, relying primarily on the use of low, filtered lighting and film (in which Caroline is portrayed by Emmanuelle Seigner). Not for everyone, certainly, but Berlin is a work to be admired.</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>Format : Matroska
Format version : Version 2
File size : 5.18 GiB
Duration : 1h 20mn
Overall bit rate mode : Variable
Overall bit rate : 9 163 Kbps
Movie name : LOU REED'S BERLIN.Title0.BlurayRip
Encoded date : UTC 2013-06-07 10:46:59
Writing library : libebml v0.7.8 + libmatroska v0.8.1
VIDEO INFO
Format : AVC
Format/Info : Advanced Video Codec
Format profile : High@L4.1
Format settings, CABAC : Yes
Format settings, ReFrames : 2 frames
Codec ID : V_MPEG4/ISO/AVC
Duration : 1h 20mn
Width : 1 920 pixels
Height : 1 018 pixels
Display aspect ratio : 1.886
Frame rate mode : Constant
Frame rate : 23.976 fps
Color space : YUV
Chroma subsampling : 4:2:0
Bit depth : 8 bits
Scan type : Progressive
Writing library : x264 core
Default : Yes
Forced : No
Color primaries : BT.709
Transfer characteristics : BT.709
Matrix coefficients : BT.709
AUDIO INFO
Format : DTS
Format/Info : Digital Theater Systems
Format profile : MA / Core
Mode : 16
Format settings, Endianness : Big
Codec ID : A_DTS
Duration : 1h 20mn
Bit rate mode : Variable
Bit rate : Unknown / 1 509 Kbps
Channel(s) : 6 channels
Channel positions : Front: L C R, Side: L R, LFE
Sampling rate : 48.0 KHz
Bit depth : 16 bits
Compression mode : Lossless / Lossy
Language : English
Default : Yes
Forced : No</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>1.20</Duracion>
        <Poster>30bc4821e322c2958478dfadae3d374c.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="92" contador="56">
        <Nombre>Miles Davis - Live at Montreux</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>1991</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>Miles Davis y Quincy Jones con la orquesta de Gil Evans-Live at Montreux 
This concert from 8 July 1991 was the last of Miles Davis many appearances at the Montreux Jazz Festival and took place only a few months before his death. Despite a defiant never look back philosophy, Miles was persuaded by Quincy Jones and Claude Nobs to take part in this tribute to his great friend Gil Evans, who had passed away in 1988. This truly unique concert was an historical event and a musical triumph, thankfully captured here for posterity. Miles Davis was a giant of 20th century music and this concert is as much a tribute to him as it is to the late Gil Evans.
El blu ray de este concierto, ha sido editado en 2013.
0. Introduction by Claude Nobs &amp; Quincy Jones
1. Boplicity
2. Maids of Cadiz
3. The Duke
4. My Ship
5. Miles Ahead
6. Blues for Pablo
7. Orgone
8. Gone, Gone, Gone
9. Summertime
10. Here Come De Honey Man
11. The Pan Piper
12. Solea</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>CONTENEDOR: MKV 
FUENTE DE VIDEO: BLU-RAY 
CODEC DE VIDEO: x264 
FRAMES DE VIDEO: 29,97 
RESOLUCIÓN DE VIDEO: 1280x720 
BITRATE DE VIDEO: 9.999 kbps 
AUDIO 1: FLAC 2.0
AUDIO 2: AC3 5.1 640 Kbps
TAMAÑO: 4,12 GB</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>1</Duracion>
        <Poster>Mile_Davis_y_Quincy_Jones.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="93" contador="59">
        <Nombre>Jimi Hendrix - Voodoo Child West Coast Seattle Boy</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>2012</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>Plot:
Over the course of just four extraordinary years, Jimi Hendrix left an indelible stamp on the world, shaping not only popular music but popular culture as well. He remains the most innovative musician of his, or any other, era having virtually reshaped the vocabulary of the electric guitar for future generations. Jimi Hendrix: Voodoo Child is an autobiographical journey that reveals the man as never before, featuring the legendary musician&#x2019;s own words to tell the story of his remarkable life.
Drawing upon interviews granted by Hendrix, coupled with letters, writings and recordings, Jimi Hendrix: Voodoo Child provides new insight into one of the most enduring icons of popular culture. The special is filled with never before seen photographs and film footage from the Hendrix family archive and features a soundtrack that includes such legendary Hendrix recordings as "Purple Haze," "Hey Joe," "Fire," "Voodoo Child (Slight Return)" together with never before heard live performances. Funk legend and Rock and Roll Hall of Fame member Bootsy Collins of Parliament-Funkadelic renown, is featured as the voice of Jimi Hendrix.</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>Filename.......: Jimi Hendrix Voodoo Child West Coast Seattle Boy 2012 1080p BluRay AAC 2.0 x264
Format........ : Matroska
Duration.......: 1h 31mn 44s 896ms
Size...........: 3.42 GiB
Video:
Codec..........: Mpeg-4 Avc High@L4.0
Type...........: Progressive
Resolution.....: 1920x1080
Aspect Ratio...: 16:9
Bit rate.......: 5.3 Mbps  
Frame rate.....: 29.970 Fps
Audio:
Format.........: AAC Audio
Channels.......: 2 Channels
Bit rate.......: Variable
Language.......: English</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>1.31</Duracion>
        <Poster>jymmyvoodobd.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="94" contador="61">
        <Nombre>The Who - Quadrophenia - Live In London</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>2014</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>TRACKLIST:
01. I Am The Sea 01:57
02. The Real Me 03:42
03. Quadrophenia 05:50
04. Cut My Hair 04:08
05. The Punk And The Godfather 05:02
06. I'm One 03:01
07. The Dirty Jobs 04:55
08. Helpless Dancer 02:17
09. Is It In My Head 03:37
10. I've Had Enough 06:42
11. 5:15 11:12
12. Sea And Sand 05:40
13. Drowned 07:21
14. Bell Boy 05:11
15. Doctor Jimmy 08:09
16. The Rock 06:51
17. Love Reign O'er Me 07:22
Bonus Performance:
18. Who Are You 06:27
19. You Better You Bet 05:35
20. Pinball Wizard 02:53
21. Baba O'Riley 05:27
22. Won't Get Fooled Again 09:06
23. Tea &amp; Theatre 03:58</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>The Who - Quadrophenia - Live In London (2014) [BDrip 1080p x264 DTS AC3]
Contenedor: MKV
Fuente de Video:The Who - Quadrophenia - Live In London (2014).BluRay
Codec de Video: x264
Frames de Video: 23.976 fps
Resolución de Video: 1920x1080p
Bitrate de video apróx: 4.000Kbps Apróx.
Audio: Inglés DTS 5.1 
Tamaño apróx. 7.01 GB.</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>1.35</Duracion>
        <Poster>vylix2.png</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="95" contador="65">
        <Nombre>Jimi Hendrix - Blue Wild Angel Live At - The Isle Of Wight</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>2014</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>Tracklist:
1.Blue Wild Angel: Jimi Hendrix Live At The Isle Of Wight (Main Film) (Live At The Isle Of Wight)
2.Introduction (Live At The Isle Of Wight)
3.God Save The Queen (Live At The Isle Of Wight)
4.Sgt. Pepper&#x2019;s Lonely Hearts Club Band (Live At The Isle Of Wight)
5.Spanish Castle Magic (Live At The Isle Of Wight)
6.All Along The Watchtower (Live At The Isle Of Wight)
7.Machine Gun (Live At The Isle Of Wight)
8.Lover Man (Live At The Isle Of Wight)
9.Freedom (Live At The Isle Of Wight)
10.Red House (Live At The Isle Of Wight)
11.Dolly Dagger (Live At The Isle Of Wight)
12.Foxey Lady (Live At The Isle Of Wight)
13.Message To Love (Live At The Isle Of Wight)
14.Ezy Ryder (Live At The Isle Of Wight)
15.Purple Haze (Live At The Isle Of Wight)
16.Voodoo Child (Slight Return) (Live At The Isle Of Wight)
17.In From The Storm (Live At The Isle Of Wight)
18.Credits (Live At The Isle Of Wight)</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>General:
Filename.......: Jimi Hendrix Blue Wild Angel Live At The Isle Of Wight 2014 1080p BluRay DTS-HD MA 5.1 x264
Format........ : Matroska
Size...........: 8.68 GiB
Video:
Codec..........: Mpeg-4 Avc High@L4.0
Type...........: Progressive
Resolution.....: 1920x1080
Aspect Ratio...: 16:9
Bit rate.......: 8.80 Mbps
Frame rate.....: 29.970 Fps
Audio:
Format.........: Dts Hd Master Audio
Channels.......: 6 Channels
Bit rate.......: 4512 Kbps
Language.......: English</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>1.57</Duracion>
        <Poster>2w7i9lg.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="96" contador="63">
        <Nombre>Queen - Live at the Rainbow 1974</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>2014</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>Tracklist:
1.Procession
2.Now I&#x2019;m Here
3.Ogre Battle
4.Father To Son
5.White Queen (As It Began)
6.Flick Of The Wrist
7.In The Lap Of The Gods
8.Killer Queen
9.The March Of The Black Queen
10.Bring Back That Leroy Brown
11.Son And Daughter
12.Guitar Solo
13.Son And Daughter (Reprise)
14.Keep Yourself Alive
15.Drum Solo
16.Keep Yourself Alive (Reprise)
17.Seven Seas Of Rhye
18.Stone Cold Crazy
19.Liar
20.In The Lap Of The Gods&#x2026; Revisited
21.Big Spender
22.Modern Times Rock &#x2019;n&#x2019; Roll
23.Jailhouse Rock
24.God Save The Queen</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>Filename.......: Queen Live at the Rainbow 74 2014 1080p BluRay DTS-HD MA 5.1 x264
Format........ : Matroska
Duration.......: 1h 20mn 1s 398ms
Size...........: 8.37 GiB
Video:
Codec..........: Mpeg-4 Avc High@L4.0
Type...........: Progressive
Resolution.....: 1920x1080
Aspect Ratio...: 16:9
Bit rate.......: 9.79 Mbps
Frame rate.....: 29.970 Fps
Audio:
Format.........: Dts Hd Master Audio
Channels.......: 6 Channels
Bit rate.......: 7092 Kbps
Language.......: English</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>1.20</Duracion>
        <Poster>2ntzjfl.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="99" contador="66">
        <Nombre>The Who: At Kilburn</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>1977</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>The Who at Kilburn: 1977 is a film of two live performances by British rock band the Who released as a two-disc DVD set on 17 November 2008 by Image Entertainment. The first disc included the band's performance at the Gaumont State Theatre on 15 December 1977, while the second disc featured the band's performance at the London Coliseum on 14 December 1969. The film restoration was produced by Nigel Sinclair's Spitfire Pictures in association with Trinifold Management.
The Kilburn show was recorded for Jeff Stein's documentary film The Kids Are Alright and was The Who's first show in over a year. However, due to sound problems, it was canned for over 30 years, with only two small portions of the whole gig actually made it to The Kids Are Alright&#x2014;Pete saying "There's a guitar up here, if any big-mouthed little git wants to come up and fucking take it off me"; and when all four members of the band meet in the center of the stage after the conclusion of the show. "My Wife", however, made it to the soundtrack of The Kids Are Alright, albeit without any sound restoration, and slightly shortened (comparisons to bootleg versions of this show indicate portions of John Entwistle's vocals were later overdubbed to correct pitch errors). It includes their first ever live performance of "Who Are You", which would also be their last performance of the song with Moon on stage.
The Coliseum concert on 14 December 1969 was recorded during a tour of European opera houses. Combined with the features in the Extras, nearly the entire performance can be seen.
Disc 1: The Who at Kilburn 1977
    "I Can't Explain" (3:10)
    "Substitute" (2:59)
    "Baba O'Riley" (5:18)
    "My Wife" (7:02)
    "Behind Blue Eyes" (3:33)
    "Dreaming from the Waist" (5:10)
    "Pinball Wizard" (2:43)
    "I'm Free" (2:45)
    "Tommy's Holiday Camp" (1:30)
    "Summertime Blues" (3:45)
    "Shakin' All Over" (5:00)
    "My Generation" (3:44)
    "Join Together" (2:28)
    "Who Are You" (6:04)
    "Won't Get Fooled Again" (8:49)
    "(End Credits)" (1:33)</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>The Who at Kilburn 1977 - BDrip 1080p x264 DTS-HDMA mkv
Blu Ray rip in 1080p x264 MKV with 5.1 DTS-HD surround (1h5m44s)
De-interlaced and encoded at CRF18 with VidCoder</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>1977</Duracion>
        <Poster>nWqPwEtDsvkLdgLJ0fCiUHOSQwe.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="101" contador="69">
        <Nombre>The Rolling Stones - From The Vault The Marquee Club Live in 1971</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>1971</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>From The Vault: The Marquee &#x2013; Live in 1971 released on DVD and iTunes
The Rolling Stones From The Vault: The Marquee &#x2013; Live In 1971 to be released 22 June 2015.
    Sought-after club performance released for the first time on DVD in four formats
    Rare gig from the Rolling Stones in 1971 filmed at the Marquee Club
    A classic, must-own performance
    Part of the From The Vault series from The Rolling Stones archive
A sought-after, rare club performance from The Rolling Stones in 1971 filmed at London&#x2019;s iconic Marquee Club will finally see the light of day, after almost two decades of being stored away in an attic. The Rolling Stones From The Vault: The Marquee &#x2013; Live in 1971 will be released on DVD in four formats and on iTunes via Eagle Rock on 22 June 2015.
This remarkable performance was filmed for US television in 1971, shortly after The Rolling Stones had completed their 1971 Farewell Tour of the UK, and a month before the release of the album Sticky Fingers. The gig marked the first time tracks &#x2018;Brown Sugar&#x2019;, &#x2018;Dead Flowers&#x2019;, &#x2018;Bitch&#x2019; and the rarely performed &#x2018;I Got The Blues&#x2019; were showcased live; four tracks taken from the Sticky Fingers album. The line-up at this time was Mick Jagger, Keith Richards, Charlie Watts, Mick Taylor and Bill Wyman.
The show was an intimate, rare club appearance and very little footage has been released, until now. Part of the &#x201c;From The Vault&#x201d; series of live concerts from the band&#x2019;s archive, The Rolling Stones From The Vault: The Marquee &#x2013; Live In 1971 is a must own DVD for any Stones fan, featuring carefully restored footage and sound mixed to perfection by Bob Clearmountain, including 5.1 surround sound on the DVD and SD Blu-ray formats.
The release of The Rolling Stones From The Vault: The Marquee &#x2013; Live In 1971 coincides with the special edition of album Sticky Fingers, and includes alternative takes of &#x2018;I Got The Blues&#x2019; and &#x2018;Bitch&#x2019;, plus a Top of the Pops performance of &#x2018;Brown Sugar&#x2019; from 1971.
TRACKLISTING:
    Live With Me
    Dead Flowers
    I Got The Blues
    Let It Rock
    Midnight Rambler
    (I Can&#x2019;t Get No) Satisfaction
    Bitch
    Brown Sugar
BONUS TRACKS:
    I Got The Blues &#x2013; Take 1
    I Got The Blues &#x2013; Take 2
    Bitch &#x2013; Take 1
    Bitch &#x2013; take 2
    Brown Sugar (Top Of The Pops, 1971)</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>The.Rolling.Stones.From.The.Vault.The.Marquee.Club.Live.In.1971.2015.1080p.MBLURAY.x264-DEV0
picture -.-.-.- 1440x1080 @ 11571 kbit/s
speed -.-.-.-.- 29,970 fps
audio -.-.-.-.- dts 1509 6ch, flac 3086 2ch
length .-.-.-.- 0h38m
size .-.-.-.-.- 4.37 GiB (4692439032 bytes)
Extras:</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>0.38 + 0.22</Duracion>
        <Poster>Rolling-Stones-Marquee-71-DVD-cover-hr-425x600.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="102" contador="74">
        <Nombre>The Doors - Feast Of Friends</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>1968</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>Notes:Feast Of Friends, filmed in 1968, was the first and only film produced about The Doors by The Doors. It offers a cinematic look at The Doors on the road during their summer &#x2019;68 tour. Whilst never truly completed, the film provides a stylistic approach in true sixties cinéma vérité style. Concert performances are intercut with fly-on-the-wall footage of the group in their natural habitat, sometimes playful, sensitive, chaotic and touching. Other than a few appearances in film festivals in 1968, an official release would never be seen until now. Completely restored from the original negative, as supervised by Jim Morrison, the film has been color-corrected and mastered in high definition with the soundtrack totally remixed and remastered by long-time Doors co-producer/engineer Bruce Botnick.
Bonus Features:
1) Feast Of Friends: Encore &#x2013; A newly produced feature using footage shot for Feast Of Friends, Encore is a complimentary piece which provides a deeper look into the life of the band at this period as they tour, record, travel and even vacation together. The program avoids the typical selection of hits and makes use of The Doors rare recordings to accompany this unreleased footage.
2) The Doors Are Open &#x2013; A British TV documentary originally aired on December 17th, 1968, The Doors Are Open is focused around the band&#x2019;s performance at London&#x2019;s Roundhouse, which took place just days after the completion of filming for Feast Of Friends. Although previously released, the film has suffered from numerous sound and picture quality issues. Now the image quality has been dramatically improved and the sound has been transformed by Bruce Botnick to be as true to the original live sound as possible.
3) The End &#x2013; Filmed in Toronto, Canada in August 1967 and first broadcast in October that year, this performance of &#x201c;The End&#x201d; was for The O&#x2019;Keefe Centre Presents: The Rock Scene &#x2013; Like It Is. In addition to the performance it includes the introduction by Noel Harrison and later interviews by John Densmore, Robby Krieger, Ray Manzarek and Danny Sugerman. Many fans consider this recording to be one of the best Doors performances ever caught on film.</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>The Doors Feast Of Friends 1968 BRRIP 1080p x264 DTS AAC INFERNO
Video Codec......: AVC
Video Bitrate....: 6749 Kbps
Audio Codec1.....: DTS
Audio Bitrate....: 1509 Kbps, 6 channels - ("Feast of Friends:Encore" did not have a 6 channel audio source available, 1510 Kbps, 5 channels)
Audio Codec2.....: AAC
Audio Bitrate....: 640 Kbps, 6 channels - ("Feast of Friends:Encore" did not have a 6 channel audio source available, 640 Kbps, 2 channels)
File Size........: The Doors Feast Of Friends 1968 - 2.46 GiB, The Doors Feast Of Friends_Encore - 2.14 GiB, The Doors Are Open - 3.35 GiB, The End - 0.99 GiB
Resolution.......: 1920 x 1072
Runtime..........: The Doors Feast Of Friends 1968 - 39mn 30s, The Doors Feast Of Friends_Encore - 34mn 44s, The Doors Are Open - 53mn 49s, The End - 16mn 1s
Language.........: English
Subtitles........: No
Sample...........: Yes
Source...........: The.Doors.Feast.Of.Friends.1968.COMPLETE.MBLURAY-COPYRiOT</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>53+39+34+16</Duracion>
        <Poster>jiTNfzm.jpeg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="103" contador="75">
        <Nombre>Jimi Hendrix  - Electric Church (1970)</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>2015</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>notes &gt;&gt; live at the atlanta pop festival
july 4, 1970
jimi! lay your hands on me!
tracklist &gt;&gt; fire
spanish castle magic
red house
room full of mirrors
all along the watchtower
freedom
foxet lady
purple haze
hey joe
voodoo child (slight return)
stone free
star sprangled banner
straight ahead</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>Jimi Hendrix Experience - Electric Church (2015)
picture &gt;&gt; 1280x720 @ 4421kb/s
speed &gt;&gt; 23.976fps
audio &gt;&gt; FLAC 1557kb/s 2ch, DTS 1509kb/s 6ch
text &gt;&gt; en fr de es nl</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>1.41</Duracion>
        <Poster>141928_front.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="104" contador="73">
        <Nombre>Roger Waters - The Wall</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>2015</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>Roger Waters The Wall captures Roger Waters
sold-out 2010-2013 The Wall Live tour, the first
complete staging of the classic Pink Floyd
concept album since 1990. A tour-de-force of
rock &amp; roll stagecraft anchored in a powerful
message of peace and compassion, The Wall
became a must-see concert event for music
fans everywhere. It played to over 4.5 million
people at more than 200 shows across four
continents, making it the most successful
worldwide tour by a solo artist in history
Details o ne of the most elaborately staged
theatrical productions in music history as Pink
Floyd frontman Roger Waters performs the
band's critically acclaimed album The Wall
in its entirety: 14 Brick Wall 3
01 In The Flesh? 15 Last Few Bricks
02 The Thin Ice 16 Goodbye Cruel World
03 Brick Wall 1 17 Hey You
04 The Happiest Days 18 Is There Anybody Out
05 Brick Wall 2 19 Nobody Home
06 The Ballad Of Jean 20 Vera
07 Mother 21 Bring The Boys Back
08 Goodbye Blue Sky 22 Comfortably Numb
09 Empty Spaces 23 The Show Must Go On
10 What Shall We Do Now? 24 In The Flesh
11 Young Lust 25 Run Like Hell
12 One Of My Turns 26 Waiting For The Worms
13 Don't Leave Me Now 27 Stop: 28 The Trial
29 Outside The Wall</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>sOURCE..............................bluray
gENRE..........art-rock|prog-rock|psy-rock
rATING............................8.7|1017
fOOTAGE...........................1280x536
fPS.................................23.976
bITRATE...............................4538
aUDIO|A...............flac|7.1|dolby-atmos
pLAYTIME..........................02:12:00
sIZE................................7.63gb
sUBS.........de|en|fr|it|es|pt|el|dk|fi|no
sUBS.........se|bt|pl|ru|cz|hu|tr|ja|ko|zh
sCANZ................................cover</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>2.12</Duracion>
        <Poster>roger_waters_the_wall.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="105" contador="70">
        <Nombre>Indio Solari - En Concierto</Nombre>
        <Annus>2015</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>A partir del Miércoles 16 de Diciembre de 2015, sale a la venta en todo el país "Indio y los Fundamentalistas del Aire Acondicionado, el Concierto".
Se trata de una tirada especial y limitada de 30.000 unidades del registro en DVD de la película ya estrenada en los cines. Como Bonus especial también contara con dos CDs estéreo de la banda de sonido de dicho film. Los precios no han sido confirmados desde la producción, pero rondaran entre los 600 y 700 pesos.
Una caja que contiene, 2 DVDs y 2 CDs más un librillo con fotos referentes al concierto de diciembre de 2008.
De esta manera la producción del Indio Solari cierra un año de esfuerzo y dedicación para lograr un documento único que quedará para siempre en la historia del rock nacional.</Critica>
        <Comentario>Resolución: 1280*720
Formato: .mkv TDTRip TVP
Codec Video: AVC High@L4.1
Codec Audio: AAC
Bitrate Video: ~5000 Kbp
Bitrate Audio: 192 Kbps</Comentario>
        <DatosTecnicos>Video: 100
Audio: AC3 2.0 320 Kbps / DTS 1510 Kbps
Norma de Video: NTSC
Formato de Pantalla: Fullscreen
Idioma Audio: Español
Subtitulos: No
Menú: Si
Extras: No</DatosTecnicos>
        <Poster>m4enSFC.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="106" contador="71">
        <Nombre>Sumo - Zero Bar</Nombre>
        <Id>VHSrip</Id>
        <Annus>1983</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>SINOPSIS:
01 - Divididos por la felicidad
02 - Heroina
03 - La Rubia Tarada (Una noche en New York City)
04 - Night and Day
05 - Fuck You
06 - No Duermas Mas
07 - Regtest
08 - Don't Cry
09 - White Trash
10 - Reggae Blues
11 - Banderitas y Globos
12 - Mejor No Hablar de Ciertas Cosas (Incompleto)
[:exc:] INFORMACIÓN ADICIONAL:
Quien lo subió a la web escribió esto:
Para todos aquellos que lo pudieron ver en vivo y para los jóvenes que no, aqui les paso este video recuperado de un VHS, grabado por mi en 1983. Creo que no quedan dudas que Sumo en vivo fue una banda muy poderosas, que nunca se reflejó en los discos.
Además estamos frente a un hecho histórico dado que fue la última vez que Sokoll, tocó la batería para luego dedicarse a ser mormón, cosa que duró muy poco.
Fue reemplazado por el baterista de la Hurlingham Reggae Band :banda paralela de Luca, "Superman" Troglio, quien terminaba los recitales poniéndose hielo en sus manos, dado que tocaba muy intensamente.
Para terminar : Disfruten de Luca y de la banda que más fuerza tuvo en los ´80.
Y para los que tienen mi edad, muéstrenle a sus hijos la terrible aplanadora que era Sumo, y sobre todo el Gran Luca Prodan, que dejaba su vida en cada show.
Saludos a todos sus fans. Es un gran honor aportar esto y tengo otro recital que tengo que buscar, así que : queden a la espera. Abrazos a todos los seguidores de Sumo</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>Resolución: 1280x720
Formato: VHSrip (WebRip)
Codec Video: MPEG-4
Codec Audio: AAC
Bitrate Video: 2557 Kbps
Bitrate Audio: 192 Kbps</DatosTecnicos>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="107" contador="72">
        <Nombre>Jimi Hendrix - Jimi Plays Monterey</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>1986</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>Jimi Hendrix's landmark concert in Monterey County
Fairgrounds in California in which he plays signature
songs like "Purp;e Haze," "Foxy Lady," and "Wild
Thing."</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>Jimi.Plays.Monterey.1986.1080p.BluRay.x264-SADPANDA
* SIZE ...... 4.4 GiB
* DURATION .. 49mn 2s
* VIDEO ..... x264 1440x1080 11,203Kbps @ 23.976fps
* AUDIO ..... English FLAC 1536Kbps 2ch
* SUBS ...... N/A</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>49</Duracion>
        <Poster>blu-ray-jimi-plays-monterey-shake-otis-at-monterey-277011-MLC20457636772_102015-O.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="108" contador="78">
        <Nombre>The Rolling Stones - Havana Moon</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>2016</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <DatosTecnicos>7.90 GiB
1080p
8 000 kb/s
DTS</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>1.50 + 0,28</Duracion>
        <Poster>Havana-Moon-Rolling-Stones.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="109" contador="76">
        <Nombre>The Beatles: 1</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>2015</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>Additional 23 videos including
alternate versions, as well as
rarely seen and newly restored
films and videos: 01 Twist And Shout
02 Baby It's You (1995 Promo Clip)
03 Words Of Love (2013 Promo Clip)
04 Please Please Me
05 I Feel Fine (Version 2)
06 Day Tripper
07 Day Tripper (Version 3)
08 We Can Work It Out (Version 3)
09 Paperback Writer (Version 2)
10 Rain (Version 1)
11 Rain (Version 5)
12 Strawberry Fields Forever
13 Within You Without You / Tomorrow Never Knows
14 A Day In The Life
15 Hello, Goodbye (Version 2)
16 Hello, Goodbye (Version 3)
17 Hey Bulldog (1999 Edit)
18 Hey Jude (Mix Of Versions 2 &amp; 3)
19 Revolution (Version 2)
20 Get Back (Naked Version 2003)
21 Don't Let Me Down (Naked Version 2003)
22 Free As A Bird
23 Real Love</Critica>
        <Problemas>5 tema, rrevolution,audio -4500
6 tema, get back, -3700</Problemas>
        <DatosTecnicos>The Beatles ONE PLUS 1962-1970 REMASTERED 1080p iNTERNAL MBluRay x264-LiQUiD
MAIn.fOOTAGE..........................1440x1080
fPS.................................23.976
bITRATE...............................9398
aUDIO|A...........................flac|2.0
aUDIO|B...........................flac|5.1
pLAYTIME..........................00:37:00
sIZE................................4.37gb
sUBS..................................none</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>0.38</Duracion>
        <Poster>índice.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="111" contador="77">
        <Nombre>The Rolling Stones - Ole Ole Ole A Trip Across Latin America</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>2017</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>Track Listing
1) Out Of Control (Buenos Aires, Argentina)
2) Paint It Black (Buenos Aires, Argentina)
3) Honky Tonk Women (S o Paulo, Brazil)
4) Sympathy For The Devil (S o Paulo, Brazil)
5) You Got The Silver (Lima, Peru)
6) Midnight Rambler (Lima, Peru)
7) Miss You (Lima, Peru)</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>The.Rolling.Stones.Ole.Ole.Ole.A.Trip.Across.Latin.America.2017.1080p.MBluRay.x264-FKKHD
format.....mkv
video......1920x800 @ 0 kbps
audio......DTS 5.1 @ 1509 kbps</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>0.55</Duracion>
        <Poster>71YqyUA+jdL._SL1500_.jpg</Poster>
        <Poster>71uIblJ7LhL._SL1024_.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="112" contador="79">
        <Nombre>David Gilmour - Live At Pompeii Show</Nombre>
        <Annus>2017</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>David Gilmour returns to historic Pompeii Amphitheater, performing two spectacular shows shot in dazzling 4K. He's the only performer to play to an audience in the arena since the gladiators. These shows are not only historic, they are an audio-visual experience. Featuring lasers, pyrotechnics, and of course, rock and roll, this once-in-a-millennia opportunity also features a documentary entitled Pompeii: Then and Now. The documentary includes footage from both of David Gilmour s appearances at the Pompeii Amphitheater, from the audience-less show in 1971 to the electrifying performance in 2016
David Gilmour - Live At Pompeii Show 1
The full deluxe 2DiSC Bluray release includes:
DiSC1: conert itself (2x shows) and documentary Pompeii Then And Now
DiSC2: bonus concert films (South America 2015, Wroclaw 2016) various tour documentaries from 2015-2016 and David Gilmour: Wider Horizons BBC Documentary
----Show 1 of DiSC1:
5 A.M
Rattle That Lock
Faces Of Stone
What Do You Want From Me
The Blue
The Great Gig In The Sky
A Boat Lies Waiting
Whish You Were Here
Money
In Any Tongue
High Hopes
----Show 2 of DiSC1:
One Of These Days
Shine On You Crazy Diamond (Parts 1-5)
Fat Old Sun
Coming Back To Life
On An Island
Today
Sorrow
Run Like Hell
Time/Breathe (In The Air) (Reprise)
Comfortably Numb
----extras 1:
Astronomy Domine
Us And Them
Today
Time/Breathe(In The Air) (Reprise)
Comfortobly Numb
----extras 2:
Tracklist:
5 A.M
Rattle That Rock
Dancing Right In Front Of Me
The Girl In The Yellow Dress
In Any Tongue</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>Year: 2017 Rel Date: 10-2017
Size: 5.45GB Rar: 59x100
Video: x264 @ 9943kbps Menus: n/a
Audio: DTS 6ch @ 1509kbps Subtitles: None
Region: NTSC Resolution: 1920 x 1280
Disco 2:
Size: 6.55GB Rar: 71x100
Video: x264 @ 9632kbps Menus: n/a
Audio: DTS 6ch @ 1509kbps Subtitles: None
Region: NTSC Resolution: 1920 x 1080
Disco 3 (extras)
Audio: DTS 6ch @ 1509kbps Subtitles: None
Region: NTSC Resolution: 1280 x 720</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>1.08 + 1.24 + 0.35 + 0.29</Duracion>
        <Poster>David-Gilmour-Pompeii-Movie-Poster.jpg</Poster>
        <Poster>91qb3S7WysL._SL1500_.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="113" contador="80">
        <Nombre>Monterey Pop</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>1968</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>A film about the greatest pre-Woodstock rock music festival.</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>Monterey.Pop.1968.REMASTERED.720p.BluRay.x264-DEV0
picture &gt;&gt; 960x720 6361kb/s
speed &gt;&gt; 23.976fps
audio &gt;&gt; English 1509kb/s 6ch DTS
text &gt;&gt; none
runtime &gt;&gt; 1h 19mn
size &gt;&gt; 4476.21mb (4693646794bytes)
Monterey.Pop.The.Outtake.Performances.1968.720p.MBLURAY.x264-DEV0
picture &gt;&gt; 976x720 7046kb/s
speed &gt;&gt; 23.976fps
audio &gt;&gt; English 192kb/s 2ch AC-3
text &gt;&gt; none
runtime &gt;&gt; 2h 9mn
size &gt;&gt; 6716.44mb (7042701063bytes)</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>1.19+2.09</Duracion>
        <Poster>189159_front</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="114" contador="81">
        <Nombre>Bob Marley - A Caribbean Icon</Nombre>
        <Id>dvd no hd</Id>
        <Annus>2010</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>TRACK LiST: 01. Trenchtown Rock
02. Them Belly Full (But We Hungry)
03. I Shot The Sheriff
04. Rebel Music
05. Lively Up Yourself
06. Crazy Baid Heads
07. Medley: War / No More Trouble
08. The Heathen
09. No Woman, No Cry
10. Jamming
11. Get Up, Stand Up
12. Exodus
13. Curley David - Reggae Adventure</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>:AURORA PROUDLY PRESENTS: Bob.Marley.A.Caribbean.Icon.2010.PAL.MDVDR-AURORA: RELEASE INFO: Label: T2 Entertainment Cat.No: 220269
Date: 2018/03/23 Source: PAL DVD5
Genre: Reggae Aspect: 4:3
Runtime: 01:26:13 Files: 82x50MB
Link: www.amazon.com/Bob-Marley-Caribbean-Audio-2010-07-12/dp/B014I3GAVM
:(VIDEO):. .:(MENU):. .:(EXTRAS):
Untouched, Untouched, Untouched
Re-encoded
Passes
Bitrate
:(AUDIO):. .:(SUBS):
English, DD 2.0 Mono
French
German, German
Spanish
Dutch</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>1.26</Duracion>
        <Poster>41qFeUV5uFL.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="115" contador="82">
        <Nombre>The Beatles - Sgt Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band Super Deluxe Anniversary Edition</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>2017</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>The Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band has been remixed and presented with additional session recordings, and it is the first Beatles album to be remixed and expanded since the 2003 release of Let It Be&#x2026; Naked. To create the new stereo and 5.1 surround audio mixes for 'Sgt. Pepper,' producer Giles Martin and mix engineer Sam Okell worked with an expert team of engineers and audio restoration specialists at Abbey Road Studios in London.
The Anniversary Edition releases include Martin's new stereo mix of the album, which was sourced directly from the original four-track session tapes and guided by the original, Beatles-preferred mono mix produced by his father, George Martin. The set also includes the 1992 The Making Of Sgt. Pepper documentary.
The Making of Sgt. Pepper [restored 1992 documentary film, previously unreleased]
- Promotional Films: "A Day In The Life;" "Strawberry Fields Forever;" "Penny Lane" [4K restored]</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>Video
Codec: MPEG-4 AVC
Resolution: 1080p
The Making Of Sgt. Pepper
LPCM 2.0, 2304Kbps, 48kHz, 24 Bit
Subtitles
English, French, Spanish, German, Dutch, Italian and Portuguese</DatosTecnicos>
        <Poster>61QEH5tSzbL._SS500.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="116" contador="83">
        <Nombre>John Lennon - Gimme Some Truth</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>2000</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>Eagle Rock are delighted to announce the
release of two films by John and Yoko
Imagine and Gimme Some Truth
Both films, which focus on the Imagine era
have been hand restored frame-by-frame
from the original film reels into HD
and their soundtracks have been remixed
in glorious 5.1 surround sound, and remastered
01 Imagine
02 Crippled Inside
03 Good Morning
04 Jealous Guy
05 Don't Count The Waves
06 It's So Hard
07 Mrs. Lennon
08 In Bag
09 I Don't Wanna Be A Soldier Mama
10 Mind Train
11 Whisper Piece
12 What's That In The Sky?
13 Power To The People
14 Gimme Some Truth
15 Midsummer New York
16 Oh My Love
17 How Do You Sleep?
18 How?
19 Oh Yoko!
20 Beach / End Credits
21 Gimme Some Truth:Imagine
22 Crippled Inside
23 Oh Yoko!
24 Jealous Guy
25 It's So Hard
26 I Don't Wanna Be A Soldier Mama
27 Gimme Some Truth
28 My Love
29 How Do You Sleep?
30 How?
31 Imagine: This is the first time both films have been
commercially available at the same time</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>1504 x 1080
29.970
8574
FLAC 2.0
FLAC 5.1
01:03:00
BLURAY
7.65 GB: |</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>1.03</Duracion>
        <Poster>41NDM0XEPTL.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="117" contador="84">
        <Nombre>John Lennon - Imagine</Nombre>
        <Annus>1972</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>The Imagine music films by John &amp; Yoko
Directors: John Lennon, Yoko Ono
Starring: John Lennon, Yoko Ono, George Harrison
Universal Music Group is celebrating what would have been John Lennon's 78th birthday on October 9 with the release of Imagine and tangentially related items in a number of formats. That includes a new "two fer" released in collaboration with Eagle Rock Entertainment that gathers together two fascinating films featuring John and Yoko tied directly to Imagine. Those wanting more information on this title and its sibling are encouraged to read our Imagine &amp; Gimme Some Truth Blu-ray review, which contains full coverage and more screenshots from each film included on the Blu-ray disc.
Imagine and Gimme Some Truth are presented on Blu-ray courtesy of Eagle Vision, an imprint of Eagle Rock Entertainment, and Universal Music Group, with AVC encoded 1080i transfers in 1.39:1. Both of the films feature rather involved restoration credits at the end which document a seemingly ungainly time period spanning from 2010 to 2018 to complete the process. Why that's the case is unknown to me (and the documentation provided with this release doesn't offer any clues), but considering some of the variances on display, especially in Imagine, I'm wondering if completed versions might have needed to be cobbled together from different sources. The interesting interviews included in the insert booklet suggest that at least Gimme Some Truth was sourced largely from 16mm, but both films on this release have an at times grainy and fuzzy appearance that suggest smaller formats. That said, footage like the interstitial scenes featuring Jack Palance look decidedly rougher than the at times already pretty soft bulk of footage, and I wonder if perhaps a few 8mm home movies might have been included (see screenshot 29 for an example of what the Palance footage can look like when compared to most of the rest of Imagine). The palette is a bit more suffused on Imagine than Gimme Some Truth (and it looks like some duplicate elements of Imagine footage may have been used for Gimme Some Truth), though both features retain a generally accurate accounting of the colors. Fine detail tends to vary based on lighting sources and proximity to the camera. While it evidently took eight years to restore these features, whatever corrective gauntlet the elements were put through missed a number of things like hairs in the gate, some of which stick around for quite long periods of time. Screenshots 23 - 26 show some of these hairs (look both at the tops and bottoms of the frames), while screenshots 27 - 29 document some of the rougher looking moments.
01 Imagine
02 Crippled Inside
03 Good Morning
04 Jealous Guy
05 Don't Count The Waves
06 It's So Hard
07 Mrs. Lennon
08 In Bag
09 I Don't Wanna Be A Soldier Mama
10 Mind Train
11 Whisper Piece
12 What's That In The Sky?
13 Power To The People
14 Gimme Some Truth
15 Midsummer New York
16 Oh My Love
17 How Do You Sleep?
18 How?
19 Oh Yoko!
20 Beach / End Credits
21 Gimme Some Truth:Imagine
22 Crippled Inside
23 Oh Yoko!
24 Jealous Guy
25 It's So Hard
26 I Don't Wanna Be A Soldier Mama
27 Gimme Some Truth
28 My Love
29 How Do You Sleep?
30 How?
31 Imagine: This is the first time both films have been
commercially available at the same time</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>John Lennon Imagine 1971 REMASTERED 1080p MBluRay x264-LiQUiD
1504 x 1080
29.970
8840
FLAC 2.0
FLAC 5.1
01:07:00
BLURAY
8.75 GB: |</DatosTecnicos>
        <Poster>213454_front.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="119" contador="85">
        <Nombre>The Rolling Stones - Rock and Roll Circus</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>1966</Annus>
        <Imdb-puntaje>7,7 (1.650)</Imdb-puntaje>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>Edición: 2018
The Rolling Stones Rock and Roll Circus was shot over two days in December
1968 and featured guests such as The Who, Jethro Tull, Taj Mahal, Marianne
Faithfull and the impromptu supergroup The Dirty Mac (which featured John
Lennon, Keith Richards, Mitch Mitchell, Eric Clapton and, on bag, Yoko Ono)
in addition to the original lineup of The Rolling Stones
Shot in a north London television studio by director Michael Lindsay-Hogg
(he would shoot Let It Be shortly after) The Rolling Stones Rock and Roll
Circus was a concert filmed with the band themselves as on-screen hosts in
addition to performing. The audience were made up of fan club members and it
was ostensibly meant to be a BBC TV special for the Beggars Banquet long player
But Brian Jones left and then died, and so the film wasn t properly released
for 28 years
01. Song For Jeffrey Jethro Tull
02. A Quick One While He s Away The Who
03. Ain t That A Lot Of Love Taj Mahal
04. Something Better Marianne Faithfull
05. Yer Blues The Dirty Mac
06. Whole Lotta Yoko Yoko Ono &amp; Ivry Gitlis, and The Dirty Mac
07. Jumpin Jack Flash The Rolling Stones
08. Parachute Woman The Rolling Stones
09. No Expectations The Rolling Stones
10. You Can t Always Get What You Want The Rolling Stones
11. Sympathy for the Devil The Rolling Stones
12. Salt Of The Earth The Rolling Stones</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>The.Rolling.Stones.Rock.And.Roll.Circus.1996.1080p.MBluRay.x264-TREBLE
DATE: 2019/07/09
AUDIO: [AC3 | 5.1] [ 640Kbps] [FLAC | 2.0] [ 1522Kbps]
VIDEO: [1440 | 1080] [ 9740Kbps]
SUBS: [n/a]</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>1.05</Duracion>
        <Poster>Rolling-Stones-RRC-Poster.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="121" contador="86">
        <Nombre>Luis Alberto Spinetta - National Geographic Bios</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>2019</Annus>
        <Estado>Visto</Estado>
        <Critica>Un viaje por la vida y obra de Luis Alberto Spinetta con acceso a grabaciones y material de archivos inéditos, la participación de su familia y entrevistas a los amigos y artistas que lo acompañaron y admiraron.</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>[MP4] National Geographic Bios: Luis Alberto Spinetta (2019) WEB-DL
Resolución: 844x470
Formato: WEB-DL
Codec Video: AVC
Codec Audio: AAC
Bitrate Video: 10.6 Mbps
Bitrate Audio: 256 Kbps</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>1.38</Duracion>
        <Poster>1PQTtK3.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
    <Pelicula uniqueId="122" contador="91">
        <Nombre>The Rolling Stones - Bridges to Buenos Aires 1998</Nombre>
        <Id>HD</Id>
        <Annus>2019</Annus>
        <Estado>Sin ver</Estado>
        <Critica>Die Fans in Argentinien gelten als besonders leidenschaftlich. Auch die Rolling Stones können das bezeugen, denn im Jahr 1998 gaben sie 5 ausverkaufte Konzerte hintereinander im River Plate Stadion. Das letzte Konzert der Reihe am 05.04.1998 entwickelte sich zu einem regelrechten Hexenkessel und dem würdigen Finale, das die Fans und die Stones verdienten. Als besonderer Gast kam sogar Bob Dylan für eine spezielle Version von 'Like a Rolling Stone' auf die Bühne um die Stones zu begleiten.
Setlist:
01. (I Can&#x2019;t Get No) Satisfaction
02. Let&#x2019;s Spend The Night Together
03. Flip The Switch
04. Gimme Shelter
05. Sister Morphine
06. Its Only Rock &#x2018;n&#x2019; Roll (But I Like It)
07. Saint Of Me
08. Out Of Control
09. Miss You
10. Like A Rolling Stone (featuring Bob Dylan)
11. Thief In The Night
12. Wanna Hold You
13. Little Queenie
14. When The Whip Comes Down
15. You Got Me Rocking
16. Sympathy For The Devil
17. Tumbling Dice
18. Honky Tonk Women
19. Start Me Up
20. Jumpin&#x2019; Jack Flash
21. You Can&#x2019;t Always Get What You Want
22. Brown Sugar</Critica>
        <DatosTecnicos>The.Rolling.Stones.Bridges.to.Buenos.Aires.1998.2019.720p.MBLURAY.x264-MBLURAYFANS
Title ...... = The Rolling Stones - Bridges To Buenos Aires (2019)
Genre ...... = 08.11.2019
Runtime .... = 140 Minuten
Video ..... = 960 x 720 , x264 2PASS @ 4050 kbps
Audio ...... = English DTS 5.1 @ 1.509 kbps
Size ....... = 5596 MB</DatosTecnicos>
        <Duracion>2.20</Duracion>
        <Poster>SharedImage-94832.jpg</Poster>
    </Pelicula>
</Raíz>

